<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<lines>
	<line id="1">
		<line-text>Animals that lay eggs don't have belly buttons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="2">
		<line-text>Beavers can hold their breath for 45 minutes under water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="3">
		<line-text>Slugs have four noses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="4">
		<line-text>Camels have three eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="5">
		<line-text>A honey bee can fly at 15mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="6">
		<line-text>A queen bee can lay 800-1,500 eggs per day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="7">
		<line-text>A bee has five eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="8">
		<line-text>The average speed of a housefly is 4.5 mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="9">
		<line-text>Mosquitoes are attracted to people who just ate bananas.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="10">
		<line-text>Flamingos turn pink from eating shrimp.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="11">
		<line-text>Emus and kangaroos cannot walk backward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="12">
		<line-text>Cats have over 100 vocal cords.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="13">
		<line-text>Camel's milk does not curdle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="14">
		<line-text>All porcupines float in water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="15">
		<line-text>The world's termites outweigh the world's humans about 10 to 1.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="16">
		<line-text>A hummingbird weighs less than a penny.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="17">
		<line-text>A jellyfish is approximately 95% water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="18">
		<line-text>Children tend to grow faster in the spring.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="19">
		<line-text>Broccoli is the only vegetable that is also a flower.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="20">
		<line-text>Peaches are members of the almond family.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="21">
		<line-text>Alaska has the highest percentage of people who walk to work.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="22">
		<line-text>The San Francisco cable cars are the only mobile national monument.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="23">
		<line-text>The Hawaiian alphabet has only 12 letters.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="24">
		<line-text>A ball of glass will bounce higher than a ball of rubber.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="25">
		<line-text>On average a human being will spend up to 2 weeks kissing in his/her lifetime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="26">
		<line-text>Fish have eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="27">
		<line-text>Termites eat through wood two times faster when listening to rock music!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="28">
		<line-text>If you keep a goldfish in a dark room it will eventually turn white.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="29">
		<line-text>A snail breathes through its foot.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="30">
		<line-text>Fish cough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="31">
		<line-text>An ant's sense of smell is stronger than a dog's.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="32">
		<line-text>It is possible to lead a cow up stairs but not down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="33">
		<line-text>Frogs cannot swallow with their eyes open.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="34">
		<line-text>A cat's lower jaw cannot move sideways.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="35">
		<line-text>The bullfrog is the only animal that never sleeps.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="36">
		<line-text>Elephants are capable of swimming 20 miles per day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="37">
		<line-text>Elephants are the only mammals that can't jump.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="38">
		<line-text>Giraffes have no vocal cords.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="39">
		<line-text>Cats can hear ultrasound.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="40">
		<line-text>Despite its hump, a camel has a straight spine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="41">
		<line-text>Mosquitoes have 47 teeth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="42">
		<line-text>There are 63,360 inches in a mile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="43">
		<line-text>About 11% of the people in the world are left-handed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="44">
		<line-text>The average smell weighs 760 nanograms.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="45">
		<line-text>A human brain weighs about three pounds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="46">
		<line-text>1/4 of the bones in your body are in your feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="47">
		<line-text>You blink over 10,000,000 times a year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="48">
		<line-text>A sneeze travels out of your mouth at over 100 miles an hour.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="49">
		<line-text>Brain waves can be used to power an electric train.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="50">
		<line-text>The tongue is the fastest healing part of the body.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="51">
		<line-text>Pigs can get sunburn.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="52">
		<line-text>The life span of a taste bud is about ten days.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="53">
		<line-text>The average human produces 10,000 gallons of saliva in a lifetime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="54">
		<line-text>Strawberries contain more vitamin C than oranges.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="55">
		<line-text>A one-day weather forecast requires about 10 billion math calculations.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="56">
		<line-text>Americans, on average, eat 18 acres of pizza a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="57">
		<line-text>There are 18 different animal shapes in the animal cracker zoo.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="58">
		<line-text>The longest one-syllable word is &quot;screeched.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="59">
		<line-text>No word in the English language rhymes with month.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="60">
		<line-text>There is a town called &quot;Big Ugly&quot; in West Virginia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="61">
		<line-text>The average person spends 2 weeks over his/her lifetime waiting for a traffic light to change.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="62">
		<line-text>You share your birthday with at least 9 million other people in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="63">
		<line-text>No piece of paper can be folded more than seven times.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="64">
		<line-text>Alaska is the most eastern and western state in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="65">
		<line-text>There are 119 grooves on the edge of a quarter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="66">
		<line-text>About 18 percent of animal owners share their bed with their pet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="67">
		<line-text>Alaska has more caribou than people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="68">
		<line-text>Googol is a number (1 followed by 100 zeros).</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="69">
		<line-text>Oysters can change from one gender to another and back again.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="70">
		<line-text>The Mona Lisa has no eyebrows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="71">
		<line-text>Until the 19th century, solid blocks of tea were used as money in Siberia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="72">
		<line-text>A mile on the ocean and a mile on land are not the same distance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="73">
		<line-text>A ten gallon hat holds less than one gallon of liquid.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="74">
		<line-text>The average raindrop falls at seven mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="75">
		<line-text>Fish can drown.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="76">
		<line-text>A kangaroo can jump 30 feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="77">
		<line-text>Lizards communicate by doing push-ups.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="78">
		<line-text>Squids can have eyes the size of a volleyball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="79">
		<line-text>The average American will eat 35,000 cookies in his/her lifetime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="80">
		<line-text>A turkey can run at 20 mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="81">
		<line-text>When the moon is directly overhead, you weigh slightly less.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="82">
		<line-text>You burn about 20 calories per hour chewing gum.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="83">
		<line-text>A one-minute kiss burns about 26 calories.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="84">
		<line-text>You would weigh less on the top of a mountain than at sea level.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="85">
		<line-text>You burn more calories sleeping than you do watching TV.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="86">
		<line-text>Smelling apples and/or bananas can help you lose weight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="87">
		<line-text>Frogs never drink.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="88">
		<line-text>Only male turkeys gobble.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="89">
		<line-text>At birth, a Dalmatian is always pure white.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="90">
		<line-text>The largest fish is the whale shark – it can be over 50 feet long and weigh two tons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="91">
		<line-text>Honeybees are the only insects that create a form of food for humans.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="92">
		<line-text>The hummingbird is the only bird that can fly backwards.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="93">
		<line-text>The only continent without reptiles or snakes is Antarctica.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="94">
		<line-text>The only bird that can swim and not fly is a penguin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="95">
		<line-text>A duck can't walk without bobbing its head.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="96">
		<line-text>Beavers were once the size of bears.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="97">
		<line-text>Seals sleep only one and a half minutes at a time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="98">
		<line-text>Pigeons have been trained by the U.S. Coast Guard to spot people lost at sea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="99">
		<line-text>A pigeon's feathers are heavier than its bones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="100">
		<line-text>A hummingbird's heart beats 1,400 times a minute.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="101">
		<line-text>Dragonflies have six legs but cannot walk.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="102">
		<line-text>Koalas and humans are the only animals with unique fingerprints.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="103">
		<line-text>Penguins have an organ above their eyes that converts seawater to fresh water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="104">
		<line-text>A crocodile cannot move its tongue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="105">
		<line-text>Honeybees navigate by using the sun as a compass.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="106">
		<line-text>Strawberries are the only fruits whose seeds grow on the outside.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="107">
		<line-text>The city of Los Angeles has about 3x more automobiles than people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="108">
		<line-text>Hawaii is the only U.S. state that grows coffee commercially.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="109">
		<line-text>Hawaii is the only state with one school district.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="110">
		<line-text>The square dance is the official dance of the state of Washington.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="111">
		<line-text>Hawaii is the only U.S. state never to report a temperature of zero degrees F or below.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="112">
		<line-text>&quot;Q&quot; is the only letter in the alphabet not appearing in the name of any U.S. state.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="113">
		<line-text>Texas is the only state that permits residents to cast absentee ballots from space.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="114">
		<line-text>Lake Superior is the world's largest lake.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="115">
		<line-text>The smallest county in America is New York County, better known as Manhattan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="116">
		<line-text>Panama is the only place in the world where you can see the sun rise on the Pacific and set on the Atlantic.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="117">
		<line-text>The tallest man was 8 ft. 11 in.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="118">
		<line-text>Theodore Roosevelt was the only president who was blind in one eye.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="119">
		<line-text>The first sport to be filmed was boxing in 1894.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="120">
		<line-text>The speed limit in NYC was eight mph in 1895.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="121">
		<line-text>In 1926, the first outdoor mini-golf courses were built on rooftops in NYC.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="122">
		<line-text>Swimming pools in the U.S. contain enough water to cover San Francisco.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="123">
		<line-text>The first MTV video was &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; by the Buggles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="124">
		<line-text>The first TV show to ever be put into reruns was &quot;The Lone Ranger.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="125">
		<line-text>One alternate title that had been considered for NBC's hit &quot;Friends&quot; was &quot;Insomnia Café.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="126">
		<line-text>The temperature of the sun can reach up to 15 million degrees Fahrenheit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="127">
		<line-text>The first penny had the motto &quot;Mind your own business.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="128">
		<line-text>The first vacuum was so large, it was brought to a house by horses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="129">
		<line-text>Your eye expands up to 45% when looking at something pleasing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="130">
		<line-text>Before mercury, brandy was used to fill thermometers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="131">
		<line-text>You'd have to play ping-pong for about 12 hours to lose one pound.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="132">
		<line-text>One brow wrinkle is the result of 200,000 frowns.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="133">
		<line-text>The first human-made object to break the sound barrier was a whip.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="134">
		<line-text>In 1878, the first telephone book ever issued contained only 50 names.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="135">
		<line-text>The most sensitive parts of the body are the mouth and the fingertips.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="136">
		<line-text>The eye makes movements 50 times every second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="137">
		<line-text>The world's biggest pyramid is not in Egypt, but in Mexico.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="138">
		<line-text>In 1634, tulip bulbs were a form of currency in Holland.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="139">
		<line-text>The first bike was called a hobbyhorse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="140">
		<line-text>The first sailing boats were built in Egypt.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="141">
		<line-text>The first ballpoint pens were sold in 1945 for $12.00.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="142">
		<line-text>The first VCR was made in 1956 and was the size of a piano.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="143">
		<line-text>A rainbow can only be seen in the morning or late afternoon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="144">
		<line-text>The Capitol building in Washington, D.C. has 365 steps to represent every day of the year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="145">
		<line-text>The most used letters in the English language are E, T, A, O, I and N.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="146">
		<line-text>A male kangaroo is called a boomer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="147">
		<line-text>A female kangaroo is called a flyer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="148">
		<line-text>Antarctica is the driest, coldest, windiest, and highest continent on earth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="149">
		<line-text>The Sahara Desert stretches farther than the distance from California to New York.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="150">
		<line-text>Thailand means &quot;Land of the Free.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="151">
		<line-text>Popcorn was invented by the American Indians.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="152">
		<line-text>Jupiter spins so fast that there is a new sunrise nearly every 10 hours.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="153">
		<line-text>The year that read the same upside down was 1961. That won't happen again until 6009.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="154">
		<line-text>You don't have to be a lawyer to be a Supreme Court Justice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="155">
		<line-text>Eleven of the 50 U.S. states are named after an actual person.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="156">
		<line-text>If you doubled one penny every day for 30 days, you would have $5,368,709.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="157">
		<line-text>The first person crossed Niagara Falls by tightrope in 1859.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="158">
		<line-text>The U.S. is the largest country named after a real person (Amerigo Vespucci).</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="159">
		<line-text>The only one-syllabled U.S. state is Maine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="160">
		<line-text>Atlantic salmon are capable of leaping 15 feet high.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="161">
		<line-text>Over 1 million Earths would fit inside the Sun.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="162">
		<line-text>Before 1687 clocks were made with only an hour hand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="163">
		<line-text>Add up opposing sides of a dice cue and you'll always get seven.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="164">
		<line-text>The average koala sleeps 22 hours each day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="165">
		<line-text>Galapagos turtles can take up to three weeks to digest a meal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="166">
		<line-text>Tennessee banned the use of a lasso to catch fish.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="167">
		<line-text>Blackboard chalk contains no chalk.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="168">
		<line-text>A jackrabbit can travel more than 12 feet in one hop.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="169">
		<line-text>An electric eel can release a charge powerful enough to start 50 cars.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="170">
		<line-text>Porcupines each have 30,000 quills.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="171">
		<line-text>The game of basketball was first played using a soccer ball and two peach baskets.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="172">
		<line-text>America's 1st roller coaster was built in 1827 to carry coal from a mine to boats below.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="173">
		<line-text>There is a town in South Dakota named Tea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="174">
		<line-text>The Caspian Sea is actually a lake.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="175">
		<line-text>Caterpillars have over 2,000 muscles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="176">
		<line-text>The blue whale's heart is the size of a small car.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="177">
		<line-text>There are seven letters that look the same upside down as right side up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="178">
		<line-text>The biggest pig in recorded history weighed almost one ton.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="179">
		<line-text>Cows give more milk when they listen to music.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="180">
		<line-text>The number of times a cricket chirps in 15 seconds, plus 37, will give you the current air temperature.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="181">
		<line-text>An ostrich's brain is smaller than its eye.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="182">
		<line-text>&quot;Challenger Deep&quot; is the deepest point on Earth and can hold 25 Empire State Buildings end to end.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="183">
		<line-text>The only cactus plantation in the world is in Mississippi.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="184">
		<line-text>If you put all the streets in New York City in a straight line, they would stretch to Japan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="185">
		<line-text>The watermelon seed-spitting world record is about 70 feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="186">
		<line-text>The first typewriter was called the &quot;literary piano.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="187">
		<line-text>The &quot;silk&quot; of a spider is stronger than steel threads of the same diameter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="188">
		<line-text>Snoopy is the most common dog name beginning with the letter S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="189">
		<line-text>The 1st public message to be transmitted via Morse code was &quot;A patient waiter is no loser.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="190">
		<line-text>Mongolians invented lemonade around 1299 A.D.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="191">
		<line-text>There are more French restaurants in New York City than in Paris.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="192">
		<line-text>The first TV remote control, introduced in 1950, was called Lazy Bones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="193">
		<line-text>The only bird who can see the color blue is the owl.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="194">
		<line-text>Among North Atlantic lobsters, about 1 in 5,000 is born bright blue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="195">
		<line-text>There are more saunas than cars in Finland.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="196">
		<line-text>The first food eaten in space by a U.S. astronaut was applesauce.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="197">
		<line-text>The original recipe for chocolate contained chili powder instead of sugar.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="198">
		<line-text>Underwater hockey is played with a 3-pound puck.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="199">
		<line-text>Bowling pins need to tip over a mere 7 1/2 degrees to fall down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="200">
		<line-text>Your breathing rate increases when you start to type.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="201">
		<line-text>About 90% of all garlic consumed in the U.S. comes from Gilroy, CA.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="202">
		<line-text>Double Dutch jump rope is considered a cross-training sport.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="203">
		<line-text>One lemon tree will produce about 1,500 lemons a year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="204">
		<line-text>Horseback riding can improve your posture.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="205">
		<line-text>Colors like red, yellow and orange make you hungry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="206">
		<line-text>Dim lights reduce your appetite.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="207">
		<line-text>At birth a human has 350 bones, but only 206 bones when full grown.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="208">
		<line-text>Each year, the average American eats about 15 pounds of apples.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="209">
		<line-text>It took the first man to walk around the world four years, three months and 16 days to complete his journey.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="210">
		<line-text>Grizzly bears run as fast as the average horse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="211">
		<line-text>China only has one time zone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="212">
		<line-text>Canada has the longest coastline of any country in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="213">
		<line-text>The amount of concrete used in the Hoover Dam could build a highway from New York to California.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="214">
		<line-text>The original name of Nashville, Tennessee was Big Salt Lick.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="215">
		<line-text>If you drive from Los Angeles to Reno, NV, you will be heading west.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="216">
		<line-text>A compass needle does not point directly north.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="217">
		<line-text>Mt. Everest has grown one foot over the last 100 years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="218">
		<line-text>In ancient Rome, lemons were used as an antidote to all poisons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="219">
		<line-text>The height of the Eiffel Tower varies by as much as 6 inches depending on the temperature.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="220">
		<line-text>Wisconsin has points located farther east than parts of Florida.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="221">
		<line-text>Four Corners, AZ, is the only place where a person can stand in 4 states at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="222">
		<line-text>Africa is divided into more countries than any other continent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="223">
		<line-text>Heavier, not bigger lemons, produce more juice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="224">
		<line-text>Vermont is the only New England state without a seacoast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="225">
		<line-text>No only child has been a U.S. President.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="226">
		<line-text>Leonardo da Vinci could draw with one hand while writing with the other.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="227">
		<line-text>In 1860, Abraham Lincoln grew a beard at the suggestion of an 11-year-old girl.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="228">
		<line-text>David Rice Atchison was President of the United States for only one day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="229">
		<line-text>The sail fish has been clocked at speeds of over 60 miles per hour.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="230">
		<line-text>The Library of Congress has over 600 miles of shelves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="231">
		<line-text>Pennsylvania is misspelled on the Liberty Bell, because that is how they spelled it in the 18th century.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="232">
		<line-text>William Shakespeare was born and died on the same day: April 23.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="233">
		<line-text>Ketchup was once sold as a medicine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="234">
		<line-text>Napoleon suffered from a fear of cats.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="235">
		<line-text>In 1900, 1/3 of all automobiles in New York City were powered by electricity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="236">
		<line-text>The 4th Earl of Sandwich invented the sandwich so he could eat and gamble at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="237">
		<line-text>In the Middle Ages, chicken soup was considered an aphrodisiac.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="238">
		<line-text>Ancient Egyptians believed the &quot;vein of love&quot; ran from the third finger on the left hand to the heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="239">
		<line-text>The word &quot;facetious&quot; features all the vowels in alphabetical order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="240">
		<line-text>The standard Chinese typewriter has 1,500 characters.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="241">
		<line-text>A flea can jump 30,000 times without stopping.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="242">
		<line-text>&quot;O&quot; is the oldest letter of the alphabet, dating back to 3000 B.C.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="243">
		<line-text>The Japanese word &quot;judo&quot; means &quot;the gentle way.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="244">
		<line-text>No two lip impressions are the same.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="245">
		<line-text>It took Leonardo da Vinci 12 years to paint the lips of Mona Lisa.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="246">
		<line-text>Top-performing companies are called &quot;blue chips&quot; after the costliest chips in casinos.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="247">
		<line-text>The name for the space between your eyebrows is &quot;nasion.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="248">
		<line-text>The word &quot;purple&quot; does not rhyme with any other word in the English language.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="249">
		<line-text>The legs of bats are too weak to support their weight, so they hang upside down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="250">
		<line-text>75% of people wash from top to bottom in the shower.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="251">
		<line-text>On average, you'll spend a year of your life looking for misplaced objects.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="252">
		<line-text>Chewing gum was invented in New York City in 1870 by Thomas Adams.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="253">
		<line-text>The Statue of Liberty features 7 points in her crown- one for each of the continents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="254">
		<line-text>The world's first escalator was built in Coney Island, NY, in 1896.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="255">
		<line-text>The top of the Empire State Building was originally built as a place to anchor blimps.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="256">
		<line-text>The area code in Cape Canaveral, Fl, is 321.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="257">
		<line-text>Ohio is the only U.S. state that does not have a rectangular flag.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="258">
		<line-text>Long Island is the largest island in the Continental U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="259">
		<line-text>Maine produces more toothpicks than any other state in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="260">
		<line-text>The last letter to be added to our alphabet was J.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="261">
		<line-text>There are more doughnut shops per capita in Canada than in any other country.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="262">
		<line-text>There is an underground mushroom in Oregon that measures 3.5 miles across.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="263">
		<line-text>Of the 92 counties in Indiana, only 5 observe daylight savings time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="264">
		<line-text>California and Arizona grow approximately 95% of the fresh lemons in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="265">
		<line-text>The term 007 was derived from 20007, the home zip code of many Washington, D.C. agents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="266">
		<line-text>Leonardo da Vinci discovered that a tree's rings reveal its age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="267">
		<line-text>The popsicle was invented in 1905 by an 11-year-old boy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="268">
		<line-text>The medical term for writer's cramp is graphospasm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="269">
		<line-text>A male firefly's light is twice as bright as a female's.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="270">
		<line-text>It is estimated that the world's oceans contain 10 billion tons of gold.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="271">
		<line-text>Cold water weighs less than hot water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="272">
		<line-text>Storm clouds hold about 6 trillion raindrops.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="273">
		<line-text>The weight of the moon is 81 billion tons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="274">
		<line-text>Bamboo can grow three feet in one day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="275">
		<line-text>A tune that gets stuck in your head is called an earworm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="276">
		<line-text>You exhale air at 15 m.p.h.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="277">
		<line-text>A baboon is a variety of lemon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="278">
		<line-text>Butterflies were formerly known by the name Flutterby.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="279">
		<line-text>Mexican jumping beans jump to get out of sunlight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="280">
		<line-text>&quot;Arachibutlphobia&quot; is the fear of peanut butter sticking to the roof of your mouth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="281">
		<line-text>Pearls dissolve in vinegar.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="282">
		<line-text>Borborygmi is the noise that your stomach makes when you are hungry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="283">
		<line-text>The center of some golf balls contain honey.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="284">
		<line-text>International tug of war rules state that the rope must be over 100-feet long.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="285">
		<line-text>In 2003, a 6-year-old from Naples, FL was ticketed for not having a permit for her lemonade stand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="286">
		<line-text>On Valentine's Day, there is no charge to get married in the Empire State Building's chapel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="287">
		<line-text>Heat, not sunlight, ripens tomatoes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="288">
		<line-text>A housefly hums in the key of F.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="289">
		<line-text>Endocarp is the edible pulp inside a lemon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="290">
		<line-text>Thomas Edison coined the word &quot;hello&quot; and introduced it as a way to answer the phone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="291">
		<line-text>&quot;Way&quot; is the most frequently used noun in the English language.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="292">
		<line-text>The &quot;high five&quot; was introduced by a professional baseball player in 1977.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="293">
		<line-text>&quot;Disco&quot; means &quot;I learn&quot; in Latin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="294">
		<line-text>It costs the U.S. government 2.5 cents to produce a quarter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="295">
		<line-text>Baboons were once trained by Egyptians to wait on tables.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="296">
		<line-text>The official state gem of Washington is petrified wood.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="297">
		<line-text>Mount Katahdin in Maine is the first place in the U.S. to get sunlight each morning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="298">
		<line-text>Each year, the average person walks the distance from NY to Miami.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="299">
		<line-text>New York City's public school students represent about 188 different countries.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="300">
		<line-text>In the U.S., all interstate highways that run east to west are even-numbered.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="301">
		<line-text>Three out of every six Americans live within fifty miles of where they were born.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="302">
		<line-text>The raised bump reflectors on U.S. roads are named &quot;Botts dots.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="303">
		<line-text>Nearly 9,000 people injure themselves with a toothpick each year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="304">
		<line-text>It is impossible to sneeze with your eyes open.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="305">
		<line-text>The dragonfly can reach speeds of up to 36 mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="306">
		<line-text>Hippos can open their mouths 180 degrees.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="307">
		<line-text>Christopher Columbus brought the first lemon seeds to America.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="308">
		<line-text>The East Antarctic Ice Sheet is as thick as the Alps Mountains are high.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="309">
		<line-text>The deepest place in the ocean is about seven miles deep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="310">
		<line-text>Panda bears eat up to 16 hours a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="311">
		<line-text>Bald eagles can swim using a stroke similar to the butterfly stroke.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="312">
		<line-text>Lifejackets used to be filled with sunflower seeds for flotation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="313">
		<line-text>Two trees can create enough oxygen for a family of four.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="314">
		<line-text>The T-rex’s closest living relative is the chicken.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="315">
		<line-text>Chameleons can move both their eyes in different directions at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="316">
		<line-text>Many butterflies and moths are able to taste with their feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="317">
		<line-text>A jiffy is an actual time measurement equaling 1/100th of a second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="318">
		<line-text>Greyhounds can reach speeds of 45 miles per hour.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="319">
		<line-text>Apples, peaches and raspberries are all members of the rose family.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="320">
		<line-text>U.S. paper currency isn’t made of paper – it’s actually a blend of cotton and linen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="321">
		<line-text>The ZIP in the ZIP code stands for Zone Improvement Plan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="322">
		<line-text>Kangaroos can’t walk backwards.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="323">
		<line-text>The Empire State Building has 73 elevators.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="324">
		<line-text>Lemons ripen after you pick them, but oranges do not.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="325">
		<line-text>There are 118 ridges on the edge of a United States dime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="326">
		<line-text>There are 336 dimples on a regulation American golf ball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="327">
		<line-text>One acre of peanuts will make about 30,000 peanut butter sandwiches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="328">
		<line-text>A twit is the technical term for a pregnant goldfish.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="329">
		<line-text>In the U.S. a pig has to weigh more than 180 lbs to be called a hog.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="330">
		<line-text>Bloodhounds can track a man by smell for up to 100 miles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="331">
		<line-text>Beavers have orange teeth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="332">
		<line-text>The woodpecker can hammer wood up to 16 times per second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="333">
		<line-text>Mount Everest rises a few millimeters every year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="334">
		<line-text>Snails can sleep for up to three years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="335">
		<line-text>The pupils in goats’ eyes are rectangular.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="336">
		<line-text>Jousting is the official sport in the state of Maryland.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="337">
		<line-text>Bees’ wings beat about 11,400 times per minute.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="338">
		<line-text>The pound sign, or #, is called an octothorp.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="339">
		<line-text>The Statue of Liberty wears a size 879 sandal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="340">
		<line-text>If there are two full moons in a month, the second one is called a blue moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="341">
		<line-text>You breathe in about 13 pints of air every minute.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="342">
		<line-text>Sound travels quicker in water than in air.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="343">
		<line-text>A group of cats is called a clowder.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="344">
		<line-text>Human eyes have over two million working parts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="345">
		<line-text>There are approximately 9,000 taste buds on your tongue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="346">
		<line-text>Raindrops can fall as fast as 20 miles per hour.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="347">
		<line-text>Polar bear fur is transparent, not white.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="348">
		<line-text>Lobsters can live up to 50 years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="349">
		<line-text>The first traffic light was in use in London in 1868, before the advent of cars.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="350">
		<line-text>Fresh cranberries can be bounced like a rubber ball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="351">
		<line-text>A group of a dozen or more cows is called a ‘flink.’</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="352">
		<line-text>Astronauts actually get taller when in space.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="353">
		<line-text>A fifteen-year-old boy invented earmuffs in 1873.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="354">
		<line-text>There is a ranch in Texas that is bigger than the entire state of Rhode Island.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="355">
		<line-text>The dot over the letter i is called a tittle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="356">
		<line-text>The great white shark can go up to three months between meals.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="357">
		<line-text>During the Boston Tea Party, 342 chests of tea were thrown into the harbor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="358">
		<line-text>Pluto takes 248 years to orbit the sun once.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="359">
		<line-text>Camels have three eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="360">
		<line-text>454 U.S. dollar bills weigh exactly one pound.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="361">
		<line-text>Dairy cows drink up to 50 gallons of water per day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="362">
		<line-text>A nautical mile is 800 feet longer than a land mile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="363">
		<line-text>Antarctica has as much ice as the Atlantic Ocean has water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="364">
		<line-text>Candles will burn longer and drip less if they are placed in the freezer a few hours before using.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="365">
		<line-text>Over 50 percent of your body heat is lost through your head and neck.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="366">
		<line-text>Smile more – every two thousand frowns creates one wrinkle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="367">
		<line-text>New York taxi drivers collectively speak about 60 languages.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="368">
		<line-text>New York City is made up of 50 islands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="369">
		<line-text>The strike note of The Liberty Bell is E flat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="370">
		<line-text>Pigs were banished from Philadelphia's city streets in 1710.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="371">
		<line-text>About 40% of America's population lives within a one day drive to Philadelphia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="372">
		<line-text>It is against the law to put pretzels in bags in Philadelphia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="373">
		<line-text>In the game Monopoly, the properties are named after streets in Atlantic City.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="374">
		<line-text>The oldest living animal ever found was a 405 year-old clam, named Ming by researchers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="375">
		<line-text>More than 180 countries celebrate Earth Day together every April 22nd.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="376">
		<line-text>At 5 feet, the whooping crane is the tallest bird in North America.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="377">
		<line-text>A full-grown tree produces enough oxygen to support a family of four.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="378">
		<line-text>Unlike your housecat, the Siberian tiger actually loves to swim!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="379">
		<line-text>A tiger’s night vision is six times better than a human’s.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="380">
		<line-text>More Siberian tigers live in zoos than in the wild.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="381">
		<line-text>The jaguar, the largest cat in the Western Hemisphere, once lived all over the southern U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="382">
		<line-text>The giant panda can eat up to 83 lbs of bamboo a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="383">
		<line-text>Wildlife Forever has helped plant more than 132,000 trees in America since its founding in 1987.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="384">
		<line-text>Manhattan Island was once home to as many different species as Yellowstone National Park.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="385">
		<line-text>Dogs can make about 10 sounds, while cats make about 100.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="386">
		<line-text>A Pelican can hold more food in its beak than its belly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="387">
		<line-text>The average cat can jump 5 times as high as its tail is long.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="388">
		<line-text>Flying fish leap out of the water at 20 mph or more, and can glide for over 500 feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="389">
		<line-text>The roadrunner chases after its prey at a blurring speed of up to 25 mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="390">
		<line-text>The archer fish can spit water up to 7 feet to shoot down bugs from overhanging leaves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="391">
		<line-text>The spotted skunk does a handstand to warn off its enemies before it sprays its stench.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="392">
		<line-text>A male cricket's ear is located on the tibia of its leg.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="393">
		<line-text>Spiny lobsters migrate in groups of 50 or more, forming a conga line on the ocean floor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="394">
		<line-text>The National Park Service manages over 350 parks on 80 million acres of public land.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="395">
		<line-text>Stepping out for a walk every day can actually help you sleep better at night.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="396">
		<line-text>Recycled paper is made using 40% less energy than normal paper.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="397">
		<line-text>Every ton of recycled paper saves about 17 trees.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="398">
		<line-text>Steel is 100% recyclable.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="399">
		<line-text>Most rechargeable batteries can be recharged up to 1,000 times.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="400">
		<line-text>An egg that is fresh will sink in water, but a stale one won't.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="401">
		<line-text>A camel can drink 25 gallons of water in less than three minutes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="402">
		<line-text>In one day, a full-grown oak tree expels 7 tons of water through its leaves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="403">
		<line-text>There is a museum of strawberries in Belgium.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="404">
		<line-text>Mangoes are the most-consumed fruit in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="405">
		<line-text>Strawberries have an average of 200 seeds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="406">
		<line-text>A strawberry is not an actual berry, but a banana is.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="407">
		<line-text>Fresh apples float because 25 percent of their volume is air.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="408">
		<line-text>The peach was the first fruit to be eaten on the moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="409">
		<line-text>A pineapple is neither an apple or a pine. It is, in fact, a large berry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="410">
		<line-text>Only female mosquitoes bite.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="411">
		<line-text>A polar bear cannot be seen by an infrared camera, due to its transparent fur.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="412">
		<line-text>A spider’s silk is stronger than steel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="413">
		<line-text>The planet Saturn's density is lower than water; in fact, it would float if placed in water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="414">
		<line-text>Twins have a very high occurrence of left handedness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="415">
		<line-text>The fear of vegetables is called lachanophobia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="416">
		<line-text>There are over 2,000 different species of cactuses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="417">
		<line-text>The chicken is the closest living relative of Tyrannosaurus Rex.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="418">
		<line-text>All scorpions glow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="419">
		<line-text>Potatoes have more chromosomes than humans.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="420">
		<line-text>A full moon is nine times brighter than a half moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="421">
		<line-text>The human brain takes up 2% of human body weight but uses 20% of its energy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="422">
		<line-text>Poison Ivy is not Ivy and Poison Oak is not an Oak. They are both part of the Cashew family.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="423">
		<line-text>Plants, like humans, can run a fever if they are sick.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="424">
		<line-text>Over half of the world's geysers are found in Yellowstone National Park.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="425">
		<line-text>A group of geese on the ground is a gaggle, a group of geese in the air is a skein.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="426">
		<line-text>Polar bears can smell a seal from 20 miles away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="427">
		<line-text>Armadillos have four babies at a time and they are always all the same sex.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="428">
		<line-text>The only insect that can turn its head is a praying mantis.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="429">
		<line-text>Alaska was bought from Russia for about 2 cents an acre.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="430">
		<line-text>A dog's average body temperature is 101 degrees Fahrenheit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="431">
		<line-text>The common garden worm has five pairs of hearts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="432">
		<line-text>Flamingos can only eat with their heads upside down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="433">
		<line-text>A group of twelve or more cows is called a flink.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="434">
		<line-text>A group of goats is called a trip.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="435">
		<line-text>An alligator can go through 3,000 teeth in a lifetime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="436">
		<line-text>There are more chickens than people in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="437">
		<line-text>Penguins can jump 6 feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="438">
		<line-text>There are approximately 7,000 feathers on an eagle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="439">
		<line-text>The only lizard that has a voice is the Gecko.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="440">
		<line-text>A rhinoceros horn is made of compacted hair.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="441">
		<line-text>Dolphins sleep with one eye open.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="442">
		<line-text>A duck has three eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="443">
		<line-text>Tigers have striped skin, not just striped fur.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="444">
		<line-text>The muzzle of a lion is like a fingerprint - no two lions have the same pattern of whiskers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="445">
		<line-text>The hippopotamus has the capability to remain underwater for as long as five minutes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="446">
		<line-text>Most elephants weigh less than the tongue of a blue whale.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="447">
		<line-text>If a sheep and a goat mate the offspring is called a geep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="448">
		<line-text>Pistol shrimp can make a noise loud enough to break glass.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="449">
		<line-text>Mountain goats aren't actually goats. They are antelopes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="450">
		<line-text>Koalas only drink water in extreme heat or drought.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="451">
		<line-text>Bees are born fully grown.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="452">
		<line-text>Ferret comes from the Latin word for little thief.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="453">
		<line-text>Cats have 2 sets of vocal cords: one for purring and one for meowing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="454">
		<line-text>Some bears build nests in trees to sunbathe and rest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="455">
		<line-text>A group of jellyfish is called a smack.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="456">
		<line-text>The indentation between the nose and the upper lip is called the philtrum.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="457">
		<line-text>The human jaw can generate a force up to 200 pounds on the molars.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="458">
		<line-text>The human brain is about 80% water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="459">
		<line-text>The middle finger has the fastest growing nail.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="460">
		<line-text>The brain operates on the same amount of power as a 10-watt light bulb.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="461">
		<line-text>Like fingerprints, everyone's tongue print is different.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="462">
		<line-text>Your big toe only has 2 bones and the rest have 3.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="463">
		<line-text>The average person takes 23,000 breaths a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="464">
		<line-text>It is illegal to run out of gas in Youngstown, Ohio.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="465">
		<line-text>Tennessee was previously named Franklin after Benjamin Franklin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="466">
		<line-text>The official color of California's Golden Gate Bridge is International Orange.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="467">
		<line-text>It is not possible to tickle yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="468">
		<line-text>Antarctica is the only continent with no owls.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="469">
		<line-text>There are 293 ways to make change for a dollar.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="470">
		<line-text>Shakespeare invented the word assassination and bump.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="471">
		<line-text>French author Michel Thayer published a 233 page novel which has no verbs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="472">
		<line-text>Australia is the only continent without an active volcano.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="473">
		<line-text>The dots on a domino are called pips.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="474">
		<line-text>111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="475">
		<line-text>Tug-of-war was an Olympic sport in the early 1900's.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="476">
		<line-text>The name of the city we call Bangkok is 115 letters long in the Thai language.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="477">
		<line-text>In Ancient Greece, throwing an apple to a woman was considered a marriage proposal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="478">
		<line-text>Karate originated in India.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="479">
		<line-text>The infinity sign is called a lemniscate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="480">
		<line-text>Children grow faster during springtime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="481">
		<line-text>It takes an interaction of 72 muscles to produce human speech.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="482">
		<line-text>Sailors once thought wearing gold earrings improved eyesight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="483">
		<line-text>Our eyes are always the same size from birth, but our nose and ears never stop growing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="484">
		<line-text>Your skull is made up of 29 different bones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="485">
		<line-text>Every hour more than one billion cells in the body must be replaced.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="486">
		<line-text>Women's hearts typically beat faster than men's hearts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="487">
		<line-text>Adults laugh only about 15 to 100 times a day, while six-year-olds laugh an average of 300 times a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="488">
		<line-text>Children have more taste buds than adults.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="489">
		<line-text>Right handed people tend to chew food on the right side and lefties chew on the left.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="490">
		<line-text>A cucumber consists of 96% water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="491">
		<line-text>Vanilla is used to make chocolate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="492">
		<line-text>One lump of sugar is equivalent to three feet of sugar cane.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="493">
		<line-text>A lemon contains more sugar than a strawberry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="494">
		<line-text>Until the nineteenth century, solid blocks of tea were used as money in Siberia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="495">
		<line-text>Wild camels once roamed Arizona's deserts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="496">
		<line-text>New York was the first state to require cars to have license plates.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="497">
		<line-text>Miami installed the first ATM for rollerbladers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="498">
		<line-text>Hawaii has its own time zone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="499">
		<line-text>Oregon has more ghost towns than any other US state.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="500">
		<line-text>Cleveland, OH is home to the first electric traffic lights.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="501">
		<line-text>South Carolina is home to the first tea farm in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="502">
		<line-text>The term rookies comes from a Civil War term, reckie, which was short for recruit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="503">
		<line-text>Taft was the heaviest U.S. President at 329lbs; Madison was the smallest at 100lbs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="504">
		<line-text>Harry Truman was the last U.S. President to not have a college degree.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="505">
		<line-text>Abraham Lincoln was the tallest U.S. President at 6'4&quot;, while James Madison was the shortest at 5'4&quot;.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="506">
		<line-text>Franklin Roosevelt was related to 5 U.S. Presidents by blood and 6 by marriage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="507">
		<line-text>Thomas Jefferson invented the coat hanger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="508">
		<line-text>Theodore Roosevelt had a pet bear while in office.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="509">
		<line-text>President Warren G. Harding once lost white house china in a poker game.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="510">
		<line-text>Ulysses Simpson Grant was fined $20.00 for speeding on his horse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="511">
		<line-text>President William Taft weighed over 300 lbs and once got stuck in the white house bathtub.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="512">
		<line-text>President William McKinley had a pet parrot that he named “Washington Post.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="513">
		<line-text>Harry S. Truman's middle name is S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="514">
		<line-text>The youngest U.S. president to be in office was Theodore Roosevelt at age 42.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="515">
		<line-text>Most Koala bears can sleep up to 22 hours a day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="516">
		<line-text>In 1859, 24 rabbits were released in Australia. Within 6 years, the population grew to 2 million.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="517">
		<line-text>Butterflies can taste with their hind feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="518">
		<line-text>A strand from the web of a golden spider is as strong as a steel wire of the same size.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="519">
		<line-text>The bumblebee bat is one of the smallest mammals on Earth. It weighs less than a penny.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="520">
		<line-text>The Valley of Square Trees in Panama is the only known place in the world where trees have rectangular trunks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="521">
		<line-text>The original Cinderella was Egyptian and wore fur slippers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="522">
		<line-text>The plastic things on the end of shoelaces are called aglets.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="523">
		<line-text>Neckties were first worn in Croatia, which is why they were called cravats.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="524">
		<line-text>Barbie's full name is Barbara Millicent Roberts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="525">
		<line-text>The first TV toy commercial aired in 1946 for Mr. Potato Head.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="526">
		<line-text>If done perfectly, any Rubik's Cube combination can be solved in 17 turns.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="527">
		<line-text>The side of a hammer is called a cheek.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="528">
		<line-text>In Athens, Greece, a driver's license can be taken away by law if the driver is deemed either unbathed or poorly dressed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="529">
		<line-text>In Texas, it is illegal to graffiti someone's cow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="530">
		<line-text>Less than 3% of the water on Earth is fresh.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="531">
		<line-text>A cubic mile of fog is made up of less than a gallon of water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="532">
		<line-text>The Saturn V moon rocket consumed 15 tons of fuel per second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="533">
		<line-text>A manned rocket can reach the moon in less time than it took a stagecoach to travel the length of England.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="534">
		<line-text>At room temperature, the average air molecule travels at the speed of a rifle bullet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="535">
		<line-text>The lollipop was named after one of the most famous Racehorses in the early 1900s, Lolly Pop.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="536">
		<line-text>Buzz Aldrin was one of the first men on the moon. His mother's maiden name was also Moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="537">
		<line-text>Maine is the only state with a one-syllable name.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="538">
		<line-text>The highest denomination issued by the U.S. was the 100,000 dollar bill.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="539">
		<line-text>The White House was originally called the President's Palace. It became The White House in 1901.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="540">
		<line-text>George Washington was the only unanimously elected President.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="541">
		<line-text>John Adams was the only President to be defeated by his Vice President, Thomas Jefferson.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="542">
		<line-text>New York City has over 800 miles of subway track.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="543">
		<line-text>Manatees' eyes close in a circular motion, much like the aperture of a camera.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="544">
		<line-text>Even though it is nearly twice as far away from the Sun as Mercury, Venus is by far the hottest planet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="545">
		<line-text>The nothingness of a black hole generates a sound in the key of B flat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="546">
		<line-text>Horses can't vomit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="547">
		<line-text>Babies are born with about 300 separate bones, but adults have 206.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="548">
		<line-text>Newborn babies cannot cry tears for at least three weeks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="549">
		<line-text>A day on Venus lasts longer than a year on Venus.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="550">
		<line-text>Squirrels lose more than half of the nuts they hide.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="551">
		<line-text>The penny was the first U.S. coin to feature the likeness of an actual person.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="552">
		<line-text>Forty percent of twins invent their own language.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="553">
		<line-text>In South Korea, it is against the rules for a professional baseball player to wear cabbage leaves inside of his hat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="554">
		<line-text>Curly hair follicles are oval, while straight hair follicles are round.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="555">
		<line-text>George Washington had false teeth made of gold, ivory, and lead - but never wood.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="556">
		<line-text>Napoleon Bonaparte was actually not short. At 5' 7&quot;, he was average height for his time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="557">
		<line-text>The Inca built the largest and wealthiest empire in South America, but had no concept of money.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="558">
		<line-text>It is against the law to use &quot;The Star Spangled Banner&quot; as dance music in Massachusetts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="559">
		<line-text>Queen Cleopatra of Egypt was not actually Egyptian.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="560">
		<line-text>Early football fields were painted with both horizontal and vertical lines, creating a pattern that resembled a gridiron.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="561">
		<line-text>Two national capitals are named after U.S. presidents: Washington, D.C., and Monrovia, the capital of Liberia.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="562">
		<line-text>The first spam message was transmitted over telegraph wires in 1864.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="563">
		<line-text>A pearl can be dissolved by vinegar.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="564">
		<line-text>Queen Isabella I of Spain, who funded Columbus' voyage across the ocean, claimed to have only bathed twice in her life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="565">
		<line-text>The longest attack of hiccups ever lasted 68 years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="566">
		<line-text>A bolt of lightning can reach temperatures hotter than 50,000 degrees Fahrenheit - five times hotter than the sun.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="567">
		<line-text>At the deepest point in the ocean, the water pressure is equivalent to having about 50 jumbo jets piled on top of you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="568">
		<line-text>In only 7.6 billion years, the sun will reach its maximum size and will shine 3,000 times brighter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="569">
		<line-text>The state of Alabama once financed the construction of a bridge by holding a rooster auction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="570">
		<line-text>Federal law once allowed the government to quarantine people who came in contact with aliens.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="571">
		<line-text>There are 21 &quot;secret&quot; highways that are part of the Interstate Highway System. They are not identified as such by road signs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="572">
		<line-text>The aphid insect is born pregnant.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="573">
		<line-text>John Wilkes Booth's brother saved the life of Abraham Lincoln's son.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="574">
		<line-text>It is illegal in the United Kingdom to handle salmon in suspicious circumstances.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="575">
		<line-text>It is illegal to play annoying games in the street in the United Kingdom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="576">
		<line-text>Tennis was originally played with bare hands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="577">
		<line-text>-40 degrees Fahrenheit is the same temperatures as -40 degrees Celsius.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="578">
		<line-text>U.S. President John Tyler had 15 children, the last of which was born when he was 70 years old.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="579">
		<line-text>Dolphins are unable to smell.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="580">
		<line-text>Charlie Chaplin failed to make the finals of a Charlie Chaplin look-alike contest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="581">
		<line-text>The name of the city of Portland, Oregon was decided by a coin toss. The name that lost was Boston.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="582">
		<line-text>The letter J is the only letter in the alphabet that does not appear anywhere on the periodic table of the elements.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="583">
		<line-text>'K' was chosen to stand for a strikeout in baseball because 'S' was being used to denote a sacrifice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="584">
		<line-text>A dimpled golf ball produces less drag and flies farther than a smooth golf ball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="585">
		<line-text>When grazing or resting, cows tend to align their bodies with the magnetic north and south poles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="586">
		<line-text>President Chester A. Arthur owned 80 pairs of pants, which he changed several times per day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="587">
		<line-text>Cows do not have upper front teeth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="588">
		<line-text>Between 1979 and 1999, the planet Neptune was farther from the Sun than Pluto. This won't happen again until 2227.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="589">
		<line-text>When creating a mummy, Ancient Egyptians removed the brain by inserting a hook through the nostrils.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="590">
		<line-text>All of the major candidates in the 1992, 1996, and 2008 U.S. presidential elections were left-handed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="591">
		<line-text>In Switzerland, it is illegal to own only one guinea pig because they are prone to loneliness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="592">
		<line-text>The first American gold rush happened in North Carolina, not California.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="593">
		<line-text>To make one pound of honey, a honeybee must tap about two million flowers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="594">
		<line-text>Chicago is named after smelly garlic that once grew in the area.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="595">
		<line-text>The Chicago river flows backwards; the flow reversal project was completed in 1900.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="596">
		<line-text>The patent for the fire hydrant was destroyed in a fire.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="597">
		<line-text>Powerful earthquakes can make the Earth spin faster.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="598">
		<line-text>Baby bunnies are called kittens.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="599">
		<line-text>A group of flamingos is called a flamboyance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="600">
		<line-text>Sea otters hold each other’s paws while sleeping so they don’t drift apart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="601">
		<line-text>Gentoo penguins propose to their life mates with a pebble.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="602">
		<line-text>Male pups will intentionally let female pups “win” when they play-fight so they can get to know them better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="603">
		<line-text>A cat’s nose is ridged with a unique pattern, just like a human fingerprint.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="604">
		<line-text>A group of porcupines is called a prickle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="605">
		<line-text>99% of our solar system's mass is the sun.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="606">
		<line-text>More energy from the sun hits Earth every hour than the planet uses in a year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="607">
		<line-text>If two pieces of the same type of metal touch in outer space, they will bond together permanently.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="608">
		<line-text>Just a sugar cube of neutron star matter would weigh about one hundred million tons on Earth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="609">
		<line-text>A soup can full of neutron star material would have more mass than the Moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="610">
		<line-text>Ancient Chinese warriors would show off to their enemies before battle, by juggling.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="611">
		<line-text>OMG was added to dictionaries in 2011, but its first known use was in 1917.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="612">
		<line-text>In the state of Arizona, it is illegal for donkeys to sleep in bathtubs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="613">
		<line-text>The glue on Israeli postage stamps is certified kosher.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="614">
		<line-text>Rats and mice are ticklish, and even laugh when tickled.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="615">
		<line-text>Norway once knighted a penguin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="616">
		<line-text>The King of Hearts is the only king without a mustache.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="617">
		<line-text>It is illegal to sing off-key in North Carolina.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="618">
		<line-text>Forty is the only number whose letters are in alphabetical order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="619">
		<line-text>One is the only number with letters in reverse alphabetical order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="620">
		<line-text>Strawberries are grown in every state in the U.S. and every province in Canada.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="621">
		<line-text>The phrase, “You’re a real peach” originated from the tradition of giving peaches to loved ones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="622">
		<line-text>At latitude 60° south, it is possible to sail clear around the world without touching land.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="623">
		<line-text>Interstate 90 is the longest U.S. Interstate Highway with over 3,000 miles from Seattle, WA to Boston, MA.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="624">
		<line-text>DFW Airport in Texas is larger than the island of Manhattan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="625">
		<line-text>Benjamin Franklin invented flippers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="626">
		<line-text>Miami installed the first ATM for inline skaters.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="627">
		<line-text>Indonesia is made up of more than 17,000 islands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="628">
		<line-text>Giraffes have the same number of vertebrae as humans: 7.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="629">
		<line-text>The official taxonomic classification for llamas is Llama glama.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="630">
		<line-text>Remove all the space between its atoms and Earth would be the size of a baseball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="631">
		<line-text>The soil on Mars is rust color because it's full of rust.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="632">
		<line-text>Sound travels up to 15 times faster through steel than air, at speeds up to 19,000 feet per second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="633">
		<line-text>Humans share 50% of their DNA with bananas.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="634">
		<line-text>Maine is the closest U.S. state to Africa.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="635">
		<line-text>An octopus has three hearts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="636">
		<line-text>Only 12 U.S. presidents have been elected to office for two terms and served those two terms.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="637">
		<line-text>Franklin D. Roosevelt was elected to office for four terms prior to the 22nd Amendment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="638">
		<line-text>John F. Kennedy, at 43, was the youngest elected president, and Ronald Reagan, at 73, the oldest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="639">
		<line-text>James Buchanan is the only bachelor to be elected president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="640">
		<line-text>Eight presidents have died while in office.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="641">
		<line-text>Bill Clinton was born William Jefferson Blythe III, but took his stepfather’s last name when his mother remarried.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="642">
		<line-text>Prior to the 12th Amendment in 1804, the presidential candidate who received the second highest number of electoral votes was vice president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="643">
		<line-text>George Washington was a successful liquor distributor, making rye whiskey, apple brandy, and peach brandy in his Mount Vernon distillery.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="644">
		<line-text>Thomas Jefferson and John Adams chipped off a piece of Shakespeare's chair as a souvenir when they visited his home in 1786.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="645">
		<line-text>George Washington started losing his permanent teeth in his 20s and had only one natural tooth by the time he was president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="646">
		<line-text>George Washington had false teeth made from many different materials, including an elephant tusk and hippopotamus ivory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="647">
		<line-text>George Washington protected his beloved horses from losing their teeth by making sure they were brushed regularly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="648">
		<line-text>John Quincy Adams regularly skinny-dipped in the Potomac River.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="649">
		<line-text>Calvin Coolidge was so shy, he was nicknamed “Silent Cal.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="650">
		<line-text>Calvin Coolidge loved to wear a cowboy hat and ride his mechanical horse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="651">
		<line-text>President Herbert Hoover invented “Hooverball” (a cross between volleyball and tennis using a medicine ball), which he played with his cabinet members.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="652">
		<line-text>Andrew Jackson was involved in as many as 100 duels, many of which were fought to defend the honor of his wife, Rachel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="653">
		<line-text>Martin Van Buren's nickname was &quot;Old Kinderhook&quot; because he was raised in Kinderhook, N.Y.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="654">
		<line-text>James Buchanan bought slaves in Washington, D.C., and quietly freed them in Pennsylvania.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="655">
		<line-text>Abraham Lincoln was only defeated once in about 300 wrestling matches, making it to the Wrestling Hall of Fame with honors as &quot;Outstanding American.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="656">
		<line-text>In his youth, President Andrew Johnson apprenticed as a tailor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="657">
		<line-text>Ulysses S. Grant smoked at least 20 cigars a day; citizens sent him at least 10,000 boxes in gratitude after winning the Battle of Shiloh.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="658">
		<line-text>Not only was James Garfield ambidextrous, he could write Latin with one hand and Greek with the other at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="659">
		<line-text>Benjamin Harrison was the first president to have electricity in the White House; however, he was so scared of getting electrocuted, he’d never touch the light switches himself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="660">
		<line-text>William McKinley almost always wore a red carnation on his lapel as a good-luck charm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="661">
		<line-text>Herbert Hoover's son had two pet alligators that were occasionally permitted to run loose throughout the White House.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="662">
		<line-text>Jimmy Carter filed a report for a UFO sighting in 1973, calling it “the darndest thing I’ve ever seen.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="663">
		<line-text>Bill Clinton's face is so symmetrical that he ranked in facial symmetry alongside male models.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="664">
		<line-text>In 1916, Jeannette Rankin of Montana became the first woman elected to Congress.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="665">
		<line-text>Gerald Ford was the only president and vice president never to be elected to either office.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="666">
		<line-text>Victoria Woodhull, in 1872, was the first woman to run for the U.S. presidency.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="667">
		<line-text>James Monroe received every electoral vote but one in the 1820 election.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="668">
		<line-text>There are only three requirements to become U.S. president: must be 35, a natural-born U.S. citizen, and have resided in the U.S. for at least 14 years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="669">
		<line-text>To cut groundskeeping costs during World War I, President Woodrow Wilson brought a flock of sheep to trim the White House grounds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="670">
		<line-text>Rutherford B. Hayes was the first president to use a phone, and his phone number was extremely easy to remember – simply “1.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="671">
		<line-text>Martin Van Buren was the first president born a U.S. citizen; all presidents before him were British.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="672">
		<line-text>Andrew Jackson's pet parrot Poll was removed from his funeral for cursing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="673">
		<line-text>There has never been a U.S. president whose name started with the common letter S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="674">
		<line-text>Abraham Lincoln is the only U.S. president who was also a licensed bartender.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="675">
		<line-text>Barack Obama is called the 44th president, but is actually the 43rd because Grover Cleveland is counted twice, as he was elected for two terms.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="676">
		<line-text>Four times in U.S history has a presidential candidate won the popular vote but lost the election.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="677">
		<line-text>President Herbert Hoover and his wife were fluent in Mandarin Chinese and would use it in the White House to speak privately to each other.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="678">
		<line-text>November was chosen to be election month because it fell between harvest and brutal winter weather.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="679">
		<line-text>Six of the last 12 U.S. presidents have been left-handed, far greater than the national average of lefties (10%).</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="680">
		<line-text>William Henry Harrison owned a pet goat while in office.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="681">
		<line-text>John Adams had a horse named Cleopatra.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="682">
		<line-text>James Madison had a pet parrot who outlived him and his wife.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="683">
		<line-text>John Quincy Adams' wife raised silkworms.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="684">
		<line-text>Martin Van Buren was given two tiger cubs while he was president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="685">
		<line-text>William Harrison had a billy goat at the White House.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="686">
		<line-text>Franklin Pierce was gifted two small &quot;sleeve dogs&quot; – he kept one and gave the other to Jefferson Davis.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="687">
		<line-text>Abraham Lincoln's son had a pet turkey, which he gave a pardon so it wasn't killed and eaten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="688">
		<line-text>James Garfield had a dog appropriately named Veto.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="689">
		<line-text>William Taft liked milk so much that he had cows graze on the White House lawn, Pauline being the last in history to graze there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="690">
		<line-text>Calvin Coolidge had a bulldog named Boston Beans, a terrier named Peter Pan, and a pet raccoon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="691">
		<line-text>John Kennedy had a pony named Macaroni.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="692">
		<line-text>Lyndon Johnson had two beagles, named Him and Her, for which he was criticized for picking up by their ears.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="693">
		<line-text>Jimmy Carter had a dog named Grits, a gift given to his daughter Amy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="694">
		<line-text>Bill Clinton had a cat named Socks, which was the first presidential pet to have its own website.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="695">
		<line-text>Woodrow Wilson passed the Georgia Bar Exam despite not finishing law school; he also has a PhD.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="696">
		<line-text>President Zachary Taylor's nickname was &quot;Old Rough and Ready&quot; because of his famed war career.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="697">
		<line-text>Andrew Jackson was once given a 1,400-pound cheese wheel as a gift, which he served at his outgoing President's Reception.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="698">
		<line-text>Blueberry jelly beans were created for Ronald Reagan’s presidential inauguration in 1981.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="699">
		<line-text>Dwight D. Eisenhower was the first Texas-born president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="700">
		<line-text>Lyndon Johnson's family all had the initials LBJ.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="701">
		<line-text>Thomas Jefferson was convinced that if he soaked his feet in a bucket of cold water every day, he’d never get sick.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="702">
		<line-text>Gerald Ford worked as a fashion model during college and actually appeared on the cover of Cosmopolitan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="703">
		<line-text>Dwight Eisenhower was the only president to serve in both World War I and World War II.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="704">
		<line-text>Jimmy Carter was the first president to be born in a hospital.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="705">
		<line-text>Calvin Coolidge liked to have his head rubbed with petroleum jelly while eating breakfast in bed, believing it was good for his health.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="706">
		<line-text>A portion of Grover Cleveland's jaw was artificial, composed of vulcanized rubber.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="707">
		<line-text>Russia and the United States are less than three miles apart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="708">
		<line-text>John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other on the Fourth of July in 1826.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="709">
		<line-text>Abraham Lincoln's dog Fido was the first &quot;First Dog&quot; to be photographed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="710">
		<line-text>President Calvin Coolidge owned two lion cubs: Tax Reduction and Budget Bureau.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="711">
		<line-text>President Rutherford B. Hayes' cat Siam was the first Siamese cat in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="712">
		<line-text>President John Quincy Adams' pet alligator lived in a White House bathroom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="713">
		<line-text>First Lady Abigail Adams famously wrote, &quot;If you love me...you must love my dog.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="714">
		<line-text>John Adams' pets Satan and Juno were the first dogs to live in the White House.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="715">
		<line-text>Calvin Coolidge walked pet raccoon Rebecca on a leash around the White House.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="716">
		<line-text>More presidents have had pet birds than cats.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="717">
		<line-text>Thomas Jefferson's pet mockingbird was trained to eat out of his mouth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="718">
		<line-text>Spotty Bush, an English Springer Spaniel, has been the only presidential pet to live at the White House during two different administrations.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="719">
		<line-text>Andrew Jackson was the first president to ride on a railroad train.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="720">
		<line-text>Pat Nixon was the first First Lady to wear pants in public.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="721">
		<line-text>First Lady Martha Washington was the first American woman to be honored on a U.S. postage stamp.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="722">
		<line-text>When snakes are born with two heads, they fight each other for food.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="723">
		<line-text>Venus is the only planet to rotate clockwise.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="724">
		<line-text>Tennessee ties with Missouri as the most neighborly state, bordered by 8 states.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="725">
		<line-text>The cotton candy machine was invented in 1897, by a dentist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="726">
		<line-text>You can’t hum while plugging your nose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="727">
		<line-text>Elephants are afraid of bees.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="728">
		<line-text>They used to offer goat carriage rides in Central Park.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="729">
		<line-text>Chimps can develop their own fashion trends.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="730">
		<line-text>Monday is the only day of the week with an anagram: dynamo.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="731">
		<line-text>The only Michelangelo painting in the Western Hemisphere is on display in Fort Worth, TX.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="732">
		<line-text>Humans are 1-2 centimeters taller in the morning than at night.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="733">
		<line-text>Baby giraffes fall up to 6 feet to the ground when they are born.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="734">
		<line-text>It takes around 200 muscles to take a step.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="735">
		<line-text>The flamingo can only eat when its head is upside down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="736">
		<line-text>A bald eagle nest can weigh up to two tons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="737">
		<line-text>Worrying squirrels is not tolerated in Missouri.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="738">
		<line-text>Wombat droppings are cube-shaped.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="739">
		<line-text>Adult humans are the only mammal that can't breathe and swallow at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="740">
		<line-text>Hens do not need a rooster to lay an egg.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="741">
		<line-text>There are more nerve connections or &quot;synapses&quot; in your brain than there are stars in our galaxy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="742">
		<line-text>There are more English words beginning with the letter &quot;S&quot; than any other letter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="743">
		<line-text>There are more fake than real flamingos.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="744">
		<line-text>The word “bride” comes from an old Proto-Germanic word meaning “to cook.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="745">
		<line-text>The word utopia – an ideal place – ironically comes from a Greek word meaning “no place.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="746">
		<line-text>Los Angeles was originally founded as El Pueblo de la Reina de Los Angeles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="747">
		<line-text>The woolly mammoth still roamed the earth while the pyramids were being built.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="748">
		<line-text>Nine-banded armadillos almost always give birth to four identical quadruplets.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="749">
		<line-text>Jellyfish don’t have brains.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="750">
		<line-text>Jellyfish can clone themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="751">
		<line-text>The koala is the longest-sleeping animal, sleeping an average of 22 hours per day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="752">
		<line-text>Walruses are true party animals; they can go without sleep for 84 hours.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="753">
		<line-text>The city of Chicago was raised by over a foot during the 1850s and ’60s without disrupting daily life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="754">
		<line-text>Red kangaroos can hop up to 44 mph.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="755">
		<line-text>Arkansas has the only active diamond mine in the United States.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="756">
		<line-text>Robert Heft, who designed the current U.S. flag in a high school project, received a B- because it &quot;lacked originality.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="757">
		<line-text>The first 18-hole golf course in America was built on a sheep farm in 1892.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="758">
		<line-text>Most newborns will lose all the hair they are born with in the first six months of life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="759">
		<line-text>Ripening bananas glow an intense blue under black light.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="760">
		<line-text>Coconut water was used as an IV drip in WWII when saline solution was in short supply.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="761">
		<line-text>Mercury and Venus are the only planets in our solar system with no moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="762">
		<line-text>Peanuts are not actually nuts but legumes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="763">
		<line-text>The Oscar statuette is brittanium plated with 24K gold.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="764">
		<line-text>The only thing that can scratch a diamond is a diamond.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="765">
		<line-text>There is a star that is a diamond of ten billion trillion trillion carats.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="766">
		<line-text>One ounce of gold can be stretched into a thin wire measuring 50 miles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="767">
		<line-text>A $100,000 bill exists, but was only used by Federal Reserve Banks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="768">
		<line-text>10 million bricks were used to build the Empire State Building.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="769">
		<line-text>One quarter of all the body’s bones are in the feet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="770">
		<line-text>Lake Havasu City, AZ, has been recorded as the hottest city in the U.S. with average summer temperatures of 94.6.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="771">
		<line-text>Early sunscreens included ingredients like rice bran oil, iron, clay, and tar.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="772">
		<line-text>One of the first sunscreens was sold in the 1910s under the name Zeozon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="773">
		<line-text>In the U.S., there is an official rock, paper, scissors league.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="774">
		<line-text>The largest bill ever issued by the U.S. was a $100,000 bill in 1934.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="775">
		<line-text>Kickball is referred to as “soccer-baseball” in some parts of Canada.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="776">
		<line-text>Less than 1% of Sweden’s household waste ends up in a dump.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="777">
		<line-text>Duck Duck Goose is called Duck Duck Grey Duck in Minnesota.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="778">
		<line-text>There are more tigers owned by Americans than in the wild worldwide.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="779">
		<line-text>Hawaiian pizza was actually created in Canada.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="780">
		<line-text>A city in Greece struggles to build subway systems because they keep digging up ancient ruins.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="781">
		<line-text>Elvis was a natural blonde.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="782">
		<line-text>On Venus, it snows metal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="783">
		<line-text>Eating 600 bananas is the equivalent of one chest X-ray in terms of radiation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="784">
		<line-text>The potato became the first vegetable to be grown in space.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="785">
		<line-text>The average dog can understand over 150 words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="786">
		<line-text>At one time, serving ice cream on cherry pie in Kansas was prohibited.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="787">
		<line-text>Blueberries are one of the only natural foods that are truly blue in color.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="788">
		<line-text>Blueberries are also called “star berries.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="789">
		<line-text>There are more varieties of blueberries than states in the U.S.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="790">
		<line-text>Typically, blueberries become ripe after 2-5 weeks on a bush.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="791">
		<line-text>Love blueberries. Celebrate them all year round, but especially in July, National Blueberry Month.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="792">
		<line-text>While blueberries grow in clusters on their bush, the individual blueberries ripen at different times.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="793">
		<line-text>The first commercial batch of blueberries came from Whitesbog, New Jersey, in 1916.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="794">
		<line-text>The perfect blueberry should be “dusty” in color.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="795">
		<line-text>Maine produces more wild blueberries than anywhere else in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="796">
		<line-text>75% of the U.S.’s tart cherries come from Michigan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="797">
		<line-text>Traverse, MI, considers itself the Cherry Capital of the World.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="798">
		<line-text>Once cherries have been picked, they don’t ripen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="799">
		<line-text>Make sure to eat a chocolate-covered cherry on January 3; it’s National Chocolate-Covered Cherry Day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="800">
		<line-text>On average, how many cherries are in a pound? 44.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="801">
		<line-text>The word “cherry” comes from the Turkish town of Cerasus.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="802">
		<line-text>A cherry pie is made of about 250 cherries.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="803">
		<line-text>Eau Claire, Michigan, is known as “The Cherry Pit Spitting Capital of the World.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="804">
		<line-text>The National Anthem of Greece has 158 verses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="805">
		<line-text>North Korea and Finland are technically separated by only one country.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="806">
		<line-text>Australia’s first police force was made up of the most well-behaved convicts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="807">
		<line-text>Emergency phone number in Europe is 112.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="808">
		<line-text>Canada's postal code for Santa Claus at the North Pole is H0H 0H0.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="809">
		<line-text>Russia has a larger surface area than Pluto.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="810">
		<line-text>In New Zealand, it is illegal to name your twin babies &quot;Fish&quot; and &quot;Chips.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="811">
		<line-text>Chocolate bars and blue denim both originated in Guatemala.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="812">
		<line-text>In New Zealand, parents have to run baby names by the government for approval.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="813">
		<line-text>When a child loses their tooth in Greece, they throw it on the roof as a good luck wish that their adult teeth will be strong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="814">
		<line-text>Australia is the only nation to govern an entire continent and its outlying islands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="815">
		<line-text>No one in Greece can choose not to vote; voting is required by law for every citizen who is 18 or older.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="816">
		<line-text>Australia has 10,685 beaches; you could visit a new beach every day for more than 29 years.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="817">
		<line-text>China is large enough to cover about five separate time zones, but only has one national time zone since the Chinese Civil War in 1949.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="818">
		<line-text>There is a language in Botswana that consists of mainly five types of clicks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="819">
		<line-text>An African elephant can turn the pages of a book with its trunk.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="820">
		<line-text>Ancient Egyptians slept on head rests made of wood, ivory, or stone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="821">
		<line-text>A traffic jam once lasted for 11 days in Beijing, China.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="822">
		<line-text>Alaska is the only state that can be typed on one row of keys.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="823">
		<line-text>The blue in the Sistine Chapel is made of ground lapis lazuli gems and oils.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="824">
		<line-text>&quot;The Bridge of Eggs&quot; built in Lima, Peru, was made of mortar that was mixed with egg whites.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="825">
		<line-text>In South Korea, you are one year old at birth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="826">
		<line-text>The Great Wall of China is 13,170.7 miles long, over five times the distance from LA to NYC.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="827">
		<line-text>The horizontal line between two numbers in a fraction is called a vinculum.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="828">
		<line-text>The metal ring on the end of a pencil is called a ferrule.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="829">
		<line-text>You cannot taste food until mixed with saliva.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="830">
		<line-text>There is an uninhabited island in the Bahamas known as Pig Beach, which is populated entirely by swimming pigs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="831">
		<line-text>Lake Hillier, in Western Australia, is colored a bright pink.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="832">
		<line-text>Spiked dog collars were invented by the Ancient Greeks, who used them on their sheepdogs to protect their necks from wolves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="833">
		<line-text>&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="834">
		<line-text>On Jupiter and Saturn, it rains diamonds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="835">
		<line-text>Nowhere in the Humpty Dumpty nursery rhyme does it say that Humpty Dumpty is an egg.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="836">
		<line-text>Located on the Detroit River, the J.W. Wescott II is the only floating post office in the U.S. and has its own ZIP Code: 48222.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="837">
		<line-text>Antarctica is the largest desert in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="838">
		<line-text>Tomatoes have more genes than humans.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="839">
		<line-text>In Texas, it is legal to kill Bigfoot if you ever find it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="840">
		<line-text>Elephants can smell water up to 3 miles away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="841">
		<line-text>A snail can grow back a new eye if it loses one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="842">
		<line-text>You can tell a turtle’s gender by the noise it makes. Males grunt and females hiss.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="843">
		<line-text>French poodles actually originated in Germany.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="844">
		<line-text>Marine mammals swim by moving their tails up and down, while fish swim by moving their tails left and right.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="845">
		<line-text>“Knocker uppers” were professionals paid to shoot peas at windows. They were replaced by alarm clocks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="846">
		<line-text>An average cumulus cloud weighs more than 70 adult T. rexes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="847">
		<line-text>Clicking your computer mouse 1,400 times burns one calorie.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="848">
		<line-text>&quot;Guy&quot; was once an insult for anyone dressed in poor clothes, originating from the burning of effigies of the infamous British rebel, Guy Fawkes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="849">
		<line-text>The national animal of Scotland is the unicorn.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="850">
		<line-text>The tea bag was created by accident in 1908 by Thomas Sullivan of New York.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="851">
		<line-text>The male ostrich can roar just like a lion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="852">
		<line-text>A group of frogs is called an army.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="853">
		<line-text>Corn always has an even number of rows on each ear.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="854">
		<line-text>You are always looking at your nose; your brain just chooses to ignore it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="855">
		<line-text>There is a single mega-colony of ants that spans three continents, covering much of Europe, the west coast of the U.S., and the west coast of Japan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="856">
		<line-text>The world's largest mountain range is under the sea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="857">
		<line-text>The Anglo-Zanzibar war of 1896 is the shortest war on record, lasting an exhausting 38 minutes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="858">
		<line-text>Below the Kalahari Desert lies the world's largest underground lake.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="859">
		<line-text>Oregon and Mexico once shared a border.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="860">
		<line-text>Bluetooth technology was named after a 10th century Scandinavian king.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="861">
		<line-text>A nun held one of the first PhDs in computer science.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="862">
		<line-text>For 67 years, Nintendo only produced playing cards.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="863">
		<line-text>The ancient Chinese carried Pekingese puppies in the sleeves of their robes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="864">
		<line-text>A tarantula can survive for more than two years without food.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="865">
		<line-text>Ethiopia follows a calendar that is seven years behind the rest of the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="866">
		<line-text>In Denmark, citizens have to select baby names from a list of 7,000 government-approved names.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="867">
		<line-text>Every tweet Americans send is archived by the Library of Congress.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="868">
		<line-text>A neuron star is as dense as stuffing 50 million elephants into a thimble.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="869">
		<line-text>More energy from the sun hits Earth every hour than the planet uses in a year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="870">
		<line-text>An earthquake in 1812 caused the Mississippi River to flow backward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="871">
		<line-text>In 2014, the Department of Veterans Affairs was still paying a Civil War pension.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="872">
		<line-text>In Webster's Dictionary, the longest words without repeating letters are “uncopyrightable” and “dermatoglyphics.”</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="873">
		<line-text>“Unprosperousness” is the longest word in which no letter occurs only once.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="874">
		<line-text>“Typewriter” and “perpetuity” are the longest words that can be typed on a single line of a QWERTY keyboard.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="875">
		<line-text>There have been three Olympic games held in countries that no longer exist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="876">
		<line-text>Golf is the only sport to be played on the moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="877">
		<line-text>The word &quot;checkmate&quot; comes from the Persian phrase meaning &quot;the king is dead.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="878">
		<line-text>The brain is the only organ in the human body without pain receptors.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="879">
		<line-text>There is a volcano on Mars the size of Arizona.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="880">
		<line-text>The blue whale can produce the loudest sound of any animal. At 188 decibels, the noise can be detected over 800 kilometers away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="881">
		<line-text>Dogs’ sense of hearing is more than ten times more acute than a human’s.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="882">
		<line-text>A housefly hums in the key of F.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="883">
		<line-text>Venus is the only planet in the solar system where the sun rises in the west.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="884">
		<line-text>The state animal of Tennessee is a raccoon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="885">
		<line-text>If you were to stretch out a Slinky until it’s flat, it would measure 87 feet long.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="886">
		<line-text>It's illegal in many countries to perform surgery on an octopus without anesthesia because of its intelligence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="887">
		<line-text>There are more trees on Earth than stars in the galaxy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="888">
		<line-text>Human thigh bones are stronger than concrete.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="889">
		<line-text>Fires spread faster uphill than downhill.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="890">
		<line-text>The Florida Everglades is the only place in the world where both alligators and crocodiles live together.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="891">
		<line-text>Newborns can't cry actual tears. This normally occurs between 3 weeks and 3 months of life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="892">
		<line-text>If you could drive your car upward, you would be in space in less than an hour.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="893">
		<line-text>The sun is actually white, but the Earth’s atmosphere makes it appear yellow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="894">
		<line-text>The Earth rotates at a speed of 1,040 MPH.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="895">
		<line-text>Even when a snake has its eyes closed, it can still see through its eyelids.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="896">
		<line-text>The word &quot;aegilops&quot; is the longest word in the English language to have all of its letters in alphabetical order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="897">
		<line-text>Gorillas burp when they are happy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="898">
		<line-text>Because of metal prices, since 2006 the U.S. Mint has had to spend more to make a penny than they are worth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="899">
		<line-text>&quot;Never odd or even&quot; spelled backward is still &quot;Never odd or even.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="900">
		<line-text>In Alabama, it's illegal to carry an ice cream cone in your back pocket at any time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="901">
		<line-text>Alaska is the most northern, western, and eastern U.S. state.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="902">
		<line-text>In France, it's illegal for employers to send emails after work hours.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="903">
		<line-text>A group of raccoons is called a gaze.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="904">
		<line-text>Pteronophobia is the fear of being tickled by feathers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="905">
		<line-text>Cherophobia is the fear of happiness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="906">
		<line-text>The vertical distance between the Earth's highest and lowest points is about 12 miles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="907">
		<line-text>A flock of crows is known as a murder.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="908">
		<line-text>Dr. Seuss wrote &quot;Green Eggs and Ham&quot; to win a bet with his publisher who thought he could not complete a book with only 50 words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="909">
		<line-text>Over 80% of the land in Nevada is owned by the U.S. government.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="910">
		<line-text>There are more people on Facebook today than there were on the Earth 200 years ago.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="911">
		<line-text>Mangoes have noses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="912">
		<line-text>Mangoes can get sunburned.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="913">
		<line-text>Before 1859, baseball umpires sat behind home plate in rocking chairs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="914">
		<line-text>The shortest professional baseball player was 3 feet, 7 inches tall.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="915">
		<line-text>The average life span of an MLB baseball is five to seven pitches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="916">
		<line-text>The most valuable baseball card ever is worth about $2.8 million.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="917">
		<line-text>The paisley pattern is based on the mango.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="918">
		<line-text>In India, mango leaves are used to celebrate the birth of a boy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="919">
		<line-text>A flipped coin is more likely to land on the side it started on.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="920">
		<line-text>When sprinting, professional cyclists produce enough power to power a home.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="921">
		<line-text>Mosquitoes prefer to bite people with Type O blood.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="922">
		<line-text>During a typical MLB season, approximately 160,000 baseballs are used.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="923">
		<line-text>The Bible is the world's most shoplifted book.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="924">
		<line-text>The British pound is the world's oldest currency still in use.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="925">
		<line-text>The Great Lakes have more than 30,000 islands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="926">
		<line-text>Mountain lions can whistle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="927">
		<line-text>While rabbits have near-perfect 360-degree panoramic vision, their most critical blind spot is directly in front of their nose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="928">
		<line-text>When a koala is born, it is about the size of a jelly bean.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="929">
		<line-text>Toe wrestling is a competitive sport.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="930">
		<line-text>There have been 85 recorded instances of a pitcher striking out four batters in one inning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="931">
		<line-text>3.7 million bags of ballpark peanuts are eaten every year at ballparks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="932">
		<line-text>Shakespeare created the name Jessica for his play &quot;The Merchant of Venice.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="933">
		<line-text>Tooth enamel is the hardest substance in the human body.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="934">
		<line-text>The mummy of Pharaoh Ramesses II has a passport.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="935">
		<line-text>It is physically impossible for a pig to look at the sky.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="936">
		<line-text>There are more stars in the universe than grains of sand on earth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="937">
		<line-text>A caterpillar has more muscles than a human.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="938">
		<line-text>A shrimp's heart is in its head.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="939">
		<line-text>A human being could swim through the blood vessels of a blue whale.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="940">
		<line-text>Light could travel around the earth nearly 7.5 times in one second.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="941">
		<line-text>A single lightning bolt contains enough energy to cook 100,000 pieces of toast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="942">
		<line-text>About one in every 2,000 babies is born with teeth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="943">
		<line-text>Water can boil and freeze at the same time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="944">
		<line-text>Less than 5% of the population needs just 4-5 hours of sleep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="945">
		<line-text>Peanut butter can be converted into diamonds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="946">
		<line-text>Astronauts can't burp in space.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="947">
		<line-text>An Immaculate Inning is when a pitcher strikes out three batters with only nine pitches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="948">
		<line-text>Earth is the only planet not named after a Greek or Roman god.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="949">
		<line-text>Yawns are contagious to dogs as well as humans.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="950">
		<line-text>In the 1960s, the U.S. government tried to turn a cat into a spy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="951">
		<line-text>Movie trailers used to come on at the end of movies, but no one stuck around to watch them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="952">
		<line-text>MLB umpires often wear black underwear, in case they split their pants.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="953">
		<line-text>It is possible to record four outs in one-half inning of baseball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="954">
		<line-text>There are nine different ways to reach first base.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="955">
		<line-text>During World War II, the U.S. military designed a grenade to be the size and weight of a baseball, since &quot;any young American man should be able to properly throw it.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="956">
		<line-text>Philadelphia zookeeper Jim Murray sent baseball scores to telegraph offices by carrier pigeon every half inning in 1883.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="957">
		<line-text>From 1845 through 1867, home base was circular, made of iron, painted or enameled white, and 12 inches in diameter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="958">
		<line-text>President Bill Clinton's first presidential pitch (on April 4, 1993) was the first ever from the pitcher's mound to the catcher's mitt.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="959">
		<line-text>Thunder is actually the sound caused by lightning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="960">
		<line-text>Australia is wider than the moon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="961">
		<line-text>85% of people only breathe out of one nostril at a time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="962">
		<line-text>An albatross can sleep while it flies.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="963">
		<line-text>In a room of 23 people, there is a 50% chance that two people have the same birthday.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="964">
		<line-text>Bubble wrap was originally invented as a wallpaper in 1957.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="965">
		<line-text>There is a species of jellyfish that is immortal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="966">
		<line-text>Of the 193 members of the United Nations, Britain has invaded 171 of them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="967">
		<line-text>The Apollo 11 guidance computer was no more powerful than today's pocket calculator.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="968">
		<line-text>“Sphenopalatine ganglioneuralgia” is the technical name for brain freeze.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="969">
		<line-text>Earth is actually located inside the sun's atmosphere.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="970">
		<line-text>The spiral shapes of sunflowers follow the Fibonacci sequence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="971">
		<line-text>If you drilled a hole through the earth, it would take 42 minutes to fall through it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="972">
		<line-text>The planet 55 Cancri e is made of diamonds and would be worth $26.9 nonillion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="973">
		<line-text>France used the guillotine as recently as 1977.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="974">
		<line-text>Sloths move so slow that algae can grow on them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="975">
		<line-text>Zero is the only number that cannot be represented by Roman numerals.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="976">
		<line-text>Michelangelo hated painting and wrote a poem about it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="977">
		<line-text>The dwarf lantern shark grows to be no bigger than a human hand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="978">
		<line-text>&quot;Tools of ignorance&quot; is a nickname for the equipment worn by catchers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="979">
		<line-text>More than 100 baseballs are used during a typical MLB game.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="980">
		<line-text>Pitchers were prohibited from delivering the ball overhand for much of the 19th century.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="981">
		<line-text>Walks were scored as hits during the 1887 season.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="982">
		<line-text>A regulation baseball has 108 stitches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="983">
		<line-text>A &quot;can of corn&quot; is a routine fly ball hit to an outfielder.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="984">
		<line-text>Baseball is played in more than 100 countries.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="985">
		<line-text>“Take Me Out to the Ballgame” was written in 1908 by Jack Norworth and Albert Von Tilzer, both of whom had never been to a baseball game.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="986">
		<line-text>A baseball pitcher’s curveball can break up to 17 inches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="987">
		<line-text>MLB baseballs are rubbed in Lena Blackburne Baseball Rubbing Mud, a unique mud found only near Palmyra, New Jersey.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="988">
		<line-text>The Metropolitan Museum of Art has over 30,000 baseball cards as part of the Jefferson R. Burdick collection.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="989">
		<line-text>William Howard Taft, the 27th president of the U.S., began the tradition of throwing out the ceremonial first pitch in 1910.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="990">
		<line-text>MLB National League (1876) is the oldest professional sports league that is still in existence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="991">
		<line-text>The first modern-day World Series game was played in 1903.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="992">
		<line-text>The Mendoza Line is a .200 batting average.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="993">
		<line-text>There are 13 different pitches a pitcher can throw in baseball.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="994">
		<line-text>The first MLB All-Star Game was played in 1933.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="995">
		<line-text>A player was once ejected from an MLB game for sleeping during the game.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="996">
		<line-text>Baseball hits that bounced over the fence were considered home runs until the 1930s.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="997">
		<line-text>The most home runs ever recorded in an MLB season is 73.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="998">
		<line-text>The highest batting average ever recorded in an MLB season is .440.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="999">
		<line-text>MLB has not had a lefty play catcher since 1989.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1000">
		<line-text>The longest MLB game went 26 innings.</line-text>
	</line>
</lines>
