<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<lines>
	<line id="1">
		<line-text>Too many of us look upon Americans as dollar chasers. This is a cruel libel, even if it is reiterated thoughtlessly by the Americans themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="2">
		<line-text>Now I know what a statesman is; he's a dead politician. We need more statesmen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="3">
		<line-text>Imitation is the sincerest form of television.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="4">
		<line-text>Consistency requires you to be as ignorant today as you were a year ago.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="5">
		<line-text>Destiny is no matter of chance. It is a matter of choice. It is not a thing to be waited for, it is a thing to be achieved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="6">
		<line-text>Though it sounds absurd, it is true to say I felt younger at sixty than I felt at twenty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="7">
		<line-text>Difficulties strengthen the mind, as labor does the body.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="8">
		<line-text>Doubt is not a pleasant condition, but certainty is absurd.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="9">
		<line-text>If you tell the truth you don't have to remember anything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="10">
		<line-text>The past is not dead. In fact, it's not even past.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="11">
		<line-text>The greater the ignorance the greater the dogmatism.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="12">
		<line-text>Keep your fears to yourself, but share your courage with others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="13">
		<line-text>Doubt whom you will, but never yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="14">
		<line-text>Play: Work that you enjoy doing for nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="15">
		<line-text>In recent years, we've become enamored with our own past success. Lulled into complacency by the glitter of our own achievements. We've become accustomed to the title of Military Superpower, forgetting the qualities that got us there. We've become accustomed to our economic dominance in the world, forgetting that it wasn't reckless deals and get rich quick schemes that got us where we are, but hard work and smart ideas, quality products and wise investments.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="16">
		<line-text>Some things you do because you want to. Some things you do because of the needs of others in your family.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="17">
		<line-text>None of us will ever accomplish anything excellent or commanding except when he listens to this whisper which is heard by him alone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="18">
		<line-text>There's an old saying that if you come back to the place where you became a man, you will remember all those things you need to be happy... That saying never made sense to me, but I thought it was worth a try.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="19">
		<line-text>They can conquer who believe they can.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="20">
		<line-text>I thought about how wonderfully strange it would be to live in a place where almost everything had been built by the dead.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="21">
		<line-text>There I lay staring upward, while the stars wheeled over... Faint to my ears came the gathered rumour of all lands: the springing and the dying, the song and the weeping, and the slow everlasting groan of overburdened stone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="22">
		<line-text>Yes, there is a Nirvanah; it is leading your sheep to a green pasture, and in putting your child to sleep, and in writing the last line of your poem.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="23">
		<line-text>The average American can get into the kingdom of heaven much more easily than he can get into the Boulevard St. Germain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="24">
		<line-text>There is only one thing that a philosopher can be relied on to do, and that is, to contradict other philosophers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="25">
		<line-text>A prayer in its simplest definition is merely a wish turned Godward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="26">
		<line-text>When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="27">
		<line-text>As a well-spent day brings happy sleep, so life well used brings happy death.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="28">
		<line-text>Common-sense appears to be only another name for the thoughtlessness of the unthinking. It is made of the prejudices of childhood, the idiosyncrasies of individual character and the opinion of the newspapers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="29">
		<line-text>Just goes to show you. You can kill a guy, fold him up, stuff him in your trunk, and still you don't *really* know him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="30">
		<line-text>If not actually disgruntled, he was far from being gruntled.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="31">
		<line-text>Better late than never.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="32">
		<line-text>Strike the tent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="33">
		<line-text>But my dear man, reality is only a Rorschach ink-blot, you know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="34">
		<line-text>Immature poets imitate; mature poets steal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="35">
		<line-text>He who loves the world as his body may be entrusted with the empire.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="36">
		<line-text>A man is like a fraction whose numerator is what he is and whose denominator is what he thinks of himself. The larger the denominator the smaller the fraction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="37">
		<line-text>He who is afraid to ask is ashamed of learning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="38">
		<line-text>In Mexico we have a word for sushi: Bait.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="39">
		<line-text>Bring down my gray hairs with sorrow to the grave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="40">
		<line-text>A woman impudent and mannish grown is not more loathed than an effeminate man in time of action.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="41">
		<line-text>Before my term has ended, we shall have to test anew whether a nation organized and governed such as ours can endure. The outcome is by no means certain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="42">
		<line-text>In order to fully realize how bad a popular play can be, it is necessary to see it twice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="43">
		<line-text>No snowflake in an avalanche ever feels responsible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="44">
		<line-text>...and in the long run, disease is more humane than war or starvation. My, isn't that gloomy?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="45">
		<line-text>Reports that say that something hasn't happened are always interesting to me, because as we know, there are known knowns; there are things we know we know. We also know there are known unknowns; that is to say we know there are some things we do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns - - the ones we don't know we don't know. And if one looks throughout the history of our country and other free countries, it is the latter category that tend to be the difficult ones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="46">
		<line-text>He who fears being conquered is sure of defeat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="47">
		<line-text>The most gifted members of the human species are at their creative best when they cannot have their way, and must compensate for what they miss by realizing and cultivating their capacities and talents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="48">
		<line-text>Joy is not in things; it is in us.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="49">
		<line-text>Against my soul's pure truth why labour you to make it wander in an unknown field?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="50">
		<line-text>People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing—that's why we recommend it daily.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="51">
		<line-text>Passion is the quickest to develop, and the quickest to fade. Intimacy develops more slowly, and commitment more gradually still.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="52">
		<line-text>A witty saying proves nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="53">
		<line-text>While the fates permit, live happily; life speeds on with hurried step, and with winged days the wheel of the headlong year is turned.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="54">
		<line-text>Jealousy would be far less torturous if we understood that love is a passion entirely unrelated to our merits.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="55">
		<line-text>Sex: the thing that takes up the least amount of time and causes the most amount of trouble.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="56">
		<line-text>We are not in a position in which we have nothing to work with. We already have capacities, talents, direction, missions, callings.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="57">
		<line-text>Education is for improving the lives of others and for leaving your community and world better than you found it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="58">
		<line-text>To keep the heart unwrinkled, to be hopeful, kindly, cheerful, reverent - that is to triumph over old age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="59">
		<line-text>Traditionalists often study what is taught, not what there is to create.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="60">
		<line-text>I don't have hobbies; hobbies cost money. Interests are quite free.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="61">
		<line-text>It is not the critic who counts, not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood, who strives valiantly, who errs and comes up short again and again. Because there is no effort without error and shortcomings, he who knows the great devotion, who spends himself in a worthy cause, who at the best knows in the end the high achievement of triumph and who at worst, if he fails while daring greatly, knows his place shall never be with those timid and cold souls who know neither victory nor defeat&quot;.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="62">
		<line-text>The demonstration that no possible combination of known substances, known forms of machinery and known forms of force, can be united in a practical machine by which man shall fly long distances through the air, seems to the writer as complete as it is possible for the demonstration of any physical fact to be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="63">
		<line-text>CALLOUS, adj. Gifted with great fortitude to bear the evils afflicting another.
When Zeno was told that one of his enemies was no more he was observed to be deeply moved. &quot;What!&quot; said one of his disciples, &quot;you weep at the death of an enemy?&quot; &quot;Ah, 'tis true,&quot; replied the great Stoic; &quot;but you should see me smile at the death of a friend.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="64">
		<line-text>They say you just stand over there, he'll say thank you and you walk back off and that's what I thought was gonna happen, but in my head, I had for five or six years known that he was gonna call me over.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="65">
		<line-text>Do not accustom yourself to use big words for little matters.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="66">
		<line-text>There's such a difference between saying a thing yourself and hearing other people say it. You may know a thing is so, but you can't help hoping other people don't quite think it is.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="67">
		<line-text>I know God will not give me anything I can't handle. I just wish that He didn't trust me so much.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="68">
		<line-text>You've got be careful about getting locked into open systems.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="69">
		<line-text>Here is the world, sound as a nut, perfect, not the smallest piece of chaos left, never a stitch nor an end, not a mark of haste, or botching, or second thought; but the theory of the world is a thing of shreds and patches.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="70">
		<line-text>I cannot pretend to feel impartial about colours. I rejoice with the brilliant ones and am genuinely sorry for the poor browns.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="71">
		<line-text>It's easy to quit drinking. I 've done it a thousand times.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="72">
		<line-text>Why do we have to wait for special moments to say nice things or tell people we care about them?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="73">
		<line-text>Take rest; a field that has rested gives a bountiful crop.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="74">
		<line-text>Discretion is the better part of valor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="75">
		<line-text>And remember, no matter where you go, there you are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="76">
		<line-text>If I have ever made any valuable discoveries, it has been owing more to patient attention, than to any other talent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="77">
		<line-text>I don't know a better preparation for life than a love of poetry and a good digestion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="78">
		<line-text>My thoughts are my company; I can bring them together, select them, detain them, dismiss them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="79">
		<line-text>In soft regions are born soft men.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="80">
		<line-text>Refuse to be ill. Never tell people you are ill; never own it to yourself. Illness is one of those things which a man should resist on principle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="81">
		<line-text>Give what you have. To some it may be better than you dare think.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="82">
		<line-text>We are here to change the world with small acts of thoughtfulness done daily rather than with one great breakthrough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="83">
		<line-text>A life of pleasure makes even the strongest mind frivolous at last.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="84">
		<line-text>Life is too short for traffic.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="85">
		<line-text>You can protect your liberties in this world only by protecting the other man's freedom. You can be free only if I am free.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="86">
		<line-text>Quit worrying about your health. It'll go away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="87">
		<line-text>Political power grows out of the barrel of a gun.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="88">
		<line-text>The human race has one really effective weapon, and that is laughter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="89">
		<line-text>Philosophy is a game with objectives and no rules. Mathematics is a game with rules and no objectives.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="90">
		<line-text>A man who carries a cat by the tail learns something he can learn in no other way.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="91">
		<line-text>It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="92">
		<line-text>The harder the conflict, the more glorious the triumph. What we obtain too cheap, we esteem too lightly; it is dearness only that gives everything its value. I love the man that can smile in trouble, that can gather strength from distress and grow brave by reflection. 'Tis the business of little minds to shrink; but he whose heart is firm, and whose conscience approves his conduct, will pursue his principles unto death.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="93">
		<line-text>I am not afraid... I was born to do this.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="94">
		<line-text>Half of the American people have never read a newspaper. Half never voted for President. One hopes it is the same half.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="95">
		<line-text>Better no law than laws not enforced.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="96">
		<line-text>There are three rules for writing the novel. Unfortunately, no one knows what they are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="97">
		<line-text>Facts are stupid things.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="98">
		<line-text>All the knowledge in the world is found within you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="99">
		<line-text>Who you are isn't tied solely to what you say, even though it may feel that way to you now.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="100">
		<line-text>The important thing is not to stop questioning. Curiosity has its own reason for existing. One cannot help but be in awe when he contemplates the mysteries of eternity, of life, of the marvelous structure of reality. It is enough if one tries merely to comprehend a little of this mystery every day. Never lose a holy curiosity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="101">
		<line-text>Where love and wisdom drink out of the same cup, in this everyday world, it is the exception.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="102">
		<line-text>The humble suffer when the mighty disagree.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="103">
		<line-text>I make a fortune from criticizing the policy of the government, and then hand it over to the government in taxes to keep it going.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="104">
		<line-text>If there are no stupid questions, then what kind of questions do stupid people ask? Do they get smart just in time to ask questions?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="105">
		<line-text>Two roads diverged in a wood, and I -- I took the one less traveled by, and that has made all the difference.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="106">
		<line-text>Every pursuit is great when greatly pursued.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="107">
		<line-text>The first rule of life is to reveal nothing, to be exceptionally cautious in what you say, in whatever company you may find yourself. If you have a secret, you have only to whisper it to your dearest friend with the strictest injunction that it will go no further, and within half a day the story is all over town, and when you do make what would seem to be a perfectly sensible remark, you will find it reported in the most grotesque form, thus incurring no end of criticism to rebound upon you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="108">
		<line-text>In America, through pressure of conformity, there is freedom of choice, but nothing to choose from.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="109">
		<line-text>I know not, sir whether Bacon wrote the works of Shakespeare, but if he did not it seems to me that he missed the opportunity of his life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="110">
		<line-text>There is nothing that is personal and private, it is all universal. All that stuff we share but don't admit to, and don't talk about...what is that about?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="111">
		<line-text>Talent, lying in the understanding, is often inherited; genius, being the action of reason or imagination, rarely or never.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="112">
		<line-text>No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="113">
		<line-text>Deep doubts, deep wisdom; small doubts, little wisdom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="114">
		<line-text>A nation is a society united by delusions about its ancestry and by a common hatred of its neighbors.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="115">
		<line-text>This is something that I do consider to be good advice: I took my first paycheck and I put it in the goddamn bank. Then I took my second paycheck and put it in the goddamn bank. I had seen the roller coaster of my father's career - top of the world, then unemployed - and I never wanted to take a job because I needed money.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="116">
		<line-text>Everyone complains of his lack of memory, but nobody of his want of judgment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="117">
		<line-text>Better than a thousand hollow words, is one word that brings peace.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="118">
		<line-text>There are no such things as applied sciences, only applications of science.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="119">
		<line-text>The quickest way to a man's heart really is through his stomach, because then you don't have to chop through that pesky rib cage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="120">
		<line-text>I shall give life here my best, and I believe it will give its best to me in return.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="121">
		<line-text>Never regret something that once made you smile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="122">
		<line-text>To make no mistakes is not in the power of man; but from their errors and mistakes the wise and good learn wisdom for the future.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="123">
		<line-text>Read over your compositions, and wherever you meet with a passage which you think is particularly fine, strike it out.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="124">
		<line-text>Imagine a world without Darwin. Imagine a world in which Charles Darwin and Alfred Russel Wallace had not transformed our understanding of living things. What... would become baffling and puzzling..., in urgent need of explanation? The answer is: practically everything about living things....</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="125">
		<line-text>Failures are very public, and successes are short lived. It's the pleasure of drawing funny pictures that makes up for it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="126">
		<line-text>Common sense is instinct. Enough of it is genius.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="127">
		<line-text>We who are of mature age seldom suspect how unmercifully and yet with what insight the very young judge us.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="128">
		<line-text>It is a far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="129">
		<line-text>A long life may not be good enough, but a good life is long enough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="130">
		<line-text>She was a phantom of delight
When first she gleam'd upon my sight;
A lovely apparition, sent
To be a moment's ornament.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="131">
		<line-text>The only truly secure system is one that is powered off, cast in a block of concrete and sealed in a lead-lined room with armed guards -- and even then I have my doubts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="132">
		<line-text>Life engenders life. Energy creates energy. It is by spending oneself that one becomes rich.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="133">
		<line-text>INCOMPOSSIBLE, adj. Unable to exist if something else exists. Two things are incompossible when the world of being has scope enough for one of them, but not enough for both -- as Walt Whitman's poetry and God's mercy to man. Incompossibility, it will be seen, is only incompatibility let loose. Instead of such low language as &quot;Go heel yourself -- I mean to kill you on sight,&quot; the words, &quot;Sir, we are incompossible,&quot; would convey and equally significant intimation and in stately courtesy are altogether superior.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="134">
		<line-text>How comes it, that thou art then estranged from thyself?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="135">
		<line-text>The human mind is not capable of grasping the Universe. We are like a little child entering a huge library. The walls are covered to the ceilings with books in many different tongues. The child knows that someone must have written these books. It does not know who or how. It does not understand the languages in which they are written. But the child notes a definite plan in the arrangement of the books - a mysterious order which it does not comprehend, but only dimly suspects.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="136">
		<line-text>On action alone be thy interest,
Never on its fruits.
Let not the fruits of action be thy motive,
Nor be thy attachment to inaction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="137">
		<line-text>When a man's knowledge is sufficient to attain, and his virtue is not sufficient to enable him to hold, whatever he may have gained, he will lose again.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="138">
		<line-text>Nothing can so alienate a voter from the political system as backing a winning candidate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="139">
		<line-text>Tranquillity hides in small spaces, and when found needs to be treasured, because you know it's a phantom that will slip away again.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="140">
		<line-text>Golf is a good walk spoiled.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="141">
		<line-text>Freedom is one of the deepest and noblest aspirations of the human spirit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="142">
		<line-text>Few things in life are more embarrassing than the necessity of having to inform an old friend that you have just got engaged to his fiancee.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="143">
		<line-text>The business of America is not business. Neither is it war. The business of America is justice and securing the blessings of liberty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="144">
		<line-text>The novel we sit down to write, and the one we end up writing may be very different, just as the Jesus we grasp and the Jesus who grasps us may also differ.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="145">
		<line-text>BONDSMAN, n. A fool who, having property of his own, undertakes to become responsible for that entrusted to another to a third. Philippe of Orleans wishing to appoint one of his favorites, a dissolute nobleman, to a high office, asked him what security he would be able to give. &quot;I need no bondsmen,&quot; he replied, &quot;for I can give you my word of honor.&quot; &quot;And pray what may be the value of that?&quot; inquired the amused Regent. &quot;Monsieur, it is worth its weight in gold.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="146">
		<line-text>RITUALISM, n. A Dutch Garden of God where He may walk in rectilinear freedom, keeping off the grass.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="147">
		<line-text>God does not care about our mathematical difficulties. He integrates empirically.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="148">
		<line-text>Act as if were impossible to fail.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="149">
		<line-text>Big nations are like chickens. They like to make big noises, but very often it is no more than squabbling.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="150">
		<line-text>Whatever does not destroy me makes me stronger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="151">
		<line-text>He who seldom speaks, and with one calm well-timed word can strike dumb the loquacious, is a genius or a hero.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="152">
		<line-text>To flatter and follow others, without being flattered and followed in turn, is but a state of half enjoyment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="153">
		<line-text>The only reward for love is the experience of loving.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="154">
		<line-text>It is a sad fact that 50 percent of marriages in this country end in divorce. But hey, the other half end in death. You could be one of the lucky ones!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="155">
		<line-text>Mr. Gates is up to his eyeballs in his knowledge of this stuff.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="156">
		<line-text>Three passions, simple but overwhelmingly strong, have governed my life: the longing for love, the search for knowledge, and unbearable pity for the suffering of mankind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="157">
		<line-text>So act that your principle of action might safely be made a law for the whole world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="158">
		<line-text>Man is a clever animal who behaves like an imbecile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="159">
		<line-text>Religion is about turning untested belief into unshakeable truth through the power of institutions and the passage of time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="160">
		<line-text>I married a German. Every night I dress up as Poland and he invades me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="161">
		<line-text>You can take from every experience what it has to offer you. And you cannot be defeated if you just keep taking one breath followed by another.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="162">
		<line-text>I bet the human brain is a kludge.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="163">
		<line-text>The basic fact about human existence is not that it is a tragedy, but that it is a bore.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="164">
		<line-text>It was never what I wanted to buy that held my heart's hope. It was what I wanted to be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="165">
		<line-text>Dignity does not consist in possessing honors, but in deserving them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="166">
		<line-text>The word 'meaningful' when used today is nearly always meaningless.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="167">
		<line-text>Only when one has lost all curiosity about the future has one reached the age to write an autobiography.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="168">
		<line-text>An ignorant person is one who doesn't know what you have just found out.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="169">
		<line-text>Guilt resembles a sword with two edges. On the one hand, it cuts for Justice, imposing practical morality upon those who fear it. But there is another side to that weighted emotion. Conscience does not always adhere to rational judgment. Guilt is always a self-imposed burden, but it is not always rightly imposed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="170">
		<line-text>Attempt easy tasks as if they were difficult, and difficult as if they were easy; in the one case that confidence may not fall asleep, in the other that it may not be dismayed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="171">
		<line-text>Waste not fresh tears over old griefs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="172">
		<line-text>The opposite of war isn't peace, it's creation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="173">
		<line-text>Communication is something so simple and difficult that we can never put it in simple words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="174">
		<line-text>There is no passion like that of a functionary for his function.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="175">
		<line-text>Books are the carriers of civilization. Without books, history is silent, literature dumb, science crippled, thought and speculation at a standstill. I think that there is nothing, not even crime, more opposed to poetry, to philosophy, ay, to life itself than this incessant business.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="176">
		<line-text>Simple pleasures are the last refuge of the complex.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="177">
		<line-text>I don't worry about getting old. I'm old already. Only young people worry about getting old. When I was 65 I had cupid's eczema. I don't believe in dying. It's been done. I'm working on a new exit. Besides, I can't die now - I'm booked.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="178">
		<line-text>He that will not sail until all dangers are over, will never put to sea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="179">
		<line-text>Whenever you looked forward to anything pleasant you were sure to be more or less disappointed . . . perhaps that is true. But there is a good side to it too. The bad things don't always come up to your expectations either . . . they nearly always turn out ever so much better than you think.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="180">
		<line-text>Deep is a wounded heart, and strong
A voice that cries against a mighty wrong;
And full of death as a hot wind's blight,
Doth the ire of a crushed affection light.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="181">
		<line-text>You have to accept the plan and realize that if you slip, and you might, you can’t use that as a reason to give up or stop.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="182">
		<line-text>Live life to the fullest tomorrow may never be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="183">
		<line-text>In the world there are only two tragedies. One is not getting what one wants, and the other is getting it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="184">
		<line-text>My sense of God is my sense of wonder about the Universe.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="185">
		<line-text>Earthly minds, like mud walls, resist the strongest batteries; and though, perhaps, somethimes the force of a clear argument may make some impression, yet they nevertheless stand firm, keep out the enemy, truth, that would captivate or disturbe them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="186">
		<line-text>Always read stuff that will make you look good if you die in the middle of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="187">
		<line-text>An expert knows all the answers - if you ask the right questions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="188">
		<line-text>Hell, there are no rules here--we're trying to accomplish something.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="189">
		<line-text>A pessimist sees only the dark side of the clouds, and mopes; a philosopher sees both sides, and shrugs; an optimist doesn't see the clouds at all - he's walking on them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="190">
		<line-text>It is a mistake to suppose that God is only, or even chiefly, concerned with religion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="191">
		<line-text>It's amazing what you can accomplish if you do not care who gets the credit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="192">
		<line-text>Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="193">
		<line-text>GENTEEL, adj. Refined, after the fashion of a gent.

Observe with care, my son, the distinction I reveal:
A gentleman is gentle and a gent genteel.
Heed not the definitions your &quot;Unabridged&quot; presents,
For dictionary makers are generally gents.
G.J.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="194">
		<line-text>I could dance with you until the cows come home. On second thought I'd rather dance with the cows until you come home.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="195">
		<line-text>As you express joy, you draw it out of those you meet, creating joyful people and joyful events. The greater the joy you express,the more joy you experience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="196">
		<line-text>The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts, therefore guard accordingly; and take care that you entertain no notions unsuitable to virtue, and reasonable nature.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="197">
		<line-text>We certainly do not forget you as soon as you forget us. It is, perhaps, our fate rather than our merit. We cannot help ourselves. We live at home, quiet, confined, and our feelings prey upon us. You are forced on exertion. You have always a profession, pursuits, business of some sort or other, to take you back into the world immediately, and continual occupation and change soon weaken impressions. All the privilege I claim for my own sex (it is not a very enviable one; you need not covet it), is that of loving longest, when existence or when hope is gone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="198">
		<line-text>When they call the roll in the Senate, the Senators do not know whether to answer 'Present' or 'Not guilty.'</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="199">
		<line-text>There is a coherent plan in the universe, though I don't know what it's a plan for.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="200">
		<line-text>And thus I clothe my naked villainy
With old odd ends, stol'n forth of holy writ;
And seem a saint, when most I play the devil.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="201">
		<line-text>The great thing in this world is not so much where you stand, as in what direction you are moving.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="202">
		<line-text>The worst thing one can do is not to try, to be aware of what one wants and not give in to it, to spend years in silent hurt wondering if something could have materialized - never knowing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="203">
		<line-text>When you go into court you are putting your fate into the hands of twelve people who weren't smart enough to get out of jury duty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="204">
		<line-text>Everyone has certain fears, certain things that one cannot abide.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="205">
		<line-text>I think that novels that leave out technology misrepresent life as badly as Victorians misrepresented life by leaving out sex.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="206">
		<line-text>All the world's a cage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="207">
		<line-text>Each body has its art...</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="208">
		<line-text>A good relationship is like fireworks: loud, explosive, and liable to maim you if you hold on too long.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="209">
		<line-text>The capacity of human beings to bore one another seems to be vastly greater than that of any other animals.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="210">
		<line-text>Whenever a separation is made between liberty and justice, neither, in my opinion, is safe.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="211">
		<line-text>Spare no expense to save money on this one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="212">
		<line-text>I have nothing to say, and I am saying it, and that is poetry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="213">
		<line-text>There ought to be one day-- just one-- when there is open season on senators.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="214">
		<line-text>Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="215">
		<line-text>I count religion but a childish toy,
And hold there is no sin but ignorance.
Birds of the air will tell of murders past.
I am asham'd to hear such fooleries!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="216">
		<line-text>Never underestimate your own ignorance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="217">
		<line-text>The avarice of the old: it's absurd to increase one's luggage as one nears the journey's end.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="218">
		<line-text>If you ask me what I came into this world to do, I will tell you: I came to live out loud.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="219">
		<line-text>However far the stream flows, it never forgets its source.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="220">
		<line-text>Dieu me pardonnera. C'est son metier.
(God will forgive me. It's his job.)</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="221">
		<line-text>Unquestionably, there is progress. The average American now pays out twice as much in taxes as he formerly got in wages.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="222">
		<line-text>A word to the wise is infuriating.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="223">
		<line-text>Is life worth living? Yes, so long
As there is wrong to right.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="224">
		<line-text>Where you tend a rose, my lad, a thistle may not grow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="225">
		<line-text>You might as well fall flat on your face as lean over too far backward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="226">
		<line-text>We hang the petty thieves and appoint the great ones to public office.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="227">
		<line-text>I hate ingratitude more in a man
than lying, vainness, babbling, drunkenness,
or any taint of vice whose strong corruption
inhabits our frail blood.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="228">
		<line-text>We will discover the nature of our particular genius when we stop trying to conform to our own or to other peoples' models, learn to be ourselves, and allow our natural channel to open.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="229">
		<line-text>Assumptions are the termites of relationships.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="230">
		<line-text>INSCRIPTION, n. Something written on another thing. Inscriptions are of many kinds, but mostly memorial, intended to commemorate the fame of some illustrious person and hand down to distant ages the record of his services and virtues. To this class of inscriptions belongs the name of John Smith, penciled on the Washington monument. Following are examples of memorial inscriptions on tombstones: (See EPITAPH.)

&quot;In the sky my soul is found,
And my body in the ground.
By and by my body'll rise
To my spirit in the skies,
Soaring up to Heaven's gate.
1878.&quot;

&quot;Sacred to the memory of Jeremiah Tree. Cut down May 9th, 1862,
aged 27 yrs. 4 mos. and 12 ds. Indigenous.&quot;

&quot;Affliction sore long time she boar,
Phisicians was in vain,
Till Deth released the dear deceased
And left her a remain.
Gone to join Ananias in the regions of bliss.&quot;

&quot;The clay that rests beneath this stone
As Silas Wood was widely known.
Now, lying here, I ask what good
It was to let me be S. Wood.
O Man, let not ambition trouble you,
Is the advice of Silas W.&quot;

&quot;Richard Haymon, of Heaven. Fell to Earth Jan. 20, 1807, and ha
d the dust brushed off him Oct. 3, 1874.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="231">
		<line-text>They have, and bring with them, that upper-body strength. They have apparently developed that in their childhood and growing up, and they've further advanced in that regard.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="232">
		<line-text>Fear not those who argue but those who dodge.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="233">
		<line-text>If you take a dog which is starving and feed him and make him prosperous, that dog will not bite you. This is the primary difference between a dog and a man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="234">
		<line-text>What the superior man seeks is in himself; what the small man seeks is in others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="235">
		<line-text>I love you. I used to pity your sorrow. But now, were you sorrowless, without fear or any lack, still i would love you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="236">
		<line-text>Washington DC is the only place in America where people put bumper stickers on their cars the day *after* the election.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="237">
		<line-text>The genius of the United States is not best or most in its executives or legislatures, nor in its ambassadors or authors or colleges, or churches, or parlors, nor even in its newspapers or inventors, but always most in the common people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="238">
		<line-text>What if everything is an illusion and nothing exists? In that case, I definitely overpaid for my carpet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="239">
		<line-text>Only the mediocre are always at their best.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="240">
		<line-text>Good taste is always an asset.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="241">
		<line-text>California is a great place to live if you're an orange.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="242">
		<line-text>In a way, staring into a computer screen is like staring into an eclipse. It's brilliant and you don't realize the damage until its too late.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="243">
		<line-text>When words leave off, music begins.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="244">
		<line-text>You know I say just what I think, and nothing more and less. I cannot say one thing and mean another.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="245">
		<line-text>I dreamed a thousand new paths. . . I woke and walked my old one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="246">
		<line-text>The clearest way into the Universe is through a forest wilderness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="247">
		<line-text>There is nothing so annoying as to have two people talking when you're busy interrupting.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="248">
		<line-text>The beginning of compunction is the beginning of a new life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="249">
		<line-text>We must expect finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="250">
		<line-text>Politics is perhaps the only profession for which no preparation is thought necessary.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="251">
		<line-text>Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="252">
		<line-text>MIRACLE, n. An act or event out of the order of nature and unaccountable, as beating a normal hand of four kings and an ace with four aces and a king.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="253">
		<line-text>Truth is a pathless land.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="254">
		<line-text>The world is a great book; he who never stirs from home reads only a page.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="255">
		<line-text>Animals do not admire each other. A horse does not admire its companion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="256">
		<line-text>Reporter: A writer who guesses his way to the truth and dispels it with a tempest of words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="257">
		<line-text>The century which we are entering can be and must be the century of the common man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="258">
		<line-text>I have seen flowers come in stony places
And kind things done by men with ugly faces
And the gold cup won by the worst horse at the races,
So I trust too.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="259">
		<line-text>If a word in the dictionary were mispelled, how would we know?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="260">
		<line-text>There is nothing useless in nature; not even uselessness itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="261">
		<line-text>One thing I've learned in all these years is not to make love when you really don't feel it; there's probably nothing worse you can do to yourself than that.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="262">
		<line-text>The moment of victory is much too short to live for that and nothing else.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="263">
		<line-text>For the great mass of mankind, the only saving grace needed is a steady fidelity to what is nearest to hand and heart for the short moment of each human effort.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="264">
		<line-text>Think twice before you speak, and then you may be able to say something more insulting than if you spoke right out at once.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="265">
		<line-text>Before every action ask yourself. Will this bring more monkeys on my back. Will the result of my action be a blessing or a heavy burden?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="266">
		<line-text>I dream of wayward gulls and all landless lovers, rare moments of winter sun, peace, privacy, for everyone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="267">
		<line-text>Do not expect to arrive at certainty in every subject which you pursue. There are a hundred things wherein we mortals. . . must be content with probability, where our best light and reasoning will reach no farther.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="268">
		<line-text>Consult your friend on all things, especially on those which respect yourself. His counsel may then be useful where your own self-love might impair your judgment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="269">
		<line-text>An aged man is but a paltry thing, a tattered coat upon a stick.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="270">
		<line-text>...in the lexicon of the political class, the word &quot;sacrifice&quot; means that the citizens are supposed to mail even more of their income to Washington so that the political class will not have to sacrifice the pleasure of spending it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="271">
		<line-text>There are many people who reach their conclusions about life like schoolboys: they cheat their master by copying the answer out of a book without having worked the sum out for themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="272">
		<line-text>Knowledge can be communicated, but wisdom cannot. A man can find it, he can live it, he can be filled and sustained by it, but he cannot utter or teach it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="273">
		<line-text>Man is distinguished from all other creatures by the faculty of laughter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="274">
		<line-text>If you hate a person, you hate something in him that is a part of yourself. What isn't part of ourselves doesn't disturb us.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="275">
		<line-text>Ideas are far more powerful than guns. We don't allow our enemies to have guns, why should we allow them to have ideas?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="276">
		<line-text>Our deeds are like children that are born to us;they live and act apart from our own will.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="277">
		<line-text>The Americans combine the notions of Christianity and of liberty so intimately in their minds, that it is impossible to make them conceive the one without the other.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="278">
		<line-text>Facing it, always facing it, that's the way to get through. Face it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="279">
		<line-text>Theology is the effort to explain the unknowable in terms of the not worth knowing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="280">
		<line-text>An intellectual is a man who takes more words than necessary to tell more than he knows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="281">
		<line-text>The most efficient labor-saving device is still money.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="282">
		<line-text>Only those who have learned the power of sincere and selfless contribution experience life's deepest joy: true fulfillment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="283">
		<line-text>The most gifted members of the human species are at their creative best when they cannot have their way, and must compensate for what they miss by realizing and cultivating their capacities and talents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="284">
		<line-text>Freedom means the opportunity to be what we never thought we would be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="285">
		<line-text>Truth is generally the best vindication against slander.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="286">
		<line-text>Proverbs are all very fine when there's nothing to worry you, but when you're in real trouble, they're not a bit of help.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="287">
		<line-text>If you keep your mind sufficiently open, people will throw a lot of rubbish into it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="288">
		<line-text>When a woman behaves like a man, why can't she behave like a nice man?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="289">
		<line-text>There is nothing wrong with sobriety in moderation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="290">
		<line-text>Fair is foul, and foul is fair.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="291">
		<line-text>Middle age is when your broad mind and narrow waist begin to change places.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="292">
		<line-text>You might as well fall flat on your face as lean over too far backward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="293">
		<line-text>You can pretend to be serious; you can't pretend to be witty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="294">
		<line-text>Some people spend an entire lifetime wondering if they made a difference. The Marines don't have that problem.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="295">
		<line-text>Better be despised for too anxious apprehensions, than ruined by too confident security.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="296">
		<line-text>Honesty is probably the sexiest thing a man can give to a woman.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="297">
		<line-text>All speech is vain and empty unless it be accompanied by action.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="298">
		<line-text>All men have an equal right to the free development of their faculties; they have an equal right to the impartial protection of the state; but it is not true, it is against all the laws of reason and equity, it is against the eternal nature of things, that the indolent man and the laborious man, the spendthrift and the economist, the imprudent and the wise, should obtain and enjoy an equal amount of goods.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="299">
		<line-text>A man can only do what he can do. But if he does that each day he can sleep at night and do it again the next day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="300">
		<line-text>I have never seen a situation so dismal that a policeman couldn't make it worse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="301">
		<line-text>It's not what you want in this life, it's what you get that you have to do with.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="302">
		<line-text>The best and most beautiful things cannot be seen or even heard, they must be felt with the heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="303">
		<line-text>The ignorance of one voter in a democracy impairs the security of all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="304">
		<line-text>Actors search for rejection. If they don't get it they reject themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="305">
		<line-text>The highest reward for a man's toil is not what he gets for it, but what he becomes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="306">
		<line-text>Life is islands of ecstasy in an ocean of ennui, and after the age of thirty land is seldom seen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="307">
		<line-text>Such praise coming from so degraded a source, was degrading to me, its recipient.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="308">
		<line-text>Quotation ... A writer expresses himself in words that have been used before because they give his meaning better than he can give it himself, or because they are beautiful or witty, or because he expects them to touch a cord of association in his reader, or because he wishes to show that he is learned and well read. Quotations due to the last motive are invariably ill-advised; the discerning reader detects it and is contemptuous; the undiscerning is perhaps impressed, but even then is at the same time repelled, pretentious quotations being the surest road to tedium.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="309">
		<line-text>Die? I should say not, dear fellow. No Barrymore would allow such a conventional thing to happen to him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="310">
		<line-text>The best portions of a good man's life, his little, nameless acts of kindness and love.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="311">
		<line-text>You and I have a rendezvous with destiny. We will preserve for our children this, the last best hope of man on earth, or we will sentence them to take the first step into a thousand years of darkness. If we fail, at least let our children and our children's children say of us we justified our brief moment here. We did all that could be done.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="312">
		<line-text>If we believe we have no control, we acquiesce our real power, become subject to the decisions of others, and become like a leaf floating helplessly down a current of other people's decisions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="313">
		<line-text>I have taken all knowledge to be my province.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="314">
		<line-text>I am a design chauvinist. I believe that good design is magical and not to be lightly tinkered with. The difference between a great design and a lousy one is in the meshing of the thousand details that either fit or don't, and the spirit of the passionate intellect that has tied them together, or tried. That's why programming-- or buying software-- on the basis of &quot;lists of features&quot; is a doomed and misguided effort. The features can be thrown together, as in a garbage can, or carefully laid together and interwoven in elegant unification, as in APL, or the Forth language, or the game of chess.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="315">
		<line-text>Life is something to do when you can't get to sleep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="316">
		<line-text>If it is once again one against forty-eight, then I am very sorry for the forty-eight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="317">
		<line-text>Truth is what stands the test of experience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="318">
		<line-text>To design is to communicate clearly by whatever means you can control or master.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="319">
		<line-text>Content thyself to be obscurely good. When vice prevails, and impious men bear sway, the post of honor is a private station.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="320">
		<line-text>My best friend is the one who brings out the best in me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="321">
		<line-text>You may be disappointed if you fail, but you are doomed if you don't try.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="322">
		<line-text>APPETITE, n. An instinct thoughtfully implanted by Providence as a solution to the labor question.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="323">
		<line-text>The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="324">
		<line-text>Famous actress bragging about her husband: Look at him, isn't he beautiful I have kept him for seven years now&quot;
Dorothy Parker: Don't Worry--he'll come back in style&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="325">
		<line-text>Time can burn. Time can hurt. But it can also purify. It can chase away shadows. It can melt the coldest heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="326">
		<line-text>There are times of pure joy when you wish all human life well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="327">
		<line-text>Swear not by the moon, th' inconstant moon, that monthly changes in her circled orb, lest that thy love prove likewise variable.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="328">
		<line-text>Happiness is different from pleasure. Happiness has something to do with struggling and enduring and accomplishing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="329">
		<line-text>Nature is not affected by finance. If someone offered you ten thousand dollars to let them touch your eyeball without blinking, you would never collect the money. At the very last moment, Nature would force you to blink your eye. Nature will protect her own.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="330">
		<line-text>The failure of the mind in old age is often less the results of natural decay, than of disuse. Ambition has ceased to operate; contentment bring indolence, and indolence decay of mental power, ennui, and sometimes death. Men have been known to die, literally speaking, of disease induced by intellectual vacancy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="331">
		<line-text>For one human being to love another; that is perhaps the most difficult of all our tasks, the ultimate, the last test and proof, the work for which all other work is but preparation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="332">
		<line-text>People only see what they are prepared to see.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="333">
		<line-text>It's not that pink is intrinsically bad, but it is such a tiny slice of the rainbow, and, though it may celebrate girlhood in one way, it also repeatedly and firmly fuses girl's identity to appearance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="334">
		<line-text>I have come to value liberated minds as the supreme good of life on earth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="335">
		<line-text>Tact is the art of making a point without making an enemy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="336">
		<line-text>Gossip is when you hear something you like about someone you don't.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="337">
		<line-text>To believe with certainty we must begin by doubting.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="338">
		<line-text>Whoso would be a man must be a nonconformist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="339">
		<line-text>I believe that a scientist looking at nonscientific problems is just as dumb as the next guy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="340">
		<line-text>Be alert to give service. What counts a great deal in life is what we do for others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="341">
		<line-text>Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="342">
		<line-text>Providence protects children and idiots. I know because I have tested it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="343">
		<line-text>Skepticism, like chastity, should not be relinquished too readily.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="344">
		<line-text>Revolution is no dinner party, unless your dinner party is full of blood and iron.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="345">
		<line-text>In the late 19th century Evanston, Illinois, nicknamed &quot;Heavenston&quot; by Frances Willard, was a Methodist-minded town, so pious that the town fathers, resenting the dissipating influence of the soda fountain, passed an ordinance forbidding the sale of ice cream sodas on Sunday. Some ingenious confectioners, obeying the law, served ice cream with syrup but no soda. This sodaless soda was the Sunday soda, and became so popular that orders for &quot;Sundays&quot; crossed the counter everyday of the week. When objection was raised to christening the dish after the Sabbath, the spelling was changed to Sundae, and so developed one of America's most characteristic dishes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="346">
		<line-text>Let every nation know, whether it wishes us well or ill, we shall pay any price, bear any burden, meet any hardship, support any friend, oppose any foe, to assure the survival and success of liberty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="347">
		<line-text>We lift ourselves by our thought, we climb upon our vision of ourselves. If you want to enlarge your life, you must first enlarge your thought of it and of yourself. Hold the ideal of yourself as you long to be, always, everywhere - your ideal of what you long to attain - the ideal of health, efficiency, success.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="348">
		<line-text>The first duty of a man is the seeking after and the investigation of truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="349">
		<line-text>The cynics are right nine times out of ten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="350">
		<line-text>My loathings are simple: stupidity, oppression, crime, cruelty, soft music.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="351">
		<line-text>The greatest penalty of evildoing - namely, to grow into the likeness of bad men.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="352">
		<line-text>I do not know which makes a man more conservative—to know nothing but the present, or nothing but the past.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="353">
		<line-text>It is better to looked over than overlooked.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="354">
		<line-text>There is death in the pot.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="355">
		<line-text>For what do we live, but to make sport for our neighbors and laugh at them in our turn?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="356">
		<line-text>I am not sincere, even when I say I am not.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="357">
		<line-text>Hail to you gods, on that day of the great reckoning. Behold me, I have come to you, without sin, without guilt, without evil, without a witness against me, without one whom I have wronged. I am one pure of mouth, pure of hands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="358">
		<line-text>Americans have different ways of saying things. They say `elevator', we say `lift'...they say `President', we say `stupid psychopathic git'....</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="359">
		<line-text>To fear the foe, since fear oppresseth strength, gives in your weakness strength unto your foe.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="360">
		<line-text>Maude - &quot;The earth is my body, my head is in the stars...Who said that?&quot; Harold- &quot;I don't know.&quot; Maude - &quot;Well, I suppose I did.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="361">
		<line-text>The experience of this sweet life.
L'esperienza de questa dolce vita.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="362">
		<line-text>Deeds, not stones, are the true monuments of the great.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="363">
		<line-text>It is wonderful to be here in the great state of Chicago.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="364">
		<line-text>Action indeed is the sole medium of expression for ethics.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="365">
		<line-text>When the going gets weird, the weird turn pro.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="366">
		<line-text>It is always right that a man should be able to render a reason for the faith that is within him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="367">
		<line-text>I was too green to know that all cynicism masks a failure to cope -- an impotence, in short; and that to despise all effort is the greatest effort of all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="368">
		<line-text>True interactivity is not about clicking on icons or downloading files, it's about encouraging communication.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="369">
		<line-text>When you reach for the stars, you may not quite get them, but you won't come up with a handful of mud either.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="370">
		<line-text>TENACITY, n. A certain quality of the human hand in its relation to the coin of the realm. It attains its highest development in the hand of authority and is considered a serviceable equipment for a career in politics. The following illustrative lines were written of a Californian gentleman in high political preferment, who has passed to his accounting:

Of such tenacity his grip
That nothing from his hand can slip.
Well-buttered eels you may o'erwhelm
In tubs of liquid slippery-elm
In vain -- from his detaining pinch
They cannot struggle half an inch!
'Tis lucky that he so is planned
That breath he draws not with his hand,
For if he did, so great his greed
He'd draw his last with eager speed.
Nay, that were well, you say. Not so
He'd draw but never let it go!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="371">
		<line-text>Nothing in education is so astonishing as the amount of ignorance as it accumulates in the form of inert facts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="372">
		<line-text>I could never think well of a man's intellectual or moral character, if he was habitually unfaithful to his appointments.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="373">
		<line-text>Hope is like a piece of string when you're drowning; it just isn't enough to get you out by itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="374">
		<line-text>Childhood has no forebodings, but then, it is soothed by no memories of outlived sorrow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="375">
		<line-text>AIR, n. A nutritious substance supplied by a bountiful Providence for the fattening of the poor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="376">
		<line-text>Talk of nothing but business, and dispatch that business quickly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="377">
		<line-text>I guess we'd be living in a boring, perfect world if everybody wished everybody else well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="378">
		<line-text>If it doesn't have Siamese twins in a jar, it is not a fair.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="379">
		<line-text>Make yourself an honest man, and then you may be sure that there is one rascal less in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="380">
		<line-text>The higher a man gets, the smaller he seems to those who cannot fly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="381">
		<line-text>Lots of people lose themselves in love, it's no shame, they write songs about it. The hitch is you can't stay lost, sooner or later you have to get back to yourself. If you can't then love becomes your master and you're just it's dog.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="382">
		<line-text>We have the right to lie, but not about the heart of the matter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="383">
		<line-text>This is why God invented network television.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="384">
		<line-text>The English instinctively admire any man who has no talent and is modest about it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="385">
		<line-text>Traditionally, most of Australia's imports come from overseas.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="386">
		<line-text>A man that hoards up riches and enjoys them not, is like an ass that carries gold and eats thistles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="387">
		<line-text>It is not possible to conceive gods inhabiting a land which is made hideous by the smoke and din of mill chimneys and factories and whose roadways are traversed by rushing engines dragging numerous cars crowded with men mostly who know not what they are after.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="388">
		<line-text>You can lead a whore to culture, but you can't make her think.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="389">
		<line-text>The good befriend themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="390">
		<line-text>The more alternatives, the more difficult the choice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="391">
		<line-text>Time is nature's way of keeping everything from happening at once.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="392">
		<line-text>Of all the self-fulfilling prophecies in our culture, the assumption that aging means decline and poor health is probably the deadliest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="393">
		<line-text>The holy passion of Friendship is of so sweet and steady and loyal and enduring a nature that it will last through a whole lifetime, if not asked to lend money.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="394">
		<line-text>Reason has always existed, but not always in a reasonable form.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="395">
		<line-text>OTHERWISE, adv. No better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="396">
		<line-text>Integrity without knowledge is weak and useless, and knowledge without integrity is dangerous and dreadful.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="397">
		<line-text>The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched. They must be felt.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="398">
		<line-text>The only real failure in life is the failure to try.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="399">
		<line-text>I tore myself away from the safe comfort of certainties through my love for the truth; and truth rewarded me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="400">
		<line-text>The best government rests on the people, and not on the few, on persons and not on property, on the free development of public opinion and not on authority.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="401">
		<line-text>If we choose only to expose ourselves to opinions and viewpoints that are in line to our own, we become more polarized, more set in our own ways. It will only reinforce and deepen the political divides in our country. But if we choose to actively seek out information that challenges our assumptions and beliefs, perhaps we can begin to understand where the people who disagree with us are coming from.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="402">
		<line-text>A child is the root of the heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="403">
		<line-text>Happiness is always a by-product. It is probably a matter of temperament, and for anything I know it may be glandular. But it is not something that can be demanded from life, and if you are not happy you had better stop worrying about it and see what treasures you can pluck from your own brand of unhappiness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="404">
		<line-text>It is true greatness to have in one the frailty of a man and the security of a god.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="405">
		<line-text>Conversation is an exercise of the mind; gossip is merely an exercise of the tongue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="406">
		<line-text>When of a gossiping circle it was asked, &quot;What are they doing?&quot; The answer was, &quot;Swapping lies.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="407">
		<line-text>In the future everyone will be famous for fifteen minutes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="408">
		<line-text>The creator of the universe works in mysterious ways. But he uses a base ten counting system and likes round numbers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="409">
		<line-text>Peace is the happy, natural state of man; war corruption, his disgrace.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="410">
		<line-text>September tries its best to have us forget summer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="411">
		<line-text>Our test of truth is a reference to either a present or imagined future majority in favour of our view.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="412">
		<line-text>The secret of staying young is to live honestly, eat slowly, and lie about your age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="413">
		<line-text>Try to say the very thing you really mean, the whole of it, nothing more or less or other than what you really mean. That is the whole are and joy of words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="414">
		<line-text>In all affairs it's a healthy thing now and then to hang a question mark on the things you have long taken for granted.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="415">
		<line-text>It is within the families themselves where peace can begin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="416">
		<line-text>Failure is unimportant. It takes courage to make a fool of yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="417">
		<line-text>Play is an essential function of the passage from immaturity to emotional maturity. Any individual without the opportunities for adequate play in early life will go on seeking them in the stuff of adult life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="418">
		<line-text>Of all the properties which belong to honorable men, not one is so highly prized as that of character.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="419">
		<line-text>ACADEMY, n. [from ACADEME] A modern school where football is taught.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="420">
		<line-text>Consider the postage stamp: its usefulness consists in the ability to stick to one thing till it gets there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="421">
		<line-text>Where desire writhed there stands a stone; the change was sudden and complete.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="422">
		<line-text>I require three things in a man. He must be handsome, ruthless and stupid.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="423">
		<line-text>First of all, let me assert my firm belief that the only thing we have to fear is fear itself - nameless, unreasoning, unjustified terror which paralyzes needed efforts to convert retreat into advance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="424">
		<line-text>I can't bring myself to say, 'Well, I guess I'll be toddling along.' It isn't that I can't toddle. It's just that I can't guess I'll toddle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="425">
		<line-text>A book of quotations . . . can never be complete.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="426">
		<line-text>He who limps still walks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="427">
		<line-text>Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="428">
		<line-text>Life being what it is, one dreams of revenge.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="429">
		<line-text>But all endings are also beginnings. We just don't know it at the time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="430">
		<line-text>Above all things, reverence yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="431">
		<line-text>We don't care. We don't have to. We're the phone company.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="432">
		<line-text>No hatred is so bitter as that of near relations.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="433">
		<line-text>Any ordinary favor we do for someone or any compassionate reaching out may seem to be going nowhere at first, but may be planting a seed we can't see right now. Sometimes we need to just do the best we can and then trust in an unfolding we can't design or ordain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="434">
		<line-text>We have placed too much hope in political and social reforms, only to find out that we were being deprived of our most precious possession: our spiritual life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="435">
		<line-text>Oh, my friend, it's not what they take away from you that counts. Its's what you do with what you have left.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="436">
		<line-text>The Lord gave, and the Lord hath taken away; blessed be the name of the Lord.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="437">
		<line-text>Nothing deters a good man from doing what is honourable.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="438">
		<line-text>A human being should be able to change a diaper, plan an invasion, butcher a hog, conn a ship, design a building, write a sonnet, balance accounts, build a wall, set a bone, comfort the dying, take orders, give orders, cooperate, act alone, solve equations, analyze a new problem, pitch manure, program a computer, cook a tasty meal, fight efficiently, die gallantly. Specialization is for insects.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="439">
		<line-text>Many of life's failures are those who didn't know how close they were to success when they gave up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="440">
		<line-text>We're neither pure; nor wise; nor good; we do the best we know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="441">
		<line-text>1492. As children we were taught to memorize this year with pride and joy as the year people began living full and imaginative lives on the continent of North America. Actually, people had been living full and imaginative lives on the continent of North America for hundreds of years before that. 1492 was simply the year sea pirates began to rob, cheat, and kill them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="442">
		<line-text>I believe we are on an irreversible trend toward more freedom and democracy - but that could change.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="443">
		<line-text>Whenever two people meet, there are really six people present. There is each man as he sees himself, each man as the other person sees him, and each man as he really is.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="444">
		<line-text>I never seek to defeat the man I am fighting, I seek to defeat his confidence. A mind troubled by doubt cannot focus on the course to victory. Two men are equals - true equals - only when they both have equal confidence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="445">
		<line-text>Nothing is more difficult, and therefore more precious, than to be able to decide.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="446">
		<line-text>For though I do not ask for aid, we need it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="447">
		<line-text>I believe I have no prejudices whatsoever. All I need to know is that a man is a member of the human race. That's bad enough for me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="448">
		<line-text>He who despises himself, respects himself as one who despises.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="449">
		<line-text>Behold, the nations are as a drop of a bucket, and are counted as the small dust of the balance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="450">
		<line-text>The greatest pleasure in life is doing what people say you cannot do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="451">
		<line-text>The IQ and the life expectancy of the average American recently passed each other going in opposite directions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="452">
		<line-text>I shall curse you with book and bell and candle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="453">
		<line-text>To die for an idea is to place a pretty high price upon conjectures.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="454">
		<line-text>It is more tolerable to be refused than deceived.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="455">
		<line-text>O, she is rich in beauty, only poor that, when she dies, with beauty dies her store.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="456">
		<line-text>If you stop to be kind, you must swerve often from your path.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="457">
		<line-text>Civilization is a movement and not a condition, a voyage and not a harbor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="458">
		<line-text>When faced with sexism or ageism or lookism or even really aggressive Buddhism, ask yourself the following question:&quot;Is this person in between me and what do I want to do?&quot; If the answer is no, ignore it and move on. Your energy is better used doing your work and outpacing people that way. Then, when you're in charge, don't hire the people who were jerky to you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="459">
		<line-text>A book tightly shut is but a block of paper.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="460">
		<line-text>When I'm inspired, I get excited because I can't wait to see what I'll come up with next.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="461">
		<line-text>An act against my will is not my act.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="462">
		<line-text>A man should not leave this earth with unfinished business. He should live each day as if it was a pre-flight check. He should ask each morning, am I prepared to lift-off?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="463">
		<line-text>The hour of departure has arrived, and we go our ways - I to die, and you to live. Which is better God only knows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="464">
		<line-text>An appeaser is one who feeds a crocodile, hoping it will eat him last.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="465">
		<line-text>I do not mind lying, but I hate inaccuracy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="466">
		<line-text>Read much, but not many books.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="467">
		<line-text>There are some things you can't share without ending up liking each other.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="468">
		<line-text>A lot of people run a race to see who is fastest. I run to see who has the most guts, who can punish himself into exhausting pace, and then at the end, punish himself even more. Nobody is going to win a 5,000 meter race after running an easy 2 miles. Not with me. If I lose forcing the pace all the way, well, at least I can live with myself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="469">
		<line-text>Often and often afterwards, the beloved Aunt would ask me why I had never told anyone how I was being treated. Children tell little more than animals, for what comes to them they accept as eternally established.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="470">
		<line-text>All treaties between great states cease to be binding when they come in conflict with the struggle of existence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="471">
		<line-text>Fortune can, for her pleasure, fools advance,
And toss them on the wheels of Chance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="472">
		<line-text>If lawyers are disbarred and clergymen defrocked, doesn't it follow that electricians can be delighted, musicians denoted?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="473">
		<line-text>First, I do not sit down at my desk to put into verse something that is already clear in my mind. If it were clear in my mind, I should have no incentive or need to write about it. We do not write in order to be understood; we write in order to understand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="474">
		<line-text>One cannot fix one's eyes on the commonest natural production without finding food for a rambling fancy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="475">
		<line-text>It is time I stepped aside for a less experienced and less able man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="476">
		<line-text>The undertaking of a new action brings new strength.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="477">
		<line-text>After a certain high level of technical skill is achieved, science and art tend to coalesce in esthetics, plasticity, and form. The greatest sceintists are always artists as well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="478">
		<line-text>All the king's horses and all the king's men can't put the past together again. So let's remember: Don't try to saw sawdust.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="479">
		<line-text>Fight for your opinions, but do not believe that they contain the whole truth, or the only truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="480">
		<line-text>Wit is so shining a quality that everybody admires it; most people aim at it, all people fear it, and few love it unless in themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="481">
		<line-text>When we see men of worth, we should think of equaling them; when we see men of a contrary character, we should turn inwards and examine ourselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="482">
		<line-text>I don't exercise. If God had wanted me to bend over, he would have put diamonds on the floor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="483">
		<line-text>To govern is always to choose among disadvantages.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="484">
		<line-text>A verbal contract isn't worth the paper it's written on.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="485">
		<line-text>People who like quotations love meaningless generalizations.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="486">
		<line-text>Having a family is like having a bowling alley installed in your brain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="487">
		<line-text>The history of liberty is the history of resistance. The history of liberty is a history of the limitation of governmental power, not the increase of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="488">
		<line-text>I love stuff as much as the next guy, but I’ve come to understand that, regardless of the cost of acquiring it, the price of having it is freedom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="489">
		<line-text>Death is not extinguishing the light; it is putting out the lamp because dawn has come.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="490">
		<line-text>People who like this sort of thing will find this the sort of thing they like.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="491">
		<line-text>LORE, n. Learning -- particularly that sort which is not derived from a regular course of instruction but comes of the reading of occult books, or by nature. This latter is commonly designated as folk-lore and embraces popularly myths and superstitions. In Baring-Gould's _Curious Myths of the Middle Ages_ the reader will find many of these traced backward, through various people son converging lines, toward a common origin in remote antiquity. Among these are the fables of &quot;Teddy the Giant Killer,&quot; &quot;The Sleeping John Sharp Williams,&quot; &quot;Little Red Riding Hood and the Sugar Trust,&quot; &quot;Beauty and the Brisbane,&quot; &quot;The Seven Aldermen of Ephesus,&quot; &quot;Rip Van Fairbanks,&quot; and so forth. The fable with Goethe so affectingly relates under the title of &quot;The Erl- King&quot; was known two thousand years ago in Greece as &quot;The Demos and the Infant Industry.&quot; One of the most general and ancient of these myths is that Arabian tale of &quot;Ali Baba and the Forty Rockefellers.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="492">
		<line-text>Any man with a moderate income can afford to buy more books than he can read in a lifetime.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="493">
		<line-text>I have never found, in a long experience of politics, that criticism is ever inhibited by ignorance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="494">
		<line-text>The basic fact about human existence is not that it is a tragedy, but that it is a bore.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="495">
		<line-text>In university they don't tell you that the greater part of the law is learning to tolerate fools.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="496">
		<line-text>The drug that heals our sorrows forgetfulness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="497">
		<line-text>I have with me two gods, Persuasion and Compulsion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="498">
		<line-text>Your life can't go according to plan if you have no plan.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="499">
		<line-text>This is the day that the Lord hath made; let us rejoice and be glad in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="500">
		<line-text>Innovation is the specific instrument of entrepreneurship... the act that endows resources with a new capacity to create wealth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="501">
		<line-text>Whatsoever a man soweth, that shall he also reap.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="502">
		<line-text>Write 100 things that you love about your partner. It’s another way of keeping yourself in check. It’s hard to do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="503">
		<line-text>This England never did, nor never shall,
Lie at the proud foot of a conqueror.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="504">
		<line-text>It is better, I think, to grab at the stars than to sit flustered because you know you cannot reach them... At least he who reaches will get a good stretch, a good view, and perhaps even a low-hanging apple for his efforts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="505">
		<line-text>I could have gone on flying through space forever.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="506">
		<line-text>Men for the sake of getting a living forget to live.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="507">
		<line-text>If you laid all of the lawyers in the world, end to end, on the equator ---- It would be a good idea to just leave them there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="508">
		<line-text>Law is order, and good law is good order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="509">
		<line-text>When fascism comes to America, it will come wrapped in the American flag.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="510">
		<line-text>Most of our future lies ahead.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="511">
		<line-text>Hope is the poor man's bread.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="512">
		<line-text>Few people think more than two or three times a year; I have made an international reputation for myself by thinking once or twice a week.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="513">
		<line-text>If you would not be forgotten, as soon as you are rotten,
either write things worth reading or do things worth the writing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="514">
		<line-text>It was like passing the scene of a highway accident and being relieved to learn that nobody had been seriously injured.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="515">
		<line-text>Many a man has finally succeeded only because he has failed after repeated efforts. If he had never met defeat he would never have known any great victory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="516">
		<line-text>Veni, vidi, vici.
[I came, I saw, I conquered]</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="517">
		<line-text>...You don't need a weatherman to know which way the wind blows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="518">
		<line-text>Wisdom is knowing what to do next; virtue is doing it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="519">
		<line-text>When a quiet man is moved to passion, it seems the very earth will shake.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="520">
		<line-text>You can discover what your enemy fears most by observing the means he uses to frighten you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="521">
		<line-text>Great minds have purposes, others have wishes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="522">
		<line-text>In the vast reaches of the dry, cold night, thousands of stars were constantly appearing, and their sparkling icicles, loosened at once, began to slip gradually toward the horizon.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="523">
		<line-text>Progress is impossible without change, and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="524">
		<line-text>A cult is a religion with no political power.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="525">
		<line-text>The meanest, most contemptible kind of praise is that which first speaks well of a man, and then qualifies it with a &quot;but&quot;.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="526">
		<line-text>It is the cause, not the death, that makes the martyr.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="527">
		<line-text>Be regular and orderly in your life, that you may be violent and original in your work.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="528">
		<line-text>Science is a wonderful thing if one does not have to earn one's living at it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="529">
		<line-text>A true philosopher is like an elephant; he never puts the second foot down until the first one is solidly in place.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="530">
		<line-text>The quickest way of ending a war is to lose it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="531">
		<line-text>I bought some powdered water yesterday. I don't know what to add.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="532">
		<line-text>He that has done you a kindness will be more ready to do you another, than he whom you yourself have obliged.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="533">
		<line-text>The human brain starts working the moment you are born and never stops until you stand up to speak in public.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="534">
		<line-text>...as to moral feeling, this supposed special sense, the appeal to it is indeed superficial when those who cannot think believe that feeling will help them out, even in what concerns general laws: and besides, feelings which naturally differ infinitely in degree cannot furnish a uniform standard of good and evil, nor has any one a right to form judgments for others by his own feelings...</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="535">
		<line-text>Character can not be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be strengthened, ambition inspired, and success achieved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="536">
		<line-text>A facility for quotation covers the absence of original thought.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="537">
		<line-text>The worst crime against working people is a company which fails to operate at a profit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="538">
		<line-text>The story so far: In the beginning the Universe was created. This has made a lot of people very angry and has been widely regarded as a bad move.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="539">
		<line-text>The conqueror and king in each of us is the Knower of truth. Let that Knower awaken in us and drive the horses of the mind, emotions, and physical body on the pathway which that king has chosen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="540">
		<line-text>I do not want the peace which passeth understanding, I want the understanding which bringeth peace.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="541">
		<line-text>Many people think that if they were only in some other place, or had some other job, they would be happy. Well, that is doubtful. So get as much happiness out of what you are doing as you can and don't put off being happy until some future date.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="542">
		<line-text>Work, which makes a man free, and thought, which makes him worthy of freedom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="543">
		<line-text>The most radical revolutionary will become a conservative the day after the revolution.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="544">
		<line-text>Its embarrassing, you try to overthrow the government and you wind up on a Best Sellers List.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="545">
		<line-text>Fools make a mock at sin.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="546">
		<line-text>Never stop learning; knowledge doubles every fourteen months.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="547">
		<line-text>The most important thing in life is to see to it that you are never beaten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="548">
		<line-text>If the truth doesn't save us, what does that say about us?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="549">
		<line-text>It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="550">
		<line-text>A truth that's told with bad intent, Beats all the lies you can invent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="551">
		<line-text>If you marry you will regret it. If you do not marry you will regret it. If you marry or do not marry, you will regret it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="552">
		<line-text>If it bleeds, you can kill it</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="553">
		<line-text>It is after you have lost your teeth that you can afford to buy steaks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="554">
		<line-text>Delay is preferable to error.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="555">
		<line-text>One of the symptoms of an approaching nervous breakdown is the belief that one's work is terribly important.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="556">
		<line-text>A gentleman is a man who can play the accordion but doesn't.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="557">
		<line-text>In every aspect of our lives, we are always asking ourselves, How am I of value? What is my worth? Yet I believe that worthiness is our birthright.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="558">
		<line-text>My doctor told me to stop having intimate dinners for four. Unless there are three other people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="559">
		<line-text>Sometimes being a good friend means being harsh.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="560">
		<line-text>I do the very best I can to look upon life with optimism and hope and looking forward to a better day, but I don't think there is anything such as complete happiness. It pains me that there is still a lot of Klan activity and racism. I think when you say you're happy, you have everything that you need and everything that you want, and nothing more to wish for. I haven't reached that stage yet.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="561">
		<line-text>Democracy means government by discussion, but it is only effective if you can stop people talking.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="562">
		<line-text>Do not rely completely on any other human being, however dear. We meet all life's greatest tests alone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="563">
		<line-text>How come we rejoice at a birth and grieve at a funeral? It is because we are not the person involved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="564">
		<line-text>If by the last quarter of the twentiesth century godliness wasn't next to something a little more interesting than cleanliness, it might be time to reevaluate our notions of godliness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="565">
		<line-text>Bear in mind, if you are going to amount to anything, that your success does not depend upon the brilliancy and the impetuosity with which you take hold, but upon the ever lasting and sanctified bulldoggedness with which you hang on after you have taken hold.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="566">
		<line-text>It was said that boys should go on their first sea voyage at the age of ten, but surely this notion was never put forth by anyone's mother. If the bay were to be raised one degree in temperature for every woman who had lost the man or child she loved at sea, the water would have boiled, throwing off steam even in the dead of winter, poaching the bluefish and herings as they swam.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="567">
		<line-text>One must be a wise reader to quote wisely and well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="568">
		<line-text>How could I lose to such an idiot?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="569">
		<line-text>When a man is not amused, he feels an involuntary contempt for those who are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="570">
		<line-text>What would the world do without tea? - how did it exist? I am glad I was not born before tea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="571">
		<line-text>Concern should drive us into action and not into depression.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="572">
		<line-text>How easy it is for generous sentiments, high courtesy, and chivalrous courage to lose their influence beneath the chilling blight of selfishness, and to exhibit to the world a man who was great in all the minor attributes of character, but who was found wanting when it became necessary to prove how much principle is superior to policy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="573">
		<line-text>In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life. It goes on.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="574">
		<line-text>It's important to begin a search on a full stomach.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="575">
		<line-text>A noble man compares and estimates himself by an idea which is higher than himself; and a mean man, by one lower than himself. The one produces aspiration; the other ambition, which is the way in which a vulgar man aspires.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="576">
		<line-text>The great end of education is to discipline rather than to furnish the mind; to train it to the use of its own powers, rather than fill it with the accumulation of others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="577">
		<line-text>The desire for safety stands against every great and noble enterprise.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="578">
		<line-text>If man could have half his wishes, he would double his troubles.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="579">
		<line-text>Nothing is beautiful except the abnormal; and nothing is abnormal until we have grasped the norm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="580">
		<line-text>Crabbed age and youth cannot live together.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="581">
		<line-text>The time is always right to do what is right.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="582">
		<line-text>The effort to understand the universe is one of the very few things that lifts human life a little above the level of farce, and gives it some of the grace of tragedy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="583">
		<line-text>This is the day upon which we are reminded of what we are on the other three hundred and sixty-four.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="584">
		<line-text>The power of love, as the basis of a State, has never been tried.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="585">
		<line-text>Do not be afraid of defeat. you are never so near victory as when defeated in a good cause</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="586">
		<line-text>A synonym is a word you use when you can't spell the word you first thought of.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="587">
		<line-text>The deeper sorrow carves into your being the more joy you can contain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="588">
		<line-text>The test of courage comes when we are in the minority. The test of tolerance comes when we are in the majority.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="589">
		<line-text>Cleverness is like a lens with a very sharp focus. Wisdom is more like a wide-angle lens.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="590">
		<line-text>Hard work spotlights the character of people: some turn up their sleeves, some turn up their noses, and some don't turn up at all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="591">
		<line-text>Language is made out of concrete things. General expressions in non- concrete terms are a laziness, they are talk, not art, not creation. They are the reaction of things on the writer, not a creative act by the writer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="592">
		<line-text>You wake me up early in the morning to tell me I am right? Please wait until I am wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="593">
		<line-text>And virtue, though in rags, will keep me warm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="594">
		<line-text>Children will adapt to nearly any rule or routine as long as it is consistently enforced within that particular household.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="595">
		<line-text>I might have made a tactical error not going to a physician for 20 years. It was one of those phobias that didn't pay off.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="596">
		<line-text>Never let the fear of failure be an excuse for not trying. Society tells us that to fail is the most terrible thing in the world, but I know it isn't. Failure is part of what makes us human.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="597">
		<line-text>You cram these words into mine ears against the stomach of my sense.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="598">
		<line-text>The only thing you can't trade for your heart's desire is your heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="599">
		<line-text>Silent gratitude isn't much use to anyone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="600">
		<line-text>W (double U) has, of all the letters in our alphabet, the only cumbrous name, the names of the others being monosyllabic. This advantage of the Roman alphabet over the Grecian is the more valued after audibly spelling out some simple Greek word, like _epixoriambikos_. Still, it is now thought by the learned that other agencies than the difference of the two alphabets may have been concerned in the decline of &quot;the glory that was Greece&quot; and the rise of &quot;the grandeur that was Rome.&quot; There can be no doubt, however, that by simplifying the name of W (calling it &quot;wow,&quot; for example) our civilization could be, if not promoted, at least better endured.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="601">
		<line-text>Say what you will about the sweet miracle of unquestioning faith, I consider a capacity for it terrifying and absolutely vile!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="602">
		<line-text>Take a two-mile walk every morning before breakfast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="603">
		<line-text>Love is the triumph of imagination over intelligence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="604">
		<line-text>If you want to succeed you should strike out on new paths, rather than travel the worn paths of accepted success.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="605">
		<line-text>False words are not only evil in themselves, but they infect the soul with evil.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="606">
		<line-text>Youth cannot know how age thinks and feels. But old men are guilty if they forget what it was to be young.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="607">
		<line-text>Wisdom is what's left after we've run out of personal opinions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="608">
		<line-text>There is nothing so asinine that governments will not proclaim it as official doctrine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="609">
		<line-text>Pay no attention to what the critics say; there has never been set up a statue in honor of a critic.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="610">
		<line-text>One would think that if you're anonymous, you'd do anything you want, but groups have their own sense of community and what we can do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="611">
		<line-text>A strict observance of the written laws is doubtless one of the high virtues of a good citizen, but it is not the highest. The laws of necessity, of self preservation, of saving our country when in danger, are of higher obligation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="612">
		<line-text>Dictators long ago found out it is easier to unite people in common hatred than common love.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="613">
		<line-text>The deepest sin against the human mind is to believe things without evidence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="614">
		<line-text>If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="615">
		<line-text>Everybody is too busy with their own lives to give a damn about your book, painting, screenplay etc, especially if you haven't sold it yet. And the ones that aren't, you don't want in your life anyway.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="616">
		<line-text>Many persons have a wrong idea of what constitutes true happiness. It is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="617">
		<line-text>I love quotations because it is a joy to find thoughts one might have, beautifully expressed with much authority by someone recognized wiser than oneself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="618">
		<line-text>I will say this about being an optimist-- even when things don't turn out well, you are certain they will get better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="619">
		<line-text>Each religion, by the help of more or less myth which it takes more or less seriously, proposes some method of fortifying the human soul and enabline it to make its peace with its destiny.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="620">
		<line-text>Peace at home is peace in the country. Peace in the country is peace in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="621">
		<line-text>Next to the originator of a good sentence is the first quoter of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="622">
		<line-text>The Lord gave, and the Lord hath taken away; blessed be the name of the Lord.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="623">
		<line-text>The major concrete achievement of the women's movement of the 1970's was the Dutch treat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="624">
		<line-text>I would not attack the faith of a heathen without being sure I had a better one to put in its place.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="625">
		<line-text>A really companionable and indispensable dog is an accident of nature. You can't get it by breeding and you can't buy it with money. It just happens along.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="626">
		<line-text>Amusement is the happiness of those who cannot think.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="627">
		<line-text>An apology for the devil: it must be remembered that we have heard only one side of the case; God has written all the books.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="628">
		<line-text>The price good men pay for indifference to public affairs is to be ruled by evil men.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="629">
		<line-text>Living with small children is like having a bowling alley set up in your brain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="630">
		<line-text>There is nothing more helpless and irresponsible than a man in the depths of an ether binge.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="631">
		<line-text>I never saw a wild thing sorry for itself. A bird will fall frozen dead from a bough without ever having felt sorry for itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="632">
		<line-text>By heritage and by choice, the United States of America will make that stand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="633">
		<line-text>A good many things go around in the dark besides Santa Claus.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="634">
		<line-text>Before a war, military science seems a real science, like astronomy. After a war it seems more like astrology.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="635">
		<line-text>Beware the man of one book.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="636">
		<line-text>I am not in this world to live up to other people's expectations, nor do I feel that the world must live up to mine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="637">
		<line-text>What makes something special is not just what you have to gain, but what you feel there is to lose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="638">
		<line-text>Give your hearts, but not into each other’s keeping,
For only the hand of God can contain your hearts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="639">
		<line-text>Patriotism is a pernicious, psychopathic form of idiocy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="640">
		<line-text>The administration is not sympathetic to corporations, it is indentured to corporations.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="641">
		<line-text>If you aren’t going to say something directly to someone’s face, than don’t use online as an opportunity to say it. It is this sense of bravery that people get when they are anonymous that gives the blogosphere a bad reputation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="642">
		<line-text>Beware
Of entrance to a quarrel; but being in,
Bear't that the opposed may beware of thee.
Give every man thy ear, but few thy voice;
Take each man's censure, but reserve thy judgment.
Costly thy habit as thy purse can buy,
But not express'd in fancy; rich, not gaudy;
For the apparel oft proclaims the man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="643">
		<line-text>Wisdom is better than wit, and in the long run will certainly have the laugh on her side.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="644">
		<line-text>The road up and the road down is one and the same.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="645">
		<line-text>The end of all education should surely be service to others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="646">
		<line-text>You will never be alone with a poet in your pocket.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="647">
		<line-text>We are not without accomplishment. We have managed to distribute poverty equally.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="648">
		<line-text>I agree with everything you say, but I would attack to the death your right to say it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="649">
		<line-text>The turtle lives 'twixt plated decks
Which practically conceal its sex.
I think it clever of the turtle
In such a fix to be so fertile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="650">
		<line-text>You can use all the quantitative data you can get, but you still have to distrust it and use your own intelligence and judgment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="651">
		<line-text>I don't mind a little praise - as long as it's fulsome.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="652">
		<line-text>Man is born to live, not to prepare for life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="653">
		<line-text>For the poor always ye have with you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="654">
		<line-text>Strangers are just family you have yet to come to know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="655">
		<line-text>Destiny is a name often given in retrospect to choices that had dramatic consequences.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="656">
		<line-text>If a man remembers what is right at the sign of profit, is ready to lay down his life in the face of danger, and does not forget sentiments he has repeated all his life when he has been in straitened circumstances for a long time, he may be said to be a complete man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="657">
		<line-text>Give me the luxuries of life and I will willingly do without the necessities.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="658">
		<line-text>Mach-S, the speed at which stress can't keep up, is simply forward motion. But it has to be self- propelled. Note that people in cars are still stressed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="659">
		<line-text>The most important thing in life is to see to it that you are never beaten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="660">
		<line-text>The men who had hated [the book], and had not particularly loved Helvétius, flocked round him now. Voltaire forgave him all injuries, intentional or unintentional. 'What a fuss about an omelette!' he had exclaimed when he heard of the burning. How abominably unjust to persecute a man for such an airy trifle as that! 'I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it,' was his attitude now.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="661">
		<line-text>There are, in the affairs of men and nations, inexorable tides from which they cannot remain aloof.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="662">
		<line-text>The Constitution gives every American the inalienable right to make a damn fool of himself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="663">
		<line-text>In times of change, learners inherit the Earth, while the learned find themselves beautifully equipped to deal with a world that no longer exists.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="664">
		<line-text>Sending important messages via text is the coward’s way out. Don’t be the person who texts important messages. It’s rude, inconsiderate, and, yes, cowardly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="665">
		<line-text>To try to be better is to be better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="666">
		<line-text>Poetry and Hums aren't things which you get, they're things which get you. And all you can do is go where they can find you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="667">
		<line-text>Save a little money each month and at the end of the year you'll be surprised at how little you have.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="668">
		<line-text>Concentration comes out of a combination of confidence and hunger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="669">
		<line-text>The first question I ask myself when something doesn't seem to be beautiful is why do I think it's not beautiful. And very shortly you discover that there is no reason.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="670">
		<line-text>Only the brave know how to forgive; it is the most refined and generous pitch of virtue human nature can arrive at.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="671">
		<line-text>No matter how old a mother is, she watches her middle-aged children for signs of improvement.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="672">
		<line-text>DELEGATION, n. In American politics, an article of merchandise that comes in sets.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="673">
		<line-text>The most annoying trait of Right-Wing Outlaws in general is a lazy incuriosity about the real world. They know their lines, they're sure who the good guys and the bad guys are. Therefore they view the passing world as a kind of animated &quot;Bartlett's Quotations&quot; - that is, as handy source material with which to illustrate, rather than challenge, preconceived views.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="674">
		<line-text>A gem is not polished without rubbing, nor a man perfected without trials.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="675">
		<line-text>A baby is God's opinion that the world should go on.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="676">
		<line-text>The significance of man is that he is insignificant and is aware of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="677">
		<line-text>Curiosity was a form of lust, a wandering cupidity of the eye and the mind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="678">
		<line-text>The hand that rules the press, the radio, the screen and the far-spread magazine, rules the country.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="679">
		<line-text>People fail forward to success.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="680">
		<line-text>They think too little who talk too much.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="681">
		<line-text>When a man is wrapped up in himself he makes a pretty small package.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="682">
		<line-text>It is impossible to imagine Goethe or Beethoven being good at billiards or golf.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="683">
		<line-text>The only lasting beauty is the beauty of the heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="684">
		<line-text>Time eases all things.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="685">
		<line-text>Education is the guardian genius of democracy. It is the only dictator that free men recognize, and the only ruler that free men require.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="686">
		<line-text>We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful what we pretend to be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="687">
		<line-text>Colleges typically did not tell you that ninety percent of your education came after you hung the parchment on the wall. People might ask for a rebate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="688">
		<line-text>Talent develops in tranquillity, character in the full current of human life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="689">
		<line-text>He played the king as if afraid someone else would play the ace.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="690">
		<line-text>I came to realize that life lived to help others is the only one that matters and that it is my duty...This is my highest and best use as a human.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="691">
		<line-text>All thought is naught but a footnote to Plato.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="692">
		<line-text>No more important duty can be urged upon those who are entering the great theater of life than simple loyalty to their best convictions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="693">
		<line-text>The test of a first-rate intelligence is the ability to hold two opposed ideas in the mind at the same time, and still retain the ability to function.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="694">
		<line-text>Don't pray that God's on our side, pray that we're on his side.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="695">
		<line-text>Happiness comes of the capacity to feel deeply, to enjoy simply, to think freely, to risk life, to be needed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="696">
		<line-text>The one permanent emotion of the inferior man is fear - fear of the unknown, the complex, the inexplicable. What he wants beyond everything else is safety.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="697">
		<line-text>Do the duty which lieth nearest to thee! Thy second duty will already have become clearer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="698">
		<line-text>Change is good, but dollars are better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="699">
		<line-text>Derive happiness in oneself from a good day's work, from illuminating the fog that surrounds us.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="700">
		<line-text>There is no avoiding war; it can only be postponed to the advantage of others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="701">
		<line-text>Children are very nice observers, and will often perceive your slightest defects. In general, those who govern children, forgive nothing in them, but everything in themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="702">
		<line-text>Thinking is the hardest work there is, which is probably the reason why so few engage in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="703">
		<line-text>When you have an efficient government, you have a dictatorship.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="704">
		<line-text>If men could only know each other, they would neither idolize nor hate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="705">
		<line-text>For every problem there is a solution which is simple, clean and wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="706">
		<line-text>Beware of the man who works hard to learn something, learns it, and finds himself no wiser than before... He is full of murderous resentment of people who are ignorant without having come by their ignorance the hard way.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="707">
		<line-text>In forming a judgment, lay your hearts void of foretaken opinions; else, whatsoever is done or said, will be measured by a wrong rule; like them who have jaundice, to whom everything appears yellow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="708">
		<line-text>What people call insincerity is simply a method by which we can multiply our personalities.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="709">
		<line-text>To achieve great things we must live as though we were never going to die.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="710">
		<line-text>FOOL, n. A person who pervades the domain of intellectual speculation and diffuses himself through the channels of moral activity. He is omnific, omniform, omnipercipient, omniscience, omnipotent. He it was who invented letters, printing, the railroad, the steamboat, the telegraph, the platitude and the circle of the sciences. He created patriotism and taught the nations war -- founded theology, philosophy, law, medicine and Chicago. He established monarchical and republican government. He is from everlasting to everlasting -- such as creation's dawn beheld he fooleth now. In the morning of time he sang upon primitive hills, and in the noonday of existence headed the procession of being. His grandmotherly hand was warmly tucked-in the set sun of civilization, and in the twilight he prepares Man's evening meal of milk-and-morality and turns down the covers of the universal grave. And after the rest of us shall have retired for the night of eternal oblivion he will sit up to write a history of human civilization.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="711">
		<line-text>The easy confidence with which I know another man's religion is folly teaches me to suspect that my own is also. I would not interfere with any one's religion, either to strengthen it or to weaken it. I am not able to believe one's religion can affect his hereafter one way or the other, no matter what that religion may be. But it may easily be a great comfort to him in this life--hence it is a valuable possession to him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="712">
		<line-text>Mama exhorted her children at every opportunity to 'jump at de sun.' We might not land on the sun, but at least we would get off the ground.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="713">
		<line-text>I wonder what it means when your grandson is more crotchety than you are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="714">
		<line-text>If we aren't capable of being hurt we aren't capable of feeling joy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="715">
		<line-text>The most important thing she'd learned over the years was that there was no way to be a perfect mother and a million ways to be a good one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="716">
		<line-text>Democracy gives every man the right to be his own oppressor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="717">
		<line-text>The prospect of success in achieving our most cherished dream is not without its terrors. Who is more deprived and alone than the man who has achieved his dream?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="718">
		<line-text>Don't be too timid and squeamish about your actions. All life is an experiment. The more experiments you make the better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="719">
		<line-text>I have found that among its other benefits, giving liberates the soul of the giver.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="720">
		<line-text>No one can terrorize a whole nation, unless we are all his accomplices.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="721">
		<line-text>Forever is composed of nows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="722">
		<line-text>Every person, all the events of your life, are there because you have drawn them there. What you choose to do with them is up to you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="723">
		<line-text>Sinful and forbidden pleasures are like poisoned bread; they may satisfy appetite for the moment, but there is death in them at the end.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="724">
		<line-text>The difficult child is the child who is unhappy. He is at war with himself; and in consequence, he is at war with the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="725">
		<line-text>The mint makes it first, it is up to you to make it last.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="726">
		<line-text>[M]aybe the most any of us can expect of ourselves isn't perfection but progress.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="727">
		<line-text>It's a time of sorrow and sadness when we lose a loss of life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="728">
		<line-text>Propaganda makes up our minds for us, but in such a way that it leaves us the sense of pride and satisfaction of men who have made up their own minds. And in the last analysis, propaganda achieves this effect because we want it to. This is one of the few real pleasures left to modern man: this illusion that he is thinking for himself when, in fact, someone else is doing his thinking for him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="729">
		<line-text>College isn't the place to go for ideas.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="730">
		<line-text>Friends need not agree in everything or go always together, or have no comparable other friendships of the same intimacy. On the contrary, in friendship union is more about ideal things: and in that sense it is more ideal and less subject to trouble than marriage is.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="731">
		<line-text>Brains, like hearts, go where they are appreciated.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="732">
		<line-text>It is light grief that can take counsel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="733">
		<line-text>Academic and aristocratic people live in such an uncommon atmosphere that common sense can rarely reach them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="734">
		<line-text>No good deed goes unpunished.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="735">
		<line-text>...a revolution of government is the strongest proof that can be given by a people of their virtue and good sense.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="736">
		<line-text>I expect to pass through this world but once; any good thing therefore that I can do, or any kindness that I can show to any fellow creature, let me do it now; let me not defer or neglect it, for I shall not pass this way again.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="737">
		<line-text>Education's purpose is to replace an empty mind with an open one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="738">
		<line-text>The difference between a democracy and a dictatorship is that in a democracy you vote first and take orders later; in a dictatorship you don't have to waste your time voting.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="739">
		<line-text>Nothing can be pleasing which is not also becoming.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="740">
		<line-text>It just seem like musicians want to sell a few records and put out a perfume line, and I think it's so sad that there are so many musicians who don't want to change the world... Music has been so much more.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="741">
		<line-text>Passionate hatred can give meaning and purpose to an empty life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="742">
		<line-text>There are laws for everything except the harm families do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="743">
		<line-text>A fault confessed is half redressed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="744">
		<line-text>Give me the luxuries of life and I will willingly do without the necessities.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="745">
		<line-text>Take the diplomacy out of war and the thing would fall flat in a week.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="746">
		<line-text>Pepsi brings your ancestors back from the grave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="747">
		<line-text>Wear the old coat and buy the new book.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="748">
		<line-text>Let's think the unthinkable, let's do the undoable, let's prepare to grapple with the ineffable itself, and see if we may not eff it after all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="749">
		<line-text>The comfortable estate of widowhood is the only hope that keeps up a wife's spirits.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="750">
		<line-text>There are only two kinds of people who are really fascinating: people who know absolutely everything, and people who know absolutely nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="751">
		<line-text>I was astonished at the effect my successful landing in France had on the nations of the world. To me, it was like a match lighting a bonfire.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="752">
		<line-text>In and of itself, nothing really matters. What matters is that nothing is ever in and of itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="753">
		<line-text>Nothing in life is as good as the marriage of true minds between man and woman. As good? It is life itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="754">
		<line-text>The people who are doing the work are the moving force behind the Macintosh. My job is to create a space for them, to clear out the rest of the organization and keep it at bay.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="755">
		<line-text>What I learned from Weight Watchers is that food was meant to be used as fuel for our bodies. If we are using it for any other reasons, it is time to take a step back and ask ourselves what’s up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="756">
		<line-text>Nothing is harder to direct than a man in prosperity; nothing more easily managed than one is adversity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="757">
		<line-text>Man is a natural polygamist: he always has one woman leading him by the nose, and another hanging on to his coattails.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="758">
		<line-text>In the Soviet army it takes more courage to retreat than to advance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="759">
		<line-text>In Tulsa, restaurants have signs that say, ``Sorry, we're open.''</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="760">
		<line-text>Get your facts first, and then you can distort them as much as you please. (Facts are stubborn, but statistics are more pliable.)</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="761">
		<line-text>It becomes a bore doing imaginative books that do not touch imaginations, and at length one stops even planning them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="762">
		<line-text>For a good cause, wrongdoing is virtuous.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="763">
		<line-text>Not that you lied to me, but that I no longer believe you, has shaken me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="764">
		<line-text>Having supplied them with names, omnipotence, justice, knowledge, Providence, - what are they?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="765">
		<line-text>Probably all laws are useless, for good men do not want laws at all, and bad men are made no better by them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="766">
		<line-text>Who overcomes by force hath overcome but half his foe.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="767">
		<line-text>I believe in God like I believe in the sun, not because I can see it, but because of it all things are seen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="768">
		<line-text>To fall in love you have to be in the state of mind for it to take, like a disease.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="769">
		<line-text>To generalize is to be an idiot.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="770">
		<line-text>My heart suspects more than mine eye can see.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="771">
		<line-text>Do not commit your poems to pages alone, sing them I pray you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="772">
		<line-text>I cannot sleep unless I am surrounded by books.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="773">
		<line-text>Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="774">
		<line-text>The bravest thing you can do when you are not brave is to profess courage and act accordingly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="775">
		<line-text>All general statements are false.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="776">
		<line-text>Honor has not to be won; it must only not be lost.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="777">
		<line-text>I opened the window and my heart. The sun flooded my house and love flooded my soul.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="778">
		<line-text>If you go on with this nuclear arms race, all you are going to do is make the rubble bounce.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="779">
		<line-text>There is a way in which the collective knowledge of mankind expresses itself, for the finite individual, through mere daily living... a way in which life itself is sheer knowing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="780">
		<line-text>THERE ARE NO MISTAKES, only opportunities.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="781">
		<line-text>A woman's heart is a deep ocean of secrets.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="782">
		<line-text>I am an agnostic; I do not pretend to know what many ignorant men are sure of.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="783">
		<line-text>Most people never run far enough on their first wind to find out they’ve got a second. Give your dreams all you’ve got and you’ll be amazed at the energy that comes out of you!!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="784">
		<line-text>It requires more courage to suffer than to die.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="785">
		<line-text>Copy from one, it's plagiarism; copy from two, it's research.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="786">
		<line-text>A likely impossibility is always preferable to an unconvincing possibility.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="787">
		<line-text>Beware of dissipating your powers; strive constantly to concentrate them. Genius thinks it can do whatever it sees others doing, but is sure to repent of every ill-judged outlay.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="788">
		<line-text>PIRACY, n. Commerce without its folly-swaddles, just as God made it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="789">
		<line-text>Clothes make the man. Naked people have little or no influence on society.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="790">
		<line-text>The last capitalist we hang shall be the one who sold us the rope.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="791">
		<line-text>Gray hair is God's graffiti.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="792">
		<line-text>Never has a man who has bent himself been able to make others straight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="793">
		<line-text>I'm not a bad guy! I work hard, and I love my kids. So why should I spend half my Sunday hearing about how I'm going to Hell?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="794">
		<line-text>History does not record anywhere at any time a religion that has any rational basis. Religion is a crutch for people not strong enough to stand up to the unknown without help. But, like dandruff, most people do have a religion and spend time and money on it and seem to derive considerable pleasure from fiddling with it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="795">
		<line-text>Charity begins at home, but shouldn't end there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="796">
		<line-text>People without an internalized symbolic system can all too easily become captives of the media.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="797">
		<line-text>Life without the courage for death is slavery.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="798">
		<line-text>An aim of an argument should be progress, but progress ultimately means little without victory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="799">
		<line-text>Life is as tedious as a twice-told tale vexing the dull ear of a drowsy man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="800">
		<line-text>The difference between the right word and the almost right word is the difference between lightning and a lightning bug.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="801">
		<line-text>Behold, how good and pleasant it is for brethren to dwell together in unity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="802">
		<line-text>The human mind treats a new idea the same way the body treats a strange protein; it rejects it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="803">
		<line-text>K is a consonant that we get from the Greeks, but it can be traced away back beyond them to the Cerathians, a small commercial nation inhabiting the peninsula of Smero. In their tongue it was called _Klatch_, which means &quot;destroyed.&quot; The form of the letter was originally precisely that of our H, but the erudite Dr. Snedeker explains that it was altered to its present shape to commemorate the destruction of the great temple of Jarute by an earthquake, _circa_ 730 B.C. This building was famous for the two lofty columns of its portico, one of which was broken in half by the catastrophe, the other remaining intact. As the earlier form of the letter is supposed to have been suggested by these pillars, so, it is thought by the great antiquary, its later was adopted as a simple and natural -- not to say touching -- means of keeping the calamity ever in the national memory. It is not known if the name of the letter was altered as an additional mnemonic, or if the name was always _Klatch_ and the destruction one of nature's pums. As each theory seems probable enough, I see no objection to believing both -- and Dr. Snedeker arrayed himself on that side of the question.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="804">
		<line-text>Hail to you gods, on that day of the great reckoning. Behold me, I have come to you, without sin, without guilt, without evil, without a witness against me, without one whom I have wronged. I am one pure of mouth, pure of hands.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="805">
		<line-text>No pain, no palm; no thorns, no throne; no gall, no glory; no cross, no crown.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="806">
		<line-text>All my life, whenever it comes time to make a decision, I make it and forget about it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="807">
		<line-text>It is not enough to aim; you must hit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="808">
		<line-text>If a person feels he can't communicate, the least he can do is shut up about it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="809">
		<line-text>Water is the most neglected nutrient in your diet but one of the most vital.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="810">
		<line-text>FIDELITY, n. A virtue peculiar to those who are about to be betrayed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="811">
		<line-text>The proof that man is the noblest of all creatures is that no other creature has ever denied it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="812">
		<line-text>To decide, to be at the level of choice, is to take responsibility for your life and to be in control of your life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="813">
		<line-text>Colleges typically did not tell you that ninety percent of your education came after you hung the parchment on the wall. People might ask for a rebate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="814">
		<line-text>Disney, of course, has the best casting. If he doesn't like an actor, he just tears him up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="815">
		<line-text>When you write things down, they sometimes take you places you hadn't planned.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="816">
		<line-text>Men are more often bribed by their loyalties and ambitions than by money.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="817">
		<line-text>Basic research is what I am doing when I don't know what I am doing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="818">
		<line-text>Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="819">
		<line-text>Crash programs fail because they are based on the theory that, with nine women pregnant, you can get a baby a month.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="820">
		<line-text>Every time I paint a portrait I lose a friend.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="821">
		<line-text>Do not measure your loss by itself; if you do, it will seem intolerable; but if you will take all human affairs into account you will find that some comfort is to be derived from them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="822">
		<line-text>Matter and impertinency mix'd! Reason in madness!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="823">
		<line-text>It is by no means self-evident that human beings are most real when most violently excited; violent physical passions do not in themselves differentiate men from each other, but rather tend to reduce them to the same state.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="824">
		<line-text>The perfect host requires the perfect parasite.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="825">
		<line-text>We started off trying to set up a small anarchist community, but people wouldn't obey the rules.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="826">
		<line-text>To be persuasive, we must be believable; to be believable we must be credible; to be credible, we must be truthful.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="827">
		<line-text>It is foolish to wish for beauty. Sensible people never either desire it for themselves or care about it in others. If the mind be but well cultivated, and the heart well disposed, no one ever cares for the exterior.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="828">
		<line-text>MAN, n. An animal so lost in rapturous contemplation of what he thinks he is as to overlook what he indubitably ought to be. His chief occupation is extermination of other animals and his own species, which, however, multiplies with such insistent rapidity as to infest the whole habitable earth and Canada.

When the world was young and Man was new,
And everything was pleasant,
Distinctions Nature never drew
'Mongst kings and priest and peasant.
We're not that way at present,
Save here in this Republic, where
We have that old regime,
For all are kings, however bare
Their backs, howe'er extreme
Their hunger. And, indeed, each has a voice
To accept the tyrant of his party's choice.

A citizen who would not vote,
And, therefore, was detested,
Was one day with a tarry coat
(With feathers backed and breasted)
By patriots invested.
&quot;It is your duty,&quot; cried the crowd,
&quot;Your ballot true to cast
For the man o' your choice.&quot; He humbly bowed,
And explained his wicked past:
&quot;That's what I very gladly would have done,
Dear patriots, but he has never run.&quot;
Apperton Duke</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="829">
		<line-text>Be ye angry, and sin not: let not the sun go down upon your wrath.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="830">
		<line-text>If a man does not keep pace with his companions, perhaps it is because he hears a different drummer. Let him step to the music which he hears, however measured or far away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="831">
		<line-text>I never saw a wild thing sorry for itself. A bird will fall frozen dead from a bough without ever having felt sorry for itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="832">
		<line-text>The hopeful man sees success where others see failure, sunshine where others see shadows and storm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="833">
		<line-text>What others think of us would be of little moment did it not, when known, so deeply tinge what we think of ourselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="834">
		<line-text>DICTIONARY, n. A malevolent literary device for cramping the growth of a language and making it hard and inelastic. This dictionary, however, is a most useful work.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="835">
		<line-text>Reality isn't what it used to be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="836">
		<line-text>Walking is man's best medicine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="837">
		<line-text>It struck him really that he had never so lived with her as during this period of her silence; the silence was a sacred hush, a finer clearer medium, in which her idiosyncrasies showed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="838">
		<line-text>Silence is one of the great arts of conversation, as allowed by Cicero himself, who says, &quot;there is not only an art, but an eloquence in it.&quot; A well bred woman may easily and effectually promote the most useful and elegant conversation without speaking a word. The modes of speech are scarcely more variable than the modes of silence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="839">
		<line-text>What's infamy matter when you get to keep your fortune?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="840">
		<line-text>What really keeps me going is the constant belief that it could all disappear tomorrow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="841">
		<line-text>I don't think you're a very good friend if you're always being supportive. You also have to add criticism.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="842">
		<line-text>Wealth is not of necessity a curse, nor poverty a blessing. Wholesome and easy abundance is better than either extreme; better for our manhood that we have enough for daily comfort; enough for culture, for hospitality, for charity. More than this may or may not be a blessing. Certainly it can be a blessing only by being accepted as a trust.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="843">
		<line-text>What seest thou else
In the dark backward and abysm of time?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="844">
		<line-text>Let your life be a counter friction to stop the machine.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="845">
		<line-text>The only people who seem to have nothing to do with the education of the children are the parents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="846">
		<line-text>The ultimate determinant in the struggle now going on for the world will not be bombs and rockets but a test of wills and ideas-a trial of spiritual resolve: the values we hold, the beliefs we cherish and the ideals to which we are dedicated.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="847">
		<line-text>George Bush taking credit for the Berlin Wall coming down is like the rooster taking credit for the sunrise.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="848">
		<line-text>Anger repressed can poison a relationship as surely as the cruelest words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="849">
		<line-text>Conspicuous consumption of valuable goods is a means of reputability to the gentleman of leisure.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="850">
		<line-text>I've always tried to go a step past wherever people expected me to end up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="851">
		<line-text>OATH, n. In law, a solemn appeal to the Deity, made binding upon the conscience by a penalty for perjury.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="852">
		<line-text>Man's capacity for justice makes democracy possible, but man's inclination to injustice makes democracy necessary.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="853">
		<line-text>Somewhere on this globe, every ten seconds, there is a woman giving birth to a child. She must be found and stopped.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="854">
		<line-text>Stone walls do not a prison make, nor iron bars a cage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="855">
		<line-text>Brevity is the soul of wit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="856">
		<line-text>The toughest question has always been, &quot;How do you get your ideas?&quot; How do you answer that? It's like asking runners how they run, or singers how they sing. They just do it!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="857">
		<line-text>Saying what we think gives us a wider conversational range than saying what we know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="858">
		<line-text>The two most common elements in the universe are Hydrogen and stupidity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="859">
		<line-text>If you choose not to decide, you still have made a choice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="860">
		<line-text>There is a great deal of talk about loyalty from the bottom to the top. Loyalty from the top down is even more necessary and much less prevalent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="861">
		<line-text>In the arithmetic of love, one plus one equals everything, and two minus one equals nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="862">
		<line-text>Think you can, think you can't, you are Right!!!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="863">
		<line-text>Seize the day, put no trust in the morrow!
[Carpe diem, quam minimum credula postero.]</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="864">
		<line-text>The speed of the boss is the speed of the team</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="865">
		<line-text>The secret of a good life is to have the right loyalties and to hold them in the right scale of values.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="866">
		<line-text>That man can destroy life is just as miraculous a feat as that he can create it, for life is the miracle, the inexplicable. In the act of destruction, man sets himself above life; he transcends himself as a creature. Thus, the ultimate choice for a man, inasmuch as he is driven to transcend himself, is to create or to destroy, to love or to hate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="867">
		<line-text>Everything I did in my life that was worthwhile I caught hell for.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="868">
		<line-text>If there were a verb meaning &quot;to believe falsely,&quot; it would not have any significant first person, present indicative.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="869">
		<line-text>To overcome evil with good is good, to resist evil by evil is evil.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="870">
		<line-text>Humor is always based on a modicum of truth. Have you ever heard a joke about a father-in-law?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="871">
		<line-text>Any one who has common sense will remember that the bewilderments of the eyes are of two kinds, and arise from two causes, either from coming out of the light or from going into the light, which is true of the mind's eye, quite as much as of the bodily eye; and he who remembers this when he sees any one whose vision is perplexed and weak, will not be too ready to laugh; he will first ask whether that soul of man has come out of the brighter light, and is unable to see because unaccustomed to the dark, or having turned from darkness to the day is dazzled by excess of light.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="872">
		<line-text>There is always something ridiculous about the emotions of people whom one has ceased to love.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="873">
		<line-text>It takes tremendous discipline to control the influence, the power you have over other people's lives.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="874">
		<line-text>But they shall sit every man under his vine and under his fig tree.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="875">
		<line-text>I don't generally feel anything until noon; then it's time for my nap.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="876">
		<line-text>Praise, like gold and diamonds, owes its value only to its scarcity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="877">
		<line-text>EXPERIENCE, n. The wisdom that enables us to recognize as an undesirable old acquaintance the folly that we have already embraced.

To one who, journeying through night and fog,
Is mired neck-deep in an unwholesome bog,
Experience, like the rising of the dawn,
Reveals the path that he should not have gone.
Joel Frad Bink</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="878">
		<line-text>I don't care how poor and inefficient a little country is; they like to run their own business. I know men that would make my wife a better husband than I am; but, darn it, I'm not going to give her to 'em.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="879">
		<line-text>Men generally believe what they wish.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="880">
		<line-text>Ignorant men don't know what good they hold in their hands until they've flung it away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="881">
		<line-text>Those who become enamored of practices without science are like sailors who go aboard ship without a rudder and compass, for they are never certain where they will land.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="882">
		<line-text>I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="883">
		<line-text>Our incomes are like our shoes; if too small, they gall and pinch us; but if too large, they cause us to stumble and to trip.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="884">
		<line-text>Beware the fury of a patient man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="885">
		<line-text>Real stupidity beats artificial intelligence every time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="886">
		<line-text>A writer must refuse to allow himself to be transformed into an institution.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="887">
		<line-text>Books are hindrances to persisting stupidity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="888">
		<line-text>Let me tell you the secret that has led me to my goal. My strength lies solely in my tenacity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="889">
		<line-text>All that a man does outwardly is but the expression and completion of his inward thought. To work effectually, he must think clearly; to act nobly, he must think nobly. Intellectual force is a principal element of the soul's life, and should be proposed by every man as the principal end of his being.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="890">
		<line-text>Between the great things we cannot do and the small things we will not do, the danger is that we shall do nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="891">
		<line-text>Good humor is one of the best articles of dress one can wear in society.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="892">
		<line-text>Confidence in nonsense is a requirement for the creative process.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="893">
		<line-text>People are more violently opposed to fur than leather because it's safer to harass rich women than motorcycle gangs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="894">
		<line-text>It's always been about the experience of life and of not being passive. If something so excites my curiosty, I want to go there, be a part of whatever it is that's either pushing me or pulling me toward it. That desire for experience has made me very rich in life experience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="895">
		<line-text>I will permit no man to narrow and degrade my soul by making me hate him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="896">
		<line-text>The purpose of life is to live it, to taste experience to the utmost, to reach out eagerly and without fear for newer and richer experience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="897">
		<line-text>Get the facts, or the facts will get you. And when you get them, get them right, or they will get you wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="898">
		<line-text>A friend is one before whom I may think aloud.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="899">
		<line-text>The family is changing not disappearing. We have to broaden our understanding of it, look for the new metaphors.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="900">
		<line-text>A strong positive mental attitude will create more miracles than any wonder drug.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="901">
		<line-text>You do not examine legislation in the light of the benefits it will convey if properly administered, but in the light of the wrongs it would do and the harms it would cause if improperly administered.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="902">
		<line-text>In modern America, anyone who attempts to write satirically about the events of the day finds it difficult to concoct a situation so bizarre that it may not actually come to pass while the article is still on the presses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="903">
		<line-text>Dost thou not know, my son, with how little wisdom the world is governed?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="904">
		<line-text>The man who lets himself be bored is even more contemptible than the bore.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="905">
		<line-text>California, the department store state.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="906">
		<line-text>The essence of living is discovering. Indeed, it is the joy of discovering that makes life worth the effort.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="907">
		<line-text>Don't take life too seriously. You'll never get out of it alive.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="908">
		<line-text>I gotta be me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="909">
		<line-text>I was gratified to be able to answer promptly. I said I don't know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="910">
		<line-text>I don't think of myself as a poor deprived ghetto girl who made good. I think of myself as somebody who from an early age knew I was responsible for myself, and I had to make good.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="911">
		<line-text>Even the longest day has its end.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="912">
		<line-text>Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="913">
		<line-text>We think very few people sensible, except those who are of our opinion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="914">
		<line-text>To will is to select a goal, determine a course of action that will bring one to that goal, and then hold to that action till the goal is reached. The key is action.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="915">
		<line-text>An enormous part of our mature experience cannot not be expressed in words.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="916">
		<line-text>Envy is what makes you, when an aquaintance is lustily telling you that she's dating a Greek god of a guy, ask, &quot;Which one, Hades?&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="917">
		<line-text>Children are natural mimics; they act like their parents in spite of every effort to teach them good manners.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="918">
		<line-text>I do think imperfection's underrated.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="919">
		<line-text>HIBERNATE, v.i. To pass the winter season in domestic seclusion. There have been many singular popular notions about the hibernation of various animals. Many believe that the bear hibernates during the whole winter and subsists by mechanically sucking its paws. It is admitted that it comes out of its retirement in the spring so lean that it had to try twice before it can cast a shadow. Three or four centuries ago, in England, no fact was better attested than that swallows passed the winter months in the mud at the bottom of their brooks, clinging together in globular masses. They have apparently been compelled to give up the custom and account of the foulness of the brooks. Sotus Ecobius discovered in Central Asia a whole nation of people who hibernate. By some investigators, the fasting of Lent is supposed to have been originally a modified form of hibernation, to which the Church gave a religious significance; but this view was strenuously opposed by that eminent authority, Bishop Kip, who did not wish any honors denied to the memory of the Founder of his family.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="920">
		<line-text>... spell `creat' with an E.'</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="921">
		<line-text>If someone tells you he is going to make ``a realistic decision,' you immediately understand that he is going to do something bad.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="922">
		<line-text>This report, by its very length, defends itself against being read.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="923">
		<line-text>REFUGE, n. Anything assuring protection to one in peril. Moses and Joshua provided six cities of refuge -- Bezer, Golan, Ramoth, Kadesh, Schekem and Hebron -- to which one who had taken life inadvertently could flee when hunted by relatives of the deceased. This admirable expedient supplied him with wholesome exercise and enabled them to enjoy the pleasures of the chase; whereby the soul of the dead man was appropriately honored by observations akin to the funeral games of early Greece.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="924">
		<line-text>Can the Ethiopian change his skin, or the leopard his spots?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="925">
		<line-text>By the time a man realizes that maybe his father was right, he usually has a son who thinks he's wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="926">
		<line-text>Humor is the great thing, the saving thing. The minute it crops up, all our irritations and resentments slip away and a sunny spirit takes their place.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="927">
		<line-text>Our bodies communicate to us clearly and specifically, if we are willing to listen to them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="928">
		<line-text>The world breaks everyone and afterward many are strong in the broken places. But those that will not break it kills. It kills the very good and the very gentle and the very brave impartially. If you are none of these you can be sure it will kill you too but there will be no special hurry.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="929">
		<line-text>America is the greatest of opportunities and the worst of influences.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="930">
		<line-text>Players win games, teams win championships.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="931">
		<line-text>Accept the pain, cherish the joys, resolve the regrets; then can come the best of benedictions - 'If I had my life to live over, I'd do it all the same.'</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="932">
		<line-text>An idea isn't responsible for the people who believe in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="933">
		<line-text>Swat my hind with a mellon rind, That's my penguin state of mind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="934">
		<line-text>God conceals himself from the mind of man, but reveals himself to his heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="935">
		<line-text>Many persons have a wrong idea of what constitutes true happiness. It is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="936">
		<line-text>LEVIATHAN, n. An enormous aquatic animal mentioned by Job. Some suppose it to have been the whale, but that distinguished ichthyologer, Dr. Jordan, of Stanford University, maintains with considerable heat that it was a species of gigantic Tadpole (_Thaddeus Polandensis_) or Polliwig -- _Maria pseudo-hirsuta_. For an exhaustive description and history of the Tadpole consult the famous monograph of Jane Potter, _Thaddeus of Warsaw_.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="937">
		<line-text>No liberal man would impute a charge of unsteadiness to another for having changed his opinion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="938">
		<line-text>It is a bad plan that admits of no modification.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="939">
		<line-text>After a year in therapy, my psychiatrist said to me, &quot;Maybe life isn't for everyone.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="940">
		<line-text>Anyone who's ever significantly changed the course of humanity has either been a Crackpot, a Heretic, or a Dissident. In the case of Albert Einstein, he was all three!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="941">
		<line-text>Women who seek to be equal with men lack ambition.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="942">
		<line-text>Change does not change tradition. It strengthens it. Change is a challenge and an opportunity, not a threat.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="943">
		<line-text>Do all the good you can, By all the means you can, In all the ways you can, In all the places you can, At all the times you can, To all the people you can, As long as ever you can.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="944">
		<line-text>Overlook our deeds, since you know that crime was absent from our inclination.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="945">
		<line-text>It is better to give than to lend and it costs about the same.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="946">
		<line-text>The courage to be is the courage to accept oneself, in spite of being unacceptable.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="947">
		<line-text>COMMENDATION, n. The tribute that we pay to achievements that resembles, but do not equal, our own.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="948">
		<line-text>Don't underestimate the value of Doing Nothing, of just going along, listening to all the things you can't hear, and not bothering.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="949">
		<line-text>Do not be afraid of defeat. you are never so near victory as when defeated in a good cause</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="950">
		<line-text>Better hold the hand for coin, though small, Than lose, for one half a dang, it all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="951">
		<line-text>It is most unwise for people in love to marry</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="952">
		<line-text>Relationships of trust depend on our willingness to look not only to our own interests, but also the interests of others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="953">
		<line-text>You can't show love to someone at the expense of someone else who loves you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="954">
		<line-text>I read part of it all the way through.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="955">
		<line-text>As part of it's 'Astro' program LAPD helicopters maintain an average nineteen-hours-per-day vigil over 'high crime areas', tactically coordinated to patrol car forces, and exceeding even the British Army's aerial surveillance of Belfast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="956">
		<line-text>Good people do not need laws to tell them to act responsibly, while bad people will find a way around the laws.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="957">
		<line-text>Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="958">
		<line-text>When I'm inspired, I get excited because I can't wait to see what I'll come up with next.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="959">
		<line-text>Maybe kissing is sort of like nature's coffee.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="960">
		<line-text>The people who are regarded as moral luminaries are those who forego ordinary pleasures themselves and find compensation in interfering with the pleasures of others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="961">
		<line-text>Nietzche started a nonsensical idea that men had once sought as good what we now call evil; if it were so, we could not talk of surpassing or even falling short of them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="962">
		<line-text>Indecision is like a stepchild: if he does not wash his hands, he is called dirty, if he does, he is wasting water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="963">
		<line-text>MANES, n. The immortal parts of dead Greeks and Romans. They were in a state of dull discomfort until the bodies from which they had exhaled were buried and burned; and they seem not to have been particularly happy afterward.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="964">
		<line-text>The time to relax is -- when you don't have time for it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="965">
		<line-text>Badness is only spoiled goodness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="966">
		<line-text>NOISE, n. A stench in the ear. Undomesticated music. The chief product and authenticating sign of civilization.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="967">
		<line-text>Hanging is too good for a man who makes puns; he should be drawn and quoted.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="968">
		<line-text>Nothing is worth more than this day.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="969">
		<line-text>Now that I've relinquished my fantasies of all the people I wish I could be, and stopped feeling guilty about [them], I have more time for the things that I truly enjoy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="970">
		<line-text>There is a tragic flaw in our precious Constitution, and I don't know what can be done to fix it. This is it: Only nut cases want to be president.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="971">
		<line-text>The prospect of a long day at the beach makes me panic. There is no harder work I can think of than taking myself off to somewhere pleasant, where I am forced to stay for hours and 'have fun'.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="972">
		<line-text>Alcohol is the anesthesia by which we endure the operation of life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="973">
		<line-text>One thing you can give and still keep is your word.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="974">
		<line-text>Cogito cogito ergo cogito sum (I think that I think, therefore I think that I am.)</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="975">
		<line-text>Never play cards with a man called Doc. Never eat at a place called Mom's. Never sleep with a woman whose troubles are worse than your own.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="976">
		<line-text>If what I do prove well, it won't advance.
They'll say it's stolen, or else it was by chance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="977">
		<line-text>Keep your friends close, and your enemies closer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="978">
		<line-text>[Jupiter's] satellites are invisible to the naked eye and therefore can have no influence on the Earth and therefore would be useless and therefore do not exist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="979">
		<line-text>Being kind to your dog doesn't make you a better artist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="980">
		<line-text>There is an alchemy in sorrow. It can be transmuted into wisdom, which, if it does not bring joy, can yet bring happiness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="981">
		<line-text>I refuse to believe that trading recipes is silly. Tunafish casserole is at least as real as corporate stock.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="982">
		<line-text>I don't know the key to success, but the key to failure is to try to please everyone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="983">
		<line-text>Henry James chews more than he bites off.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="984">
		<line-text>If there are no stupid questions, then what kind of questions do stupid people ask? Do they get smart just in time to ask questions?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="985">
		<line-text>Things aren't magically better if that's what you're hoping for. It's not that simple.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="986">
		<line-text>The superior man, when resting in safety, does not forget that danger may come. When in a state of security he does not forget the possibility of ruin. When all is orderly, he does not forget that disorder may come. Thus his person is not endangered, and his States and all their clans are preserved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="987">
		<line-text>If one asks for success and prepares for failure, he will get the situation he has prepared for.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="988">
		<line-text>Quiet and sincere sympathy is often the most welcome and efficient consolation to the afflicted. Said a wise man to one in deep sorrow, &quot;I did not come to comfort you; God only can do that; but I did come to say how deeply and tenderly I feel for you in your affliction&quot;.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="989">
		<line-text>God made Truth with many doors to welcome every believer who knocks on them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="990">
		<line-text>Nietzsche was stupid and abnormal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="991">
		<line-text>It is difficult to make a man miserable while he feels he is worthy of himself and claims kindred to the great God who made him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="992">
		<line-text>Anybody can observe the Sabbath, but making it holy surely takes the rest of the week.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="993">
		<line-text>Be afraid of a gentleman when he is hungry, and of a mean person when his stomach is full.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="994">
		<line-text>To give unto them beauty for ashes, the oil of joy for mourning, the garment of praise for the spirit of heaviness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="995">
		<line-text>A patriot is mocked, scorned and hated; yet when his cause succeeds, all men will join him, for then it costs nothing to be a patriot.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="996">
		<line-text>He had heard people speak contemptuously of money: he wondered if they had ever tried to do without it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="997">
		<line-text>I would never die for my beliefs because I might be wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="998">
		<line-text>Price is what you pay. Value is what you get.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="999">
		<line-text>In Hollywood, an equitable divorce settlement means each party getting fifty percent of publicity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1000">
		<line-text>Don't join the book burners. Don't think you're going to conceal faults by concealing evidence that they ever existed. Don't be afraid to go in your library and read every book...</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1001">
		<line-text>On going to war over religion: You're basically killing each other to prove who's got the better imaginary friend.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1002">
		<line-text>He who abandons the field is beaten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1003">
		<line-text>Under certain circumstances, profanity provides a relief denied even to prayer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1004">
		<line-text>Hatred does not cease in this world by hating, but by not hating; this is an eternal truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1005">
		<line-text>Everything beautiful has its moment, and then passes away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1006">
		<line-text>Advertising is a valuable economic factor because it is the cheapest way of selling goods, particularly if the goods are worthless.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1007">
		<line-text>Being tired isn't the same as being rich, but most times it's close enough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1008">
		<line-text>It drives on with a courage which is stronger than the storm. It drives on with a mercy which does not quail in the presence of death. It drives on as proof, a symbol, a testimony that man is created in the image of God and that valour and virtue have not perished in the British race.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1009">
		<line-text>Do not fear going forward slowly; fear only to stand still.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1010">
		<line-text>The great danger... in believing yourself especially chosen is that it becomes easy to view those who are not your people as God's especially unchosen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1011">
		<line-text>Every single one of us can do things that no one else can do -- can love things that no one else can love. We are like violins. We can be used for doorstops, or we can make music. You know what to do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1012">
		<line-text>Your best shot at happiness, self-worth and personal satisfaction - the things that constitute real success - is not in earning as much as you can but in performing as well as you can something that you consider worthwhile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1013">
		<line-text>Modesty in an actor is as fake as passion in a call girl.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1014">
		<line-text>How hard it is for women to keep counsel!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1015">
		<line-text>A man with a watch knows what time it is. A man with two watches is never sure.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1016">
		<line-text>Be not afraid of life. Believe that life is worth living, and your belief will help create the fact.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1017">
		<line-text>Baloney is the lie laid on so thick you hate it. Blarney is flattery laid on so thin you love it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1018">
		<line-text>There is no sadder sight than a young pessimist, except an old optimist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1019">
		<line-text>He was so benevolent, so merciful a man that he would have held an umbrella over a duck in a shower of rain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1020">
		<line-text>That was the worst part about having cancer, sometimes: The physical evidence of disease separates you from other people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1021">
		<line-text>A child's education should begin at least one hundred years before he is born.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1022">
		<line-text>I believe in God, only I spell it Nature.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1023">
		<line-text>Reflect on your present blessings, of which every man has many; not on your past misfortunes, of which all men have some.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1024">
		<line-text>Last words are for fools who haven't said enough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1025">
		<line-text>Every creator painfully experiences the chasm between his inner vision and its ultimate expression.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1026">
		<line-text>Don't flail against the world, use it. Flexibility is the operative principle in the art of war.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1027">
		<line-text>Money is a terrible master but an excellent servant.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1028">
		<line-text>My favorite animal is steak.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1029">
		<line-text>There is a paradise that can be found
A better life to bring us round
And all we really need to do
Is see the world like lovers do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1030">
		<line-text>I believe there is no source of deception in the investigation of nature which can compare with a fixed belief that certain kinds of phenomena are impossible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1031">
		<line-text>Once, during Prohibition, I was forced to live for days on nothing but food and water.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1032">
		<line-text>Myself, I prefer life without fires, without nocturnal panics.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1033">
		<line-text>Pray as if everything depended upon God and work as if everything depended upon man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1034">
		<line-text>I'm out of ammunition on this.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1035">
		<line-text>To me, boxing is like a ballet, except there's no music, no choreography, and the dancers hit each other.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1036">
		<line-text>Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1037">
		<line-text>I'd marry again if I found a man who had fifteen million dollars, would sign over half to me, and guarantee that he'd be dead within a year.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1038">
		<line-text>Being in politics is like being a football coach. You have to be smart enough to understand the game, and dumb enough to think it's important.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1039">
		<line-text>NOUMENON, n. That which exists, as distinguished from that which merely seems to exist, the latter being a phenomenon. The noumenon is a bit difficult to locate; it can be apprehended only be a process of reasoning -- which is a phenomenon. Nevertheless, the discovery and exposition of noumena offer a rich field for what Lewes calls &quot;the endless variety and excitement of philosophic thought.&quot; Hurrah (therefore) for the noumenon!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1040">
		<line-text>I believe, and I say it is true Democratic feeling, that all the measures of the government are directed to the purpose of making the rich richer and the poor poorer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1041">
		<line-text>I like the night. Without the dark, we'd never see the stars.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1042">
		<line-text>We could call order by the name of God, but it would be an impersonal God. There's not much personal about the laws of physics.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1043">
		<line-text>Public display of mourning is no longer made by people of fashion, although some flashier kinds of widows may insist on sleeping with only black men during the first year after the death.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1044">
		<line-text>Nothing is at last sacred but the integrity of our own mind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1045">
		<line-text>Love sought is good, but given unsought is better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1046">
		<line-text>They say such nice things about people at their funerals that it makes me sad to realize that I'm going to miss mine by just a few days.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1047">
		<line-text>If a little knowledge is dangerous, where is the man who has so much as to be out of danger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1048">
		<line-text>If there is a sin against life, it consist perhaps not so much in despairing of life as hoping for another life and in eluding the implacable grandeur of this life. Albert Camus</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1049">
		<line-text>Well, I can't eat muffins in an agitated manner. The butter would probably get on my cuffs. One should always eat muffins quite calmly. It is the only way to eat them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1050">
		<line-text>No man is demolished but by himself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1051">
		<line-text>I am the only truth I know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1052">
		<line-text>It is the dull man who is always sure, and the sure man who is always dull.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1053">
		<line-text>The play's the thing
Wherein I'll catch the conscience of the king.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1054">
		<line-text>Most conversations are simply monologues delivered in the presence of witnesses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1055">
		<line-text>Social engaged intellectuals must accept reality as they found it and shape it toward positive social goals, not stand aside in self-righteous isolation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1056">
		<line-text>If you're afraid to let someone else see your weakness, take heart: Nobody's perfect. Besides, your attempts to hide your flaws don't work as well as you think they do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1057">
		<line-text>Freedom of the press is limited to those who own one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1058">
		<line-text>To want to be what one can be is purpose in life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1059">
		<line-text>I see music as the augmentation of a split second of time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1060">
		<line-text>George Bush doesn't care about black people.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1061">
		<line-text>The past is a source of knowledge, and the future is a source of hope. Love of the past implies faith in the future.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1062">
		<line-text>He that is not open to conviction, is not qualified for discussion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1063">
		<line-text>Don't be afraid to see what you see.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1064">
		<line-text>Call home thy ancient thoughts from banishment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1065">
		<line-text>The fox has many tricks. The hedgehog has but one. But that is the best of all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1066">
		<line-text>But, my dearest Agathon, it is truth which you cannot contradict; you can without any difficulty contradict Socrates.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1067">
		<line-text>Prayer indeed is good, but while calling on the gods a man should himself lend a hand.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1068">
		<line-text>He liked the idea of coffee quite a lot—a warm drink that gave you energy and had been for centuries associated with sophisticates and intellectuals. But coffee itself tasted to him like caffeinated stomach bile.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1069">
		<line-text>We do not believe if we do not live and work according to our belief.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1070">
		<line-text>If the person you are talking to doesn't appear to be listening, be patient. It may simply be that he has a small piece of fluff in his ear.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1071">
		<line-text>RED-SKIN, n. A North American Indian, whose skin is not red -- at least not on the outside.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1072">
		<line-text>Hope is tomorrow's veneer over today's disappointment.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1073">
		<line-text>You cannot strengthen the weak by weakening the strong.
You cannot help small men by tearing down big men.
You cannot help the poor by destroying the rich.
You cannot lift the wage earner by pulling down the wage payer.
You cannot keep out of trouble by spending more than your income.
You cannot further the brotherhood of man by inciting class hatreds.
You cannot establish security on borrowed money.
You cannot build character and courage by taking away a man's initiative and independence.
You cannot help men permanently by doing for them what they could and should do for themselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1074">
		<line-text>If you're hurting, you need to help somebody else ease their hurt. If you're in pain, help somebody else's pain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1075">
		<line-text>A great deal of intelligence can be invested in ignorance when the need for illusion is deep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1076">
		<line-text>Women are the only oppressed group in our society that lives in intimate association with their opressors.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1077">
		<line-text>I think that little by little I'll be able to solve my problems and survive.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1078">
		<line-text>I am a kind of paranoiac in reverse. I suspect people of plotting to make me happy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1079">
		<line-text>In a mad world only the mad are sane.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1080">
		<line-text>Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1081">
		<line-text>It is better to live richly than to die rich.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1082">
		<line-text>If I were to wish for anything, I should not wish for wealth and power, but for the passionate sense of potential -- for the eye which, ever young and ardent, sees the possible. Pleasure disappoints; possibility never.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1083">
		<line-text>We must respect the other fellow's religion, but only in the sense and to the extent that we respect his theory that his wife is beautiful and his children smart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1084">
		<line-text>I want all hellions to quit puffing that hell fume in God's clean air.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1085">
		<line-text>I do not want people to be agreeable, as it saves me that trouble of liking them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1086">
		<line-text>It's not a 9-5 job. It's an every moment you're awake job because you actually enjoy the work that you're doing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1087">
		<line-text>All that is human must retrograde if it does not advance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1088">
		<line-text>No computer has ever been designed that is ever aware of what it's doing; but most of the time, we aren't either.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1089">
		<line-text>All changes, even the most longed for, have their melancholy; for what we leave behind us is a part of ourselves; we must die to one life before we can enter another.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1090">
		<line-text>The world is full of suffering but it is also full of people overcoming it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1091">
		<line-text>The camera's only job is to get out of the way of making photographs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1092">
		<line-text>I have never thought of writing for reputation and honor. What I have in my heart must come out; that is the reason why I compose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1093">
		<line-text>If you want to make people weep, you must weep yourself. If you want to make people laugh, your face must remain serious.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1094">
		<line-text>What would the world do without tea? - how did it exist? I am glad I was not born before tea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1095">
		<line-text>I am entirely certain that twenty years from now we will look back at education as it is practiced in most schools today and wonder that we could have tolerated anything so primitive.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1096">
		<line-text>Wars teach us not to love our enemies but to hate our allies.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1097">
		<line-text>A cold in the head cause less suffering than an idea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1098">
		<line-text>Man's greatest joy is to slay his enemy, plunder his riches, ride his steeds, see the tears of his loved ones and embrace his women.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1099">
		<line-text>Patriotism is the willingness to kill and be killed for trivial reasons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1100">
		<line-text>Hatred is a boomerang which is sure to hit you harder than the one at whom you throw it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1101">
		<line-text>COURT FOOL, n. The plaintiff.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1102">
		<line-text>To save time is to lengthen life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1103">
		<line-text>Punctuality is the virtue of the bored.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1104">
		<line-text>If the world were a logical place, men would ride side saddle.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1105">
		<line-text>It is practically impossible to teach good programming style to students that have had prior exposure to BASIC; as potential programmers they are mentally mutilated beyond hope of regeneration.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1106">
		<line-text>One of the greatest creations of the human mind is the art of reviewing books without having read them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1107">
		<line-text>Don't use a big word where a diminutive one will suffice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1108">
		<line-text>For what do we live, but to make sport for our neighbours, and laugh at them in our turn?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1109">
		<line-text>What a mistake to suppose that the passions are strongest in youth! The passions are not stronger, but the control over them is weaker! They are more easily excited, they are more violent and apparent; but they have less energy, less durability, less intense and concentrated power than in the maturer life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1110">
		<line-text>The rich are the scum of the earth in every country.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1111">
		<line-text>Once you can laugh at your own weaknesses, you can move forward. Comedy breaks down walls. It opens up people. If you're good, you can fill up those openings with something positive. Maybe... combat some of the ugliness in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1112">
		<line-text>The most important work you and I will ever do will be within the walls of our own homes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1113">
		<line-text>A joy that's shared is a joy made double.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1114">
		<line-text>I'd like to hate you, but you're really nice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1115">
		<line-text>I have a perfect cure for a sore throat: cut it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1116">
		<line-text>Man's capacity for justice makes democracy possible, but man's inclination to injustice makes democracy necessary.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1117">
		<line-text>You can't leave footprints in the sands of time by sitting on your butt. And who wants to leave buttprints in the sands of time?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1118">
		<line-text>I deal with stress in two ways because there are two kinds of stress. There's stress that you can take care of and there's stress that you can't. The first one, I take care of it as fast as possible, because putting it off always makes it worse. Things that I can't fix? I think about the fact that I can't fix them. I think about why I can't fix them and I come to terms with the fact that this is a problem that I'm not going to overcome and that the world is not a wish granting factory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1119">
		<line-text>Words are, of course, the most powerful drug used by mankind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1120">
		<line-text>America has never been an empire. We may be the only great power in history that had the chance, and refused – preferring greatness to power and justice to glory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1121">
		<line-text>Is sloppiness in speech caused by ignorance or apathy? I don't know and I don't care.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1122">
		<line-text>We are shaped by our thoughts; we become what we think. When the mind is pure, joy follows like a shadow that never leaves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1123">
		<line-text>For a successful technology, reality must take precedence over public relations, for Nature cannot be fooled.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1124">
		<line-text>The mystery of government is not how Washington works but how to make it stop.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1125">
		<line-text>A child's education should begin at least one hundred years before he is born.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1126">
		<line-text>Friends should always tell you the truth. But please don’t.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1127">
		<line-text>&quot;Know thyself,&quot; said the old philosopher, &quot;improve thyself,&quot; saith the new. Our great object in time is not to waste our passions and gifts on the things external that we must leave behind, but that we cultivate within us all that we can carry into the eternal progress beyond.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1128">
		<line-text>Eighty percent of success is showing up.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1129">
		<line-text>He who tells a lie is not sensible of how great a task he undertakes; for he must be forced to invent twenty more to maintain that one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1130">
		<line-text>There is... nothing greater than touching the shore after crossing some great body of water knowing that I've done it with my own two arms and legs.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1131">
		<line-text>Words are the litmus paper of the minds. If you find yourself in the power of someone who will use the word &quot;commence&quot; in cold blood, go somewhere else very quickly. But if they say &quot;Enter&quot;, don't stop to pack.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1132">
		<line-text>Good people are good because they've come to wisdom through failure.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1133">
		<line-text>Few great men could pass Personnel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1134">
		<line-text>The history of ideas is the history of the grudges of solitary men.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1135">
		<line-text>I daresay one profits more by the mistakes one makes off one's own bat than by doing the right thing on somebody's else advice.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1136">
		<line-text>Web standards keep you out of the dustbin of history.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1137">
		<line-text>Some have half-baked ideas because their ideals are not heated up enough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1138">
		<line-text>No one is useless in this world who lightens the burdens of another.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1139">
		<line-text>Truth is the daughter of time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1140">
		<line-text>History does not record anywhere at any time a religion that has any rational basis. Religion is a crutch for people not strong enough to stand up to the unknown without help. But, like dandruff, most people do have a religion and spend time and money on it and seem to derive considerable pleasure from fiddling with it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1141">
		<line-text>If art is to nourish the roots of our culture, society must set the artist free to follow his vision wherever it takes him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1142">
		<line-text>Dreams, goals, ambitions - these are the stuff man uses for fuel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1143">
		<line-text>If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1144">
		<line-text>When defeat comes, accept it as a signal that your plans are not sound, rebuild those plans, and set sail once more toward your coveted goal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1145">
		<line-text>Where humor is concerned there are no standards - no one can say what is good or bad, although you can be sure that everyone will.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1146">
		<line-text>If people only knew how hard I work to gain my mastery, it wouldn't seem so wonderful at all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1147">
		<line-text>Cowards die many times before their deaths; the valiant never taste of death but once.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1148">
		<line-text>Even on the most exalted throne in the world we are only sitting on our own bottom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1149">
		<line-text>In the depth of winter, I learned that within me there lay an invincible summer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1150">
		<line-text>Ultimate excellence lies not in winning every battle, but in defeating the enemy without ever fighting.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1151">
		<line-text>In a networked world, trust is the most important currency.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1152">
		<line-text>Everything was beautiful and nothing hurt.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1153">
		<line-text>The illiterate of the future will not be the person who cannot read. It will be the person who does not know how to learn.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1154">
		<line-text>The generation of random numbers is too important to be left to chance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1155">
		<line-text>Love flies, runs, and rejoices; it is free and nothing can hold it back.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1156">
		<line-text>They certainly give very strange names to diseases.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1157">
		<line-text>There is only one way to happiness and that is to cease worrying about things which are beyond the power of our will.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1158">
		<line-text>California is a fine place to live--if you happen to be an orange.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1159">
		<line-text>Give death a better name or die trying.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1160">
		<line-text>&quot;Do you consider yourself a disciplined guy? Do you get up every day and `go to work'?&quot;
&quot;Well, yeah. I try to get up every day.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1161">
		<line-text>The only people who seem to have nothing to do with the education of the children are the parents.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1162">
		<line-text>When you don't have any money, the problem is food. When you have money, it's sex. When you have both, it's health. If everything is simply jake, then you're frightened of death.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1163">
		<line-text>Castles in the air - they are so easy to take refuge in. And so easy to build, too.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1164">
		<line-text>If a man empties his purse into his head no one can take it away from him. An investment in knowledge always pays the best interest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1165">
		<line-text>The only real possession you'll ever have is your character.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1166">
		<line-text>PICKANINNY, n. The young of the _Procyanthropos_, or _Americanus dominans_. It is small, black and charged with political fatalities.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1167">
		<line-text>Half of analysis is anal.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1168">
		<line-text>It is not necessary to understand things in order to argue about them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1169">
		<line-text>I know not, sir, whether Bacon wrote the works of Shakespeare, but if he did not it seems to me that he missed the opportunity of his life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1170">
		<line-text>It is better to think too much, than to think too little</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1171">
		<line-text>Who is better, they who promote truth over happiness, or happiness over truth?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1172">
		<line-text>Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1173">
		<line-text>Old friends become bitter enemies on a sudden for toys and small offenses.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1174">
		<line-text>FOREORDINATION, n. This looks like an easy word to define, but when I consider that pious and learned theologians have spent long lives in explaining it, and written libraries to explain their explanations; when I remember the nations have been divided and bloody battles caused by the difference between foreordination and predestination, and that millions of treasure have been expended in the effort to prove and disprove its compatibility with freedom of the will and the efficacy of prayer, praise, and a religious life, -- recalling these awful facts in the history of the word, I stand appalled before the mighty problem of its signification, abase my spiritual eyes, fearing to contemplate its portentous magnitude, reverently uncover and humbly refer it to His Eminence Cardinal Gibbons and His Grace Bishop Potter.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1175">
		<line-text>Every day people are straying away from the church and going back to God.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1176">
		<line-text>I love deadlines. I love the whooshing sound they make as they fly by.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1177">
		<line-text>Free advice is worth the price.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1178">
		<line-text>Overlook our deeds, since you know that crime was absent from our inclination.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1179">
		<line-text>A lot of people mistake a short memory for a clear conscience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1180">
		<line-text>Actuated by the most glorious cause that mankind ever fought in, I am determined to defend this post to the very last extremity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1181">
		<line-text>Nothing is as frustrating as arguing with someone who knows what he's talking about.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1182">
		<line-text>The true measure of a man is how he treats someone who can do him absolutely no good.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1183">
		<line-text>I am not part of the problem. I am a Republican.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1184">
		<line-text>When you tell the truth, people listen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1185">
		<line-text>Do you know, my son, with what little understanding the world is ruled?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1186">
		<line-text>One must be a wise reader to quote wisely and well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1187">
		<line-text>The average person thinks he isn't.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1188">
		<line-text>A child of my own! Oh, no, no, no! Let my flesh perish with me, and let me not transmit to anyone the boredom and ignominiousness of life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1189">
		<line-text>The illusion that times that were are better than those that are, has probably pervaded all ages.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1190">
		<line-text>Here, you can't live as you like - in any way or circumstance. You're like a bit out of those coloured mosaics in the hall, you have to fit in your own set, fit into your own pattern, because you're put there from the first. But you don't want to be like a fixed bit of a mosaic - you want to fuse into life, and melt and mix with the rest of folk, to have some things burned out of you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1191">
		<line-text>Although prepared for martyrdom, I preferred that it be postponed.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1192">
		<line-text>&quot;Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak, Courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1193">
		<line-text>Barnum was wrong - it's more like every 30 seconds.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1194">
		<line-text>I am as vulnerable and fragile as it is possible to be. I am shredded to the core. I am at the point where I am stripped bare.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1195">
		<line-text>Of course it's possible to love a human being if you don't know them too well.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1196">
		<line-text>Nature is earlier than man, but man is earlier than natural science.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1197">
		<line-text>Keep writing. Keep doing it and doing it. Even in the moments when it's so hurtful to think about writing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1198">
		<line-text>When you have too much month for you paycheck, then what you need to do is realize that there is abundance all around you and focus on the abundance and not your lack and as night follows day abundance will come to you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1199">
		<line-text>No one can have a higher opinion of him than I have - and I think he is a dirty little beast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1200">
		<line-text>Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art of all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1201">
		<line-text>We have come through a strange cycle in programming, starting with the creation of programming itself as a human activity. Executives with the tiniest smattering of knowledge assume that anyone can write a program, and only now are programmers beginning to win their battle for recognition as true professionals. Not just anyone, with any background, or any training, can do a fine job of programming. Programmers know this, but then why is it that they think that anyone picked off the street can do documentation? One has only to spend an hour looking at papers written by graduate students to realize the extent to which the ability to communicate is not universally held. And so, when we speak about computer program documentation, we are not speaking about the psychology of computer programming at all - except insofar as programmers have the illusion that anyone can do a good job of documentation, provided he is not smart enough to be a programmer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1202">
		<line-text>We judge ourselves by what we are capable of doing, while others judge us by what we have already done.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1203">
		<line-text>I was seldom able to see an opportunity until it had ceased to be one.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1204">
		<line-text>I've yet to be on a campus where most women weren't worrying about some aspect of combining marriage, children, and a career. I've yet to find one where many men were worrying about the same thing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1205">
		<line-text>Think only of the past as its remembrance gives you pleasure.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1206">
		<line-text>When we treat man as he is, we make him worse than he is; when we treat him as if he already were what he potentially could be, we make him what he should be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1207">
		<line-text>A pessimist is a man who has been compelled to live with an optimist.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1208">
		<line-text>When nothing is sure, everything is possible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1209">
		<line-text>Charm is the quality in others that makes us more satisfied with ourselves.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1210">
		<line-text>He attacked everything in life with a mix of extraordinary genius and naive incompetence, and it was often difficult to tell which was which.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1211">
		<line-text>Better to reign in Hell, than serve in Heav'n.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1212">
		<line-text>Convictions are prisons.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1213">
		<line-text>In the career of glory one gains many things; the gout and medals, a pension and rheumatism....And also frozen feet, an arm or leg the less, a bullet lodged between two bones which the surgeon cannot extract....all of these fatigues experienced in your youth, you pay for when you grow old. Because one has suffered in years gone by, it is necessary to suffer more, which does not seem exactly fair.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1214">
		<line-text>Early civilizations complained about still earlier ones, much as we do about both</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1215">
		<line-text>You cannot do wrong without suffering wrong.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1216">
		<line-text>I don't know half of you half as well as I should like; and I like less than half of you half as well as you deserve.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1217">
		<line-text>Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1218">
		<line-text>I always turn to the sports pages first, which record people's accomplishments. The front page has nothing but man's failures.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1219">
		<line-text>I keep pointing at the child; they keep staring at my finger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1220">
		<line-text>There is no being of any race who, if he finds the proper guide, cannot attain to virtue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1221">
		<line-text>O, that this too too solid flesh would melt,
Thaw and resolve itself into a dew!
Or that the Everlasting had not fix'd
His canon 'gainst self-slaughter! O God! God!
How weary, stale, flat, and unprofitable
Seem to me all the uses of this world!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1222">
		<line-text>Modesty is an excuse for sloppiness, laziness, self- indulgence; small ambitions evoke small efforts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1223">
		<line-text>The artist, depicting man disdainful of the storm and stress of life, is no less reconciling and healing than the poet who, while endowing Nature and Humanity, rejoices in its measureless superiority to human passions and human sorrows.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1224">
		<line-text>Whatever limits us, we call Fate.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1225">
		<line-text>The first thing you lose on a diet is brain mass.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1226">
		<line-text>If you want to know how a man stands, go among the people who are in his same business.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1227">
		<line-text>It is far better to be silent than merely to increase the quantity of bad books.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1228">
		<line-text>Any life, no matter how long and complex it may be, is made up of a single moment - the moment in which a man finds out, once and for all, who he is.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1229">
		<line-text>The size of your audience doesn't matter. What's important is that your audience is listening.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1230">
		<line-text>I was eyes to the blind, and feet was I to the lame.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1231">
		<line-text>The ultimate measure of a man is not where he stands in moments of comfort and convenience, but where he stands at times of challenge and controversy.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1232">
		<line-text>The life of man is the true romance, which when it is valiantly conduced, will yield the imagination a higher joy than any fiction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1233">
		<line-text>You can’t argue with all of the fools in the world. It’s easier to let them have their way, then trick them when they’re not paying attention.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1234">
		<line-text>Man shall not live by bread alone.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1235">
		<line-text>It is unbecoming for young men to utter maxims.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1236">
		<line-text>The covetous man is ever in want.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1237">
		<line-text>No matter what we do, we are always going to have Us versus Them moments. We can separate, yell or talk to each other and draw a truce. You won't agree with everybody. It doesn't mean the other person is an idiot.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1238">
		<line-text>Everything has its wonders, even darkness and silence, and I learn, whatever state I am in, therein to be content.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1239">
		<line-text>The harder you work, the harder it is to surrender.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1240">
		<line-text>There would not be so many open mouths if there were not so many open ears.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1241">
		<line-text>Under all speech that is good for anything there lies a silence that is better. Silence is deep as Eternity; speech is shallow as Time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1242">
		<line-text>A prudent question is one half of wisdom.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1243">
		<line-text>I enjoy being a highly overpaid actor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1244">
		<line-text>The resounding echo of the mortal coil, echoes in the ears of those who are unprepared for it. To some, it sounds like a symphony - to others, a death toll.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1245">
		<line-text>Truth springs from argument amongst friends.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1246">
		<line-text>I don't care what is written about me so long as it isn't true.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1247">
		<line-text>We never fully grasp the import of any true statement until we have a clear notion of what the opposite untrue statement would be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1248">
		<line-text>Cabbage: A familiar kitchen-garden vegetable about as large and wise as a man's head.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1249">
		<line-text>Few things are harder to put up with than the annoyance of a good example.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1250">
		<line-text>Love has taught us that love does not consist in gazing at each other but in looking outward together in the same direction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1251">
		<line-text>Great spirits have always found violent opposition from mediocrities. The latter cannot understand it when a man does not thoughtlessly submit to hereditary prejudices but honestly and courageously uses his intelligence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1252">
		<line-text>The trouble with most folks isn't so much their ignorance. It's know'n so many things that ain't so.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1253">
		<line-text>Mediocrity is not allowed to poets, either by the gods or man.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1254">
		<line-text>Perfection of moral virtue does not wholly take away the passions, but regulates them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1255">
		<line-text>Self-respect: the secure feeling that no one, as yet, is suspicious.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1256">
		<line-text>Idealism increases in direct proportion to one's distance from the problem.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1257">
		<line-text>Don't use words too big for the subject. Don't say 'infinitely' when you mean 'very'; otherwise you'll have no word left when you want to talk about something really infinite.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1258">
		<line-text>All philosophies, if you ride them, are nonsense, but some are greater nonsense than others.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1259">
		<line-text>McCabe's Law: Nobody _has_ to do _anything_.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1260">
		<line-text>The wisdom of the wise, and the experience of ages, may be preserved by quotation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1261">
		<line-text>Do not let people put you down. Believe in yourself and stand for yourself and trust yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1262">
		<line-text>Immorality: the morality of those who are having a better time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1263">
		<line-text>It wasn't until late in life that I discovered how easy it is to say 'I don't know'.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1264">
		<line-text>I am a man: I hold that nothing human is alien to me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1265">
		<line-text>It is in our idleness, in our dreams, that the submerged truth sometimes comes to the top.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1266">
		<line-text>The United States can't be so fixed on our desire to preserve the rights of ordinary Americans...</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1267">
		<line-text>The better part of valor is discretion, in the which better part I have saved my life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1268">
		<line-text>You should pray for a sound mind in a sound body.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1269">
		<line-text>If you wish to know what a man is, place him in authority.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1270">
		<line-text>There is no glory in otustripping donkeys.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1271">
		<line-text>I like to play saxophone because you don't inhale.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1272">
		<line-text>A coward is incapable of exhibiting love; it is the prerogative of the brave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1273">
		<line-text>Having the fewest wants, I am nearest to the gods.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1274">
		<line-text>An investment in knowledge always pays the best interest.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1275">
		<line-text>There is an alchemy in sorrow. It can be transmuted into wisdom, which, if it does not bring joy, can yet bring happiness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1276">
		<line-text>Time is at once the most valuable and the most perishable of all our possessions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1277">
		<line-text>Liberty cannot be established without morality, nor morality without faith.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1278">
		<line-text>It takes courage to grow up and turn out to be who you really are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1279">
		<line-text>Fortune helps the brave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1280">
		<line-text>Death can sneak up on you like a silent kitten, surprising you with it's touch and you have a right to act surprised. Other times death stomps in the front door, unwanted and unannounced, and makes it's noisy way to your seat on the sofa.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1281">
		<line-text>Peace of mind is that mental condition in which you have accepted the worst.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1282">
		<line-text>The opportunity for brotherhood presents itself every time you meet a human being.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1283">
		<line-text>Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1284">
		<line-text>A citizen of America will cross the ocean to fight for democracy, but won't cross the street to vote in a national election.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1285">
		<line-text>Research is the process of going up alleys to see if they are blind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1286">
		<line-text>Be courteous to all, but intimate with few; and let those few be well tried before you give them your confidence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1287">
		<line-text>We have to remember that what we observe is not nature in itself but nature exposed to our method of questioning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1288">
		<line-text>Never go out to meet trouble. If you will just sit still, nine cases out of ten someone will intercept it before it reaches you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1289">
		<line-text>Behind the phony tinsel of Hollywood lies the real tinsel.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1290">
		<line-text>It is healthier to see the good points of others than to analyze our own bad ones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1291">
		<line-text>Prove all things; hold fast that which is good.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1292">
		<line-text>It takes a lot of money to look as cheap as I do.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1293">
		<line-text>Truth has no special time of its own. Its hour is now -- always.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1294">
		<line-text>There are two ways of disliking poetry; one way is to dislike it, the other is to read Pope.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1295">
		<line-text>No man is exempt from saying silly things; the mischief is to say them deliberately.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1296">
		<line-text>There is nothing so bitter that a patient mind cannot find some solace in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1297">
		<line-text>Strive for excellence, not perfection.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1298">
		<line-text>Autumn is a second spring when every leaf is a flower.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1299">
		<line-text>Love is a dirty trick played on us to achieve the continuation of the species.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1300">
		<line-text>Your child can’t hurt you if you don’t accept the hurt. Let it go.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1301">
		<line-text>If you don't have a common set of values in life, you're gonna have a lot of trouble. Your values must be alike.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1302">
		<line-text>Neither man or nation can exist without a sublime idea.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1303">
		<line-text>Drawing on my fine command of the English language, I said nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1304">
		<line-text>The closer you are to your money, the better off you'll be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1305">
		<line-text>Art is making something out of nothing and selling it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1306">
		<line-text>[M]aybe the most any of us can expect of ourselves isn't perfection but progress.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1307">
		<line-text>I have lived some thirty years on this planet and I have yet to hear the first syllable of valuable or even earnest advice from my seniors.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1308">
		<line-text>God is really only another artist, he made the elephant, giraffe and cat. He has no real style but keeps trying new ideas.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1309">
		<line-text>But then there's a moment like tonight, a profound and transcendent experience, the feeling as if a door has opened, and it's all because of that instrument, that incredible, magical instrument.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1310">
		<line-text>In order to be truly happy, you must live along with, and you must stand for something larger than yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1311">
		<line-text>Most people never run far enough on their first wind to find out they’ve got a second. Give your dreams all you’ve got and you’ll be amazed at the energy that comes out of you!!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1312">
		<line-text>Experience suggests it doesn't matter so much how you got here, as what you do after you arrive.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1313">
		<line-text>Never judge a book by its movie.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1314">
		<line-text>If you don't like your own character there may be a new one ready-made and waiting for you. The snake sheds its skin with impunity, relying on the same nature which you rely on.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1315">
		<line-text>All the knowledge in the world is found within you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1316">
		<line-text>What luck for rulers that men do not think.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1317">
		<line-text>Age to me means nothing. I can't get old; I'm working. I was old when I was twenty-one and out of work. As long as you're working, you stay young. When I'm in front of an audience, all that love and vitality sweeps over me and I forget my age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1318">
		<line-text>Eye contact is the best accessory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1319">
		<line-text>It doesn't matter that Cathy was what I have called a monster. Perhaps we can't understand Cathy, but on the other hand we are capable of many things in all directions, of great virtues and great sins. And who in his mind has not probed the black water?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1320">
		<line-text>For what is it to die but to stand naked in the wind and to melt into the sun?
And what is it to cease breathing, but to free the breath from its restless tides, that it may rise and expand and seek God unencumbered?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1321">
		<line-text>Enjoy present pleasures in such a way as not to injure future ones.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1322">
		<line-text>Whatever my individual desires were to be free, I was not alone. There were many others who felt the same way.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1323">
		<line-text>I have never found, in a long experience of politics, that criticism is ever inhibited by ignorance.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1324">
		<line-text>The person who knows &quot;how&quot; will always have a job. The person who knows &quot;why&quot; will always be his boss.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1325">
		<line-text>To be feared is much safer then to be loved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1326">
		<line-text>The stronger must dominate and not blend with the weaker, thus sacrificing his own greatness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1327">
		<line-text>They have computers, and they may have other weapons of mass destruction.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1328">
		<line-text>He who can take no interest in what is small will take false interest in what is great.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1329">
		<line-text>Life is something that happens when you can't get to sleep.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1330">
		<line-text>I'm too shy to express my sexual needs except over the phone to people I don't know.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1331">
		<line-text>Treasure the love you receive above all. It will survive long after your gold and good health have vanished.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1332">
		<line-text>That's it baby, when you got it, flaunt it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1333">
		<line-text>Anybody can sympathise with the suffering of a friend, but it requires a very fine nature to sympathise with a friend's success.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1334">
		<line-text>He draweth out the thread of his verbosity finer than the staple of his argument.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1335">
		<line-text>All paid jobs absorb and degrade the mind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1336">
		<line-text>Procrastination is the thief of time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1337">
		<line-text>The right to life is the source of all rights--and the right to property is their only implementation. Without property rights, no other rights are possible. Since man has to sustain his life by his own effort, the man who has no right to the product of his effort has no means to sustain his life. The man who produces while others dispose of his product, is a slave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1338">
		<line-text>Science may have found a cure for most evils; but it has found no remedy for the worst of them all- the apathy of human beings.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1339">
		<line-text>Enough organization, enough lists and we think we can control the uncontrollable.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1340">
		<line-text>Anything you could ever want or be you already have and are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1341">
		<line-text>Where religion is trivialized, one is unlikely to find persecution.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1342">
		<line-text>Nothing is more conducive to peace of mind than not having any opinions at all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1343">
		<line-text>Emile Zola was a poor student at his school at Aix. We are all so different largely because we all have different combinations of intelligences. If we recognize this, I think we will have at least a better chance of dealing appropriately with many problems that we face in the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1344">
		<line-text>You always second guess yourself. Just think of all the time you'd save if you just trusted yourself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1345">
		<line-text>It is cruel to discover one's mediocrity only when it is too late.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1346">
		<line-text>Clearly he had his own strange way of judging things. I suspect he acquired it from the gospels.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1347">
		<line-text>All wars are civil wars, because all men are brothers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1348">
		<line-text>To punish the oppressors of humanity is clemency; to forgive them is cruelty.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1349">
		<line-text>BLACKGUARD, n. A man whose qualities, prepared for display like a box of berries in a market -- the fine ones on top -- have been opened on the wrong side. An inverted gentleman.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1350">
		<line-text>It is perhaps a more fortunate destiny to have a taste for collecting shells than to be born a millionaire.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1351">
		<line-text>As part of it's 'Astro' program LAPD helicopters maintain an average nineteen-hours-per-day vigil over 'high crime areas', tactically coordinated to patrol car forces, and exceeding even the British Army's aerial surveillance of Belfast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1352">
		<line-text>A conscience is what hurts when all your other parts feel so good.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1353">
		<line-text>Anxiety is interest paid on trouble before it is due.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1354">
		<line-text>If we are going to stick to this damned quantum-jumping, then I regret that I ever had anything to do with quantum theory.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1355">
		<line-text>Praise will come to those whose kindness leaves you without debt.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1356">
		<line-text>I object to violence because when it appears to do good, the good is only temporary; the evil it does is permanent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1357">
		<line-text>We need quiet time to examine our lives openly and honestly. . . spending quiet time alone gives your mind an opportunity to renew itself and create order.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1358">
		<line-text>Wit ought to be a glorious treat, like caviar. Never spread it about like marmalade.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1359">
		<line-text>The secret of success is to do all you can do without thought of success.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1360">
		<line-text>Worry does not empty tomorrow of sorrow - it empties today of strength.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1361">
		<line-text>It's not enough to create magic. You have to create a price for magic, too. You have to create rules.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1362">
		<line-text>Ah, make the most of what we yet may spend, before we too into the dust descend.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1363">
		<line-text>The most extensive computation known has been conducted over the last billion years on a planet-wide scale: it is the evolution of life. The power of this computation is illustrated by the complexity and beauty of its crowning achievement, the human brain.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1364">
		<line-text>The great omission in American life is solitude. . . that zone of time and space, free from the outside pressures, which is the incinerator of the spirit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1365">
		<line-text>I exist as I am, that is enough.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1366">
		<line-text>I was born not knowing and have only had a little time to change that here and there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1367">
		<line-text>In the bleak midwinter Frosty wind made moan, Earth stood hard as iron, Water like a stone; Snow had fallen, snow on snow, Snow on snow, In the bleak midwinter, Long ago.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1368">
		<line-text>Wait for that wisest of all counselors, Time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1369">
		<line-text>Carry the battle to them. Don't let them bring it to you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1370">
		<line-text>The last thing I have to say is that ice is the past tense of water. I've always wanted to write that sentence and now I have.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1371">
		<line-text>A generation which ignores history has no past and no future.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1372">
		<line-text>INSURRECTION, n. An unsuccessful revolution. Disaffection's failure to substitute misrule for bad government.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1373">
		<line-text>Change is the process by which the future invades our lives.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1374">
		<line-text>We have given away far too many freedoms in order to be free. Now it's time to take some back.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1375">
		<line-text>I haven't spoken to my wife in years. I didn't want to interrupt her.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1376">
		<line-text>I always avoid prophesying beforehand, because it is much better policy to prophesy after the event has taken place.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1377">
		<line-text>In certain kinds of writing, particularly in art criticism and literary criticism, it is normal to come across long passages which are almost completely lacking in meaning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1378">
		<line-text>Don't be content by just beating others expectations, beat your own expectations as well. And you should expect nothing less but to win.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1379">
		<line-text>A witty saying proves nothing.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1380">
		<line-text>All great discoveries are made by men whose feelings run ahead of their thinking.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1381">
		<line-text>The opposite of a correct statement is a false statement. But the opposite of a profound truth may well be another profound truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1382">
		<line-text>It is entirely seemly for a young man killed in battle to lie mangled by the bronze spear. In his death all things appear fair. But when dogs shame the gray head and gray chin and nakedness of an old man killed, it is the most piteous thing that happens among wretched mortals.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1383">
		<line-text>The only difference between sex and death is, with death you can do it alone and nobody's going to make fun of you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1384">
		<line-text>I am patient with stupidity, but not with those who are proud of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1385">
		<line-text>Women want mediocre men, and men are working to become as mediocre as possible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1386">
		<line-text>Love cannot survive if you just give it scraps of yourself, scraps of your time, scraps of your thoughts.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1387">
		<line-text>Men are the only animals that devote themselves, day in and day out, to making one another unhappy. It is an art like any other. Its virtuosi are called altruists.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1388">
		<line-text>Not ignorance, but ignorance of ignorance, is the death of knowledge.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1389">
		<line-text>Friendship is constant in all other things
Save in the office and affairs of love:
Therefore all hearts in love use their own tongues;
Let every eye negotiate for itself
And trust no agent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1390">
		<line-text>Try not to become a man of success but rather try to become a man of value.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1391">
		<line-text>The greatest power that a person possesses is the power to choose.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1392">
		<line-text>'Tis the privilege of friendship to talk nonsense, and have her nonsense respected.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1393">
		<line-text>We cannot direct the wind, but we can adjust the sails.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1394">
		<line-text>There is one thing alone
that stands the brunt of life throughout its course:
a quiet conscience.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1395">
		<line-text>Be not so bigoted to any custom as to worship it at the expense of truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1396">
		<line-text>He who receives a benefit should never forget it; he who bestow should never remember it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1397">
		<line-text>Es tan corto el amor, y tan largo el olvido.
(Love is so short, and forgetting is so long.)</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1398">
		<line-text>Someone who expresses a view that is contrary to the view of the overwhelming majority should be allowed to stand undisturbed as a monument to our commitment to free speech.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1399">
		<line-text>Virtue isn't 'better' than vice. It's just different.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1400">
		<line-text>I always have to dream up there against the stars. If I don't dream I will make it, I won't even get close.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1401">
		<line-text>Drink no longer water, but use a little wine for thy stomach's sake.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1402">
		<line-text>There are only two kinds of scholars; those who love ideas and those who hate them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1403">
		<line-text>A bachelor never quite gets ove the idea that he is a thing of beauty and a boy forever.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1404">
		<line-text>I'm going to stay in show business until I'm the last one left.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1405">
		<line-text>It is easier to forgive an enemy than to forgive a friend.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1406">
		<line-text>I am going to Spain to fight an army without a general, and thence to the East to fight a general without an army.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1407">
		<line-text>Never have anything to do with an unlucky place, or an unlucky man. I have seen many clever men, very clever men, who had not shoes to their feet. I never act with them. Their advice sounds very well, but they cannot get on themselves; and if they cannot do good to themselves, how can they do good for me?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1408">
		<line-text>All successful newspapers are ceaselessly querulous and bellicose. They never defend anyone or anything if they can help it; if the job is forced on them, they tackle it by denouncing someone or something else.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1409">
		<line-text>Love will find a lay.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1410">
		<line-text>I saw the angel in the marble and carved until I set him free.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1411">
		<line-text>HYPOCHONDRIASIS, n. Depression of one's own spirits.

Some heaps of trash upon a vacant lot
Where long the village rubbish had been shot
Displayed a sign among the stuff and stumps --
&quot;Hypochondriasis.&quot; It meant The Dumps.
Bogul S. Purvy</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1412">
		<line-text>The future belongs to those who dare.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1413">
		<line-text>What you look like on the outside is not what makes you cool at all. I mean, I had a mullet and wore parachute pants for a long, long time, and I'm doin' okay.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1414">
		<line-text>I never have found the perfect quote. At best I have been able to find a string of quotations which merely circle the ineffable idea I seek to express.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1415">
		<line-text>Our test of truth is a reference to either a present or imagined future majority in favour of our view.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1416">
		<line-text>A man's worst difficulties begin when he is able to do as he likes.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1417">
		<line-text>We all flow from one fountain Soul. All are expressions of one Love. God does not appear, and flow out, only from narrow chinks and round bored wells here and there in favored races and places, but He flows in grand undivided currents, shoreless and boundless over creeds and forms and all kinds of civilizations and peoples and beasts, saturating all and fountainizing all.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1418">
		<line-text>Wisdom is knowledge which has become a part of one's being.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1419">
		<line-text>Brigands demand your money or your life; women require both.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1420">
		<line-text>Love is a gross exaggeration of the difference between one person and everybody else.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1421">
		<line-text>The greatest achievement of the human spirit is to live up to one's opportunities and make the most of one's resources.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1422">
		<line-text>Turn on, tune in and drop out.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1423">
		<line-text>To travel hopefully is a better thing than to arrive.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1424">
		<line-text>The strongest, most generous, and proudest of all virtues is true courage.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1425">
		<line-text>Though the vicious can sometimes pour affliction upon the good, their power is transient and their punishment certain; and that innocence, though oppressed by injustice, shall, supported by patience, finally triumph over misfortune!</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1426">
		<line-text>Life is anything that dies when you stomp on it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1427">
		<line-text>Cease to ask what the morrow will bring forth. And set down as gain each day that Fortune grants.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1428">
		<line-text>Reason and free inquiry are the only effectual agents against error.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1429">
		<line-text>The only time to buy these is on a day with no 'y' in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1430">
		<line-text>Only a man who knows what it is like to be defeated can reach down to the bottom of his soul and come up with the extra ounce of power it takes to win when the match is even.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1431">
		<line-text>Politics is the art of preventing people from sticking their noses in things that are properly their business.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1432">
		<line-text>ENVY, n. Emulation adapted to the meanest capacity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1433">
		<line-text>Never face facts; if you do, you'll never get up in the morning.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1434">
		<line-text>To know is nothing at all; to imagine is everything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1435">
		<line-text>Immature love says, I love you because I need you, mature love says, I need you because I love you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1436">
		<line-text>For if you suffer your people to be ill-educated, and their manners to be corrupted from their infancy, and then punish them for those crimes to which their first education disposed them, what else is to be concluded from this, but that you first make thieves and then punish them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1437">
		<line-text>The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious.
It is the source of all art and science.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1438">
		<line-text>Be generous, be delicate, and always pursue the prize.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1439">
		<line-text>You must not think me necessarily foolish because I am facetious, nor will I consider you necessarily wise because you are grave.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1440">
		<line-text>Among those whom I like or admire, I can find no common denominator, but among those whom I love, I can: all of them make me laugh.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1441">
		<line-text>Henry James chews more than he bites off.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1442">
		<line-text>Hamlet: Do you see yonder cloud that's almost in shape of a camel?
Polonius: By the mass, and 'tis like a camel, indeed.
Hamlet: Methinks it is like a weasel.
Polonius: It is backed like a weasel.
Hamlet: Or like a whale?
Polonius: Very like a whale.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1443">
		<line-text>I want to stay as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't see from the center.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1444">
		<line-text>Go often to the house of thy friend; for weeds soon choke up the unused path.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1445">
		<line-text>True happiness is of a retired nature, and an enemy to pomp and noise; it arises, in the first place, from the enjoyment of one's self, and in the next from the friendship and conversation of a few select companions.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1446">
		<line-text>In a heated argument we are apt to lose sight of the truth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1447">
		<line-text>The structure of language determines not only thought, but reality itself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1448">
		<line-text>My grandfather once told me that there are two kinds of people: those who work and those who take the credit. He told me to try to be in the first group; there was less competition there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1449">
		<line-text>A home is not a mere transient shelter: its essence lies in the personalities of the people who live in it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1450">
		<line-text>That's the thing about being a former fat camp champ: when asked if I'd change my past if I could, I always answer no. The pain of being an overweight kid, the humiliation, make you think twice before ever cutting anyone else down.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1451">
		<line-text>Selfishness is not living as one wishes to live. It is asking other people to live as one wishes to live.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1452">
		<line-text>I would rather be exposed to the inconveniences attending too much liberty than to those attending too small a degree of it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1453">
		<line-text>The more laws and order are made prominent,
The more thieves and robbers there will be.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1454">
		<line-text>Acting is the most minor of gifts and not a very high- class way to earn a living. After all, Shirley Temple could do it at the age of four.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1455">
		<line-text>A society grows great when old men plant trees in whose shade they know they shall never sit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1456">
		<line-text>Much speech is one thing, well-timed speech is another.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1457">
		<line-text>Extremists think &quot;communication&quot; means agreeing with them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1458">
		<line-text>There are two sides to every question.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1459">
		<line-text>We cannot defend freedom abroad by deserting it at home.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1460">
		<line-text>Every women needs at least 4 animals. A mink in her closet, a jaguar in her garage, a tiger in her bed, and a jackass that pays for everything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1461">
		<line-text>My vigor, vitality, and cheek repel me. I am the kind of woman I would run from.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1462">
		<line-text>MOUSE, n. An animal which strews its path with fainting women. As in Rome Christians were thrown to the lions, so centuries earlier in Otumwee, the most ancient and famous city of the world, female heretics were thrown to the mice. Jakak-Zotp, the historian, the only Otumwump whose writings have descended to us, says that these martyrs met their death with little dignity and much exertion. He even attempts to exculpate the mice (such is the malice of bigotry) by declaring that the unfortunate women perished, some from exhaustion, some of broken necks from falling over their own feet, and some from lack of restoratives. The mice, he avers, enjoyed the pleasures of the chase with composure. But if &quot;Roman history is nine-tenths lying,&quot; we can hardly expect a smaller proportion of that rhetorical figure in the annals of a people capable of so incredible cruelty to a lovely women; for a hard heart has a false tongue.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1463">
		<line-text>Whosoever shall not fall by the sword or by famine, shall fall by pestilence, so why bother shaving?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1464">
		<line-text>I want to know God's thoughts; the rest are details.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1465">
		<line-text>Literature is a luxury; fiction is a necessity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1466">
		<line-text>The wise man carries his possessions within him.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1467">
		<line-text>You and I have a rendezvous with destiny. We will preserve for our children this, the last best hope of man on earth, or we will sentence them to take the first step into a thousand years of darkness. If we fail, at least let our children and our children's children say of us we justified our brief moment here. We did all that could be done.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1468">
		<line-text>The grandest of all laws is the law of progressive development. Under it, in the wide sweep of things, men grow wiser as they grow older, and societies better.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1469">
		<line-text>I believe that individuals can make a difference in society. Since periods of change such as the present one come so rarely in human history, it is up to each of us to make the best use of our time to help create a happier world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1470">
		<line-text>I believe there is no source of deception in the investigation of nature which can compare with a fixed belief that certain kinds of phenomena are impossible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1471">
		<line-text>A man too busy to take care of his health is like a mechanic too busy to take care of his tools.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1472">
		<line-text>A little government and a little luck are necessary in life, but only a fool trusts either of them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1473">
		<line-text>By trying we can easily learn to endure adversity. Another man's, I mean.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1474">
		<line-text>Consult your dragon before you wager his hide.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1475">
		<line-text>Well, all I know is what I read in the papers.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1476">
		<line-text>The people have always some champion whom they set over them and nurse into greatness...This and no other is the root from which a tyrant springs; when he first appears he is a protector.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1477">
		<line-text>KILL, v.t. To create a vacancy without nominating a successor.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1478">
		<line-text>A large section of the intelligentsia seems wholly devoid of intelligence.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1479">
		<line-text>Follow your passion. Stay true to yourself. Never follow someone else's path unless you're in the woods and you're lost and you see a path. By all means, you should follow that.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1480">
		<line-text>There isn't any virtue where there has never been any temptation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1481">
		<line-text>You have to find a way of working that makes it dead easy to take full advantage of your inspired moments. They never hit at a convenient time, nor do they last long.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1482">
		<line-text>Seeds of faith are always within us; sometimes it takes a crisis to nourish and encourage their growth.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1483">
		<line-text>In business, you must remain unattached to the outcome. It matters not who is chosen first and who is chosen second. The only thing that matters is the final verdict.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1484">
		<line-text>Promise me that if you become a Christian you'll become a Presbyterian.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1485">
		<line-text>Trees were so rare in that country, and they had to make such a hard fight to grow, that we used to feel anxious about them, and visit them as if they were persons. It must have been the scarcity of detail in that tawny landscape that made detail so precious.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1486">
		<line-text>The best things and the best people rise out of their separateness; I'm against a homogenized society because I want the cream to rise.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1487">
		<line-text>If you cannot find peace within yourself, you will never find it anywhere else.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1488">
		<line-text>We would accomplish many more things if we did not think of them as impossible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1489">
		<line-text>Great men's errors are to be venerated as more fruitful than little men's truths.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1490">
		<line-text>Don't put off for tomorrow what you can do today, because if you enjoy it today, you can do it again tomorrow.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1491">
		<line-text>God is a thing that thinks.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1492">
		<line-text>Evil is obvious only in retrospect.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1493">
		<line-text>Democracy encourages the majority to decide things about which the majority is blissfully ignorant.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1494">
		<line-text>The English have no respect for their language, and will not teach their children to speak it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1495">
		<line-text>Beauty is no quality in things themselves: it exists merely in the mind which contemplates them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1496">
		<line-text>ROMANCE, n. Fiction that owes no allegiance to the God of Things as They Are. In the novel the writer's thought is tethered to probability, as a domestic horse to the hitching-post, but in romance it ranges at will over the entire region of the imagination -- free, lawless, immune to bit and rein. Your novelist is a poor creature, as Carlyle might say -- a mere reporter. He may invent his characters and plot, but he must not imagine anything taking place that might not occur, albeit his entire narrative is candidly a lie. Why he imposes this hard condition on himself, and &quot;drags at each remove a lengthening chain&quot; of his own forging he can explain in ten thick volumes without illuminating by so much as a candle's ray the black profound of his own ignorance of the matter. There are great novels, for great writers have &quot;laid waste their powers&quot; to write them, but it remains true that far and away the most fascinating fiction that we have is &quot;The Thousand and One Nights.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1497">
		<line-text>Books are hindrances to persisting stupidity.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1498">
		<line-text>Do it now. It is not safe to leave a generous feeling to the cooling influences of the world.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1499">
		<line-text>We need never be ashamed of our tears.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1500">
		<line-text>They have been at a great feast of languages, and stolen the scraps.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1501">
		<line-text>The difference between a democracy and a dictatorship is that in a democracy you vote first and take orders later; in a dictatorship you don't have to waste your time voting.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1502">
		<line-text>Many that live deserve death. And some die that deserve life. Can you give it to them? Then be not too eager to deal out death in the name of justice, fearing for your own safety. Even the wise cannot see all ends.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1503">
		<line-text>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1504">
		<line-text>KING'S EVIL, n. A malady that was formerly cured by the touch of the sovereign, but has now to be treated by the physicians. Thus 'the most pious Edward&quot; of England used to lay his royal hand upon the ailing subjects and make them whole --

a crowd of wretched souls
That stay his cure: their malady convinces
The great essay of art; but at his touch,
Such sanctity hath Heaven given his hand,
They presently amend,

as the &quot;Doctor&quot; in _Macbeth_ hath it. This useful property of the royal hand could, it appears, be transmitted along with other crown properties; for according to &quot;Malcolm,&quot;
'tis spoken
To the succeeding royalty he leaves
The healing benediction.

But the gift somewhere dropped out of the line of succession: the later sovereigns of England have not been tactual healers, and the disease once honored with the name &quot;king's evil&quot; now bears the humbler one of &quot;scrofula,&quot; from _scrofa_, a sow. The date and author of the following epigram are known only to the author of this dictionary, but it is old enough to show that the jest about Scotland's national disorder is not a thing of yesterday.

Ye Kynge his evill in me laye,
Wh. he of Scottlande charmed awaye.
He layde his hand on mine and sayd:
&quot;Be gone!&quot; Ye ill no longer stayd.
But O ye wofull plyght in wh.
I'm now y-pight: I have ye itche!

The superstition that maladies can be cured by royal taction is dead, but like many a departed conviction it has left a monument of custom to keep its memory green. The practice of forming a line and shaking the President's hand had no other origin, and when that great dignitary bestows his healing salutation on

strangely visited people,
All swoln and ulcerous, pitiful to the eye,
The mere despair of surgery,

he and his patients are handing along an extinguished torch which once was kindled at the altar-fire of a faith long held by all classes of men. It is a beautiful and edifying &quot;survival&quot; -- one which brings the sainted past close home in our &quot;business and bosoms.&quot;</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1505">
		<line-text>Drink to me.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1506">
		<line-text>Your true value depends entirely on what you are compared with.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1507">
		<line-text>I adore simple pleasures. They are the last refuge of the complex.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1508">
		<line-text>JESTER, n. An officer formerly attached to a king's household, whose business it was to amuse the court by ludicrous actions and utterances, the absurdity being attested by his motley costume. The king himself being attired with dignity, it took the world some centuries to discover that his own conduct and decrees were sufficiently ridiculous for the amusement not only of his court but of all mankind. The jester was commonly called a fool, but the poets and romancers have ever delighted to represent him as a singularly wise and witty person. In the circus of to-day the melancholy ghost of the court fool effects the dejection of humbler audiences with the same jests wherewith in life he gloomed the marble hall, panged the patrician sense of humor and tapped the tank of royal tears.

The widow-queen of Portugal
Had an audacious jester
Who entered the confessional
Disguised, and there confessed her.

&quot;Father,&quot; she said, &quot;thine ear bend down --
My sins are more than scarlet:
I love my fool -- blaspheming clown,
And common, base-born varlet.&quot;

&quot;Daughter,&quot; the mimic priest replied,
&quot;That sin, indeed, is awful:
The church's pardon is denied
To love that is unlawful.

&quot;But since thy stubborn heart will be
For him forever pleading,
Thou'dst better make him, by decree,
A man of birth and breeding.&quot;

She made the fool a duke, in hope
With Heaven's taboo to palter;
Then told a priest, who told the Pope,
Who damned her from the altar!
Barel Dort</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1509">
		<line-text>Somewhere deep down we know that in the final analysis, we do decide things and that even our decisions to let someone else decide are really our decisions, however pusillanimous.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1510">
		<line-text>Never suffer the prejudice of the eye to determine the heart.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1511">
		<line-text>It's a rare person who wants to hear what he doesn't want to hear.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1512">
		<line-text>Convictions are more dangerous enemies of the truth than lies.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1513">
		<line-text>If people really want to go, and really try all their lives, I think they will get in; for I don’t believe there are any locks on that door, or any guards at the gate. I always imagine it is as it is in the picture, where the shining ones stretch out their hands to welcome poor Christian as he comes up from the river.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1514">
		<line-text>The essence of government is power; and power, lodged as it must be in human hands, will ever be liable to abuse.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1515">
		<line-text>The first duty of a leader is to make himself be loved without courting love. To be loved without 'playing up' to anyone - even to himself.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1516">
		<line-text>I believe that all government is evil, and that trying to improve it is largely a waste of time.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1517">
		<line-text>Examples is more forcible than precept. People look at my six days in the week to see what I mean on the seventh.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1518">
		<line-text>There are people whose watch stops at a certain hour and who remain permanently at that age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1519">
		<line-text>The love of those we don't love in return settles on the surface and from there quickly evaporates.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1520">
		<line-text>Have you heard that it was good to gain the day? I also say it is good to fall, battles are lost in the same spirit in which they are won.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1521">
		<line-text>One swallow does not make a summer.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1522">
		<line-text>Get all the fools on your side and you can be elected to anything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1523">
		<line-text>Of all the creatures that were made, man is the most detestable. Of the entire brood he is the only one--the solitary one--that possesses malice. That is the basest of all instincts, passions, vices--the most hateful. He is the only creature that has pain for sport, knowing it to be pain. Also--in all the list he is the only creature that has a nasty mind.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1524">
		<line-text>I just need enough to tide me over until I need more.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1525">
		<line-text>No flower of art ever fully blossomed save it was nourished by tears of agony.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1526">
		<line-text>It is not enough to aim; you must hit.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1527">
		<line-text>Give a man a fire and he's warm for the day. But set fire to him and he's warm for the rest of his life.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1528">
		<line-text>There's a rule in acting called, &quot;Don't play the result.&quot; If you have a character who's going to end up in a certain place, don't play that until you get there. Play each scene and each beat as it comes. And that's what you do in life: You don't play the result.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1529">
		<line-text>The right to be heard does not automatically include the right to be taken seriously.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1530">
		<line-text>Death is not extinguishing the light; it is putting out the lamp because the dawn has come.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1531">
		<line-text>The artist doesn't have time to listen to the critics. The ones who want to be writers read the reviews, the ones who want to write don't have the time to read reviews.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1532">
		<line-text>The intelligent man finds almost everything ridiculous, the sensible man hardly anything.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1533">
		<line-text>I'm not concerned that you have fallen,
I'm concerned that you arise.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1534">
		<line-text>Hope springs eternal in the human breast;
Man never Is, but always To be blest:
The soul, uneasy and confin'd from home,
Rests and expatiates in a life to come.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1535">
		<line-text>We can lick gravity, but sometimes the paperwork is overwhelming.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1536">
		<line-text>The goal of life is living in agreement with nature.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1537">
		<line-text>The thing women have yet to learn is nobody gives you power. You just take it.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1538">
		<line-text>Chastity is the greatest form of perversion.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1539">
		<line-text>Writers aren't exactly people...they're a whole lot of people trying to be one person.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1540">
		<line-text>Five thousand balloons, capable of raising two men each, could not cost more than five ships of the line; and where is the prince who can afford so to cover his country with troops for its defense as that 10,000 men descending from the clouds might not in many places do an infinite deal of mischief before a force could be brought together to repel them?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1541">
		<line-text>There is nothing more contagious on this planet than enthusiasm.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1542">
		<line-text>Isn't it fascinating how long a few minutes seem when you are completely alone with not a familiar face in sight?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1543">
		<line-text>I think that maybe in every company today there is always at least one person who is going crazy slowly.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1544">
		<line-text>Time is the coin of your life. It is the only coin you have, and only you can determine how it will be spent. Be careful lest you let other people spend it for you.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1545">
		<line-text>Children begin by loving their parents; as they grow older they judge them; sometimes they forgive them.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1546">
		<line-text>The past is a foreign country; they do things differently there.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1547">
		<line-text>It is a very hard undertaking to seek to please everybody.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1548">
		<line-text>A woman impudent and mannish grown is not more loathed than an effeminate man in time of action.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1549">
		<line-text>Over the past ten years, for the first time, intelligence had become socially correct for girls.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1550">
		<line-text>Hierarchical institutions are like giant bulldozers-- obedient to the whim of any fool who takes the controls.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1551">
		<line-text>It is not possible to conceive gods inhabiting a land which is made hideous by the smoke and din of mill chimneys and factories and whose roadways are traversed by rushing engines dragging numerous cars crowded with men mostly who know not what they are after.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1552">
		<line-text>Socialism needs democracy like the human body needs oxygen.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1553">
		<line-text>My mother drew a distinction between achievement and success. She said that 'achievement is the knowledge that you have studied and worked hard and done the best that is in you. Success is being praised by others, and that's nice, too, but not as important or satisfying. Always aim for achievement and forget about success.'</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1554">
		<line-text>Yes, if we were prepared to be honest we might rid ourselves of much self deception.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1555">
		<line-text>True strength lies in gentleness.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1556">
		<line-text>CHILDHOOD, n. The period of human life intermediate between the idiocy of infancy and the folly of youth -- two removes from the sin of manhood and three from the remorse of age.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1557">
		<line-text>Let me have men about me that are fat,
Sleek-headed men, and such as sleep o' nights:
Yond Cassius has a lean and hungry look;
He thinks too much: such men are dangerous.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1558">
		<line-text>Television is the first truly democratic culture - the first culture available to everybody and entirely governed by what the people want. The most terrifying thing is what people do want.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1559">
		<line-text>I don't think success is harmful, as so many people say. Rather, I believe it indispensable to talent, if for nothing else than to increase the talent.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1560">
		<line-text>What if you slept? And what if, in your sleep, you dreamed? And what if, in your dream, you went to heaven and plucked a strange and beautiful flower? And what if, when you awoke, you had the flower in your hand? Ah, what then?</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1561">
		<line-text>Life is either a daring adventure or nothing. Security does not exist in nature, nor do the children of men as a whole experience it. Avoiding danger is no safer in the long run than exposure.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1562">
		<line-text>Energy is eternal delight.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1563">
		<line-text>EVERLASTING, adj. Lasting forever. It is with no small diffidence that I venture to offer this brief and elementary definition, for I am not unaware of the existence of a bulky volume by a sometime Bishop of Worcester, entitled, _A Partial Definition of the Word &quot;Everlasting,&quot; as Used in the Authorized Version of the Holy Scriptures_. His book was once esteemed of great authority in the Anglican Church, and is still, I understand, studied with pleasure to the mind and profit of the soul.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1564">
		<line-text>Some of my friends support the measure, and some of my friends oppose it. I support my friends.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1565">
		<line-text>I wish you well and so I take my leave,
I Pray you know me when we meet again.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1566">
		<line-text>Electronic communication is an instantaneous and illusory contact that creates a sense of intimacy without the emotional investment that leads to close friendships.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1567">
		<line-text>So, let us not be blind to our differences - but let us also direct attention to our common interests and to the means by which those differences can be resolved.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1568">
		<line-text>Think of life as a giant, fat cat you're in charge of. Sometimes you can control it, but other times, it's going to do what it wants and you have to roll with it. And sometimes you can do everything - everything you're s'posed to do- and it'll still shred all the things you hold dear... The only thing you can really do with life is rub its belly and prepare for the worst.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1569">
		<line-text>Money is a terrible master but an excellent servant.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1570">
		<line-text>To make no mistakes is not in the power of man; but from their errors and mistakes the wise and good learn wisdom for the future.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1571">
		<line-text>I can believe anything, provided that it is quite incredible.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1572">
		<line-text>Fashion is for people who don't know who they are.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1573">
		<line-text>To play it safe is not to play.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1574">
		<line-text>Out of life's school of war: What does not destroy me, makes me stronger.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1575">
		<line-text>Our test of truth is a reference to either a present or imagined future majority in favour of our view.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1576">
		<line-text>Is demum miser est, cuius nobilitas miserias nobilitat.
(Indeed, wretched the man whose fame makes his misfortunes famous.)</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1577">
		<line-text>Wise sayings often fall on barren ground; but a kind word is never thrown away.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1578">
		<line-text>Sundown, yellow moon, I replay the past. I know every scene by heart, they all went by so fast.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1579">
		<line-text>Life itself is a quotation.</line-text>
	</line>
	<line id="1580">
		<line-text>Why have many saints been so perfectly contemplative? Because they always studied to mortify themselves from worldly desires, that they might freely, with all the power of their heart, tend to our Lord.</line-text>
	</line>
</lines>
